<X-word-ms ms=100,119,740,299,240,239,680,799,500,360 index=2 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-10,11-15,16-21,22-23,24-28,29-33,34-38,39-41>been a long time since I last used Zoom so
<X-word-ms ms=299,1000,160,299,539,380,119,200 index=3 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-19,20-24,25-29,30-32,33-38>more than the Google Meet sort of thing
<X-word-ms ms=279,700,580,159,160,120,199,339,240 index=4 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-7,8-10,11-13,14-15,16-21,22-27,28-32>So i had to do a quick setup here
<X-word-ms ms=259,140,259,200,159,80,140,400 index=5 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-16,17-20,21-23,24-27,28-37>To make sure that I'm on the spotlight
<X-word-ms ms=320,359,320,679,160,80 index=6 character_ranges=0-2,3-12,13-16,17-23,24-26,27-29>Now everybody can really be in
<X-word-ms ms=80,240,299,259,600 index=7 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-18,19-29>The chat and listen everything
<X-word-ms ms=359,800,239,240,199,259 index=8 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-14,15-20,21-23,24-28>And this screen share is fine
So yeah
Awesome Today it going
<X-word-ms ms=220,399,379,360,159,440,1080 index=11 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-12,13-16,17-27,28-39>Be day one Of the SwinTrader Masterclass
<X-word-ms ms=279,199,160,0,520,419,160,199,199,100 index=12 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-15,16-23,24-27,28-31,32-35,36-41,42-44>This is going To replace the old one which of
<X-word-ms ms=280,559,600,299,240,239,280 index=13 character_ranges=0-5,6-7,8-15,16-19,20-23,24-28,29-32>course I deleted not too long ago
<X-word-ms ms=439,440,279,160,179,200 index=14 character_ranges=0-7,8-15,16-19,20-25,26-28,29-34>Awesome, awesome i'm going to close
<X-word-ms ms=139,140,179,179,179,160,60,159,280,159,80,259 index=15 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-15,16-23,24-28,29-34,35-37,38-45,46-48,49-51,52-58>The chat for now because it's Going to clutter on my screen
But once we get
<X-word-ms ms=100,219,280,219,380,119 index=17 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-5,6-8,9-14,15-20>To Q&A so We're going
Do is just kick
<X-word-ms ms=119,79,120,179,460,259 index=19 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-16,17-19,20-27>It off from Start Go through
Beginning You know
On Fundamentals Go
Into Setup And go
Through A lot
Of charts Explanation
Then Get into
<X-word-ms ms=340,179,100,279,320 index=26 character_ranges=0-0,1-2,3-4,5-12,13-15>Q & a Section So
We're Going To Do
The Q N E End
You Can Easily
Just Slam All
Questions If you Have
<X-word-ms ms=299,79,79,399,400 index=32 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-14,15-17>In The Chat And By
<X-word-ms ms=199,119,120,500,119 index=33 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-22,23-24>the End Of Presentation I
<X-word-ms ms=60,140,159,219,120,79,200,179 index=34 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-16,17-19,20-23,24-28,29-32>Will Just Go Back On The Chat And
<X-word-ms ms=179,79,240,280,59,179 index=35 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-16,17-18,19-23,24-28>Look At Questions I Have Some
Questions That I
<X-word-ms ms=200,200,179,219,239 index=37 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-14,15-18>Piled Up From A Lot
Of Members We're
<X-word-ms ms=140,219,120,219,159,340 index=39 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-15,16-18,19-23>Not Able To Make It Live
In The Presentations
But Send Me Question
So I Can Condense
A Lot Inside You
Know Simple Questions
That Touch More Or
Less Same Thing Again
<X-word-ms ms=400,19,99,160,200,260 index=47 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-15,16-18,19-26>This Is Going Be An Awesome
Presentation Really Was
<X-word-ms ms=199,220,179,219,320 index=49 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-17,18-22>Here To Do Another Live
<X-word-ms ms=219,219,259,239,120 index=50 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-17,18-21>Like This So Thank You
<X-word-ms ms=79,179,180,359,260 index=51 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-20,21-24>Very Much For Joining For
<X-word-ms ms=199,240,339,140,140 index=52 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-15,16-17,18-22>Being Here Alive I Know
Sunday Is Not Ideal
<X-word-ms ms=220,179,260,219,340 index=54 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-10,11-16,17-22>To Do These Stuff Right
But It Was The
<X-word-ms ms=219,159,140,180,479 index=56 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-16,17-21>Day That Could Be Make
Sure To Be And
You Know The
Time Zone Is Best
For Everybody Around The
<X-word-ms ms=180,319,480,379,240 index=61 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-13,14-18,19-24>World From The West Coast
In The US East Coast
Now Europeans And
Australians Nations Could Be
<X-word-ms ms=120,159,299,400,179 index=65 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-15,16-20>All The Same You Know
<X-word-ms ms=219,120,320,179,120,219 index=66 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-13,14-16,17-20,21-23>Kind Of Window We Can Be
At This Time You
<X-word-ms ms=140,240,179,359,79,299 index=68 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-18,19-20,21-27>Know But Again It's A Sunday
So Again Think
<X-word-ms ms=99,219,200,260,420 index=70 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-15,16-18,19-24>About Being Here So Let'S
Get Started With These
<X-word-ms ms=179,60,99,120,120,140,519 index=72 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-17,18-20,21-23,24-34>You Know Are Going To Be Discussing
Today Fundamentals And Setup
<X-word-ms ms=319,209,159,200,420 index=74 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-15,16-18>So Were Going To Go
Deep Into First
<X-word-ms ms=140,180,299,260,200 index=76 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-12,13-22,23-26>Of All Define Amountles Why
Would Should Be You
<X-word-ms ms=179,200,180,159,140,219 index=78 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-10,11-13,14-16,17-21>Know Why We Do Is Soon
<X-word-ms ms=200,140,119,180,439 index=79 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-15,16-25>Tree What Is The Advantage
<X-word-ms ms=159,239,240,200,379 index=80 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-12,13-17,18-22>Of Really You Know Soon
<X-word-ms ms=140,179,140,219,260,79 index=81 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-13,14-18,19-25,26-27>Train To Begin With That's A
<X-word-ms ms=180,179,159,160,259,100 index=82 character_ranges=0-7,8-10,11-15,16-18,19-22,23-25>Question We Have To Ask Or
<X-word-ms ms=140,159,179,219,360 index=83 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-13,14-20,21-28>Have To Answer Before Getting
And Going Deeper
<X-word-ms ms=39,140,219,280,480 index=85 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-17,18-25>Are Going To Start Talking
About How We
Do It Specifically Here
How We Do It
Here In Liberty Signal
<X-word-ms ms=460,239,140,139,340 index=90 character_ranges=0-7,8-12,13-16,17-20,21-31>Specific What Are The Principles
That We You
<X-word-ms ms=219,219,239,159,300 index=92 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-10,11-15,16-23>Know Try To Move Forward
<X-word-ms ms=219,159,80,60,159,120,319 index=93 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-17,18-23,24-26,27-34>With And Then Were Going Go Through
<X-word-ms ms=419,140,219,180,439 index=94 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-12,13-17,18-23>I Could Cover Your Setup
Trade Something Based On
That Is A Structural
<X-word-ms ms=240,139,100,219,119,160,179 index=97 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-18,19-21,22-26,27-36>Thing To The Market So It's Something
That Do We Stocks
<X-word-ms ms=140,300,219,199,159 index=99 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-14,15-18,19-21>Really Move Its Not As
You Know Just
<X-word-ms ms=139,360,180,179,320 index=101 character_ranges=0-1,2-9,10-12,13-16,17-26>An Opinion Is Not Something
<X-word-ms ms=219,159,259,240,239 index=102 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-14,15-17>That We See And We
Try Too Or You
Know Another Side From
Opinions Very You
Know Crunchy Number Things
<X-word-ms ms=299,159,159,180,159,460 index=107 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-13,14-19,20-30>That In All Of These Conditions
<X-word-ms ms=199,360,219,139,460 index=108 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-12,13-17,18-23>Are Super You Know Stuff
Has Go Up You
<X-word-ms ms=79,240,280,199,40,280 index=110 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-6,7-11,12-16,17-19>Know 4% Then Then Go
Back Lower 2%
And Then An Inside
Day 1 One Percent
<X-word-ms ms=259,120,120,180,459 index=114 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-8,9-14,15-19>I Know Of These Very
Specific Rules That They
<X-word-ms ms=180,60,120,259,259,200 index=116 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-16,17-19,20-22>Tend To Be Curved It So
We're Going On Going
<X-word-ms ms=140,179,240,99,500 index=118 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-14,15-27>To Show You The Fundamentals
<X-word-ms ms=159,240,240,299,280 index=119 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-17,18-24>Off Why This Thing Really
Works Because Is Just
A Way Stocks
<X-word-ms ms=180,219,99,199,80,120,120 index=122 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-16,17-18,19-22,23-25>Move I'm Going Do A Lot Of
<X-word-ms ms=379,319,140,139,199 index=123 character_ranges=0-7,8-15,16-21,22-24,25-27>Examples There's Going To Be
<X-word-ms ms=240,379,219,120,280 index=124 character_ranges=0-2,3-10,11-13,14-16,17-21>Eye Opening In My View
So It'S Gonna
<X-word-ms ms=400,180,40,219,239 index=126 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-13,14-16,17-22>Be The Section Of Trend
So First
<X-word-ms ms=159,200,419,159,120 index=128 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-15,16-19>Of All Right Off The
<X-word-ms ms=180,299,99,420,280 index=129 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-18,19-23>Butt We Are Trading When
I'm Training Anything From
<X-word-ms ms=139,159,300,379,560 index=131 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-15,16-20,21-29>The Church Where Only Focusing
<X-word-ms ms=180,120,199,259,200,120 index=132 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-17,18-20,21-26>On The Fast Action Of Their
<X-word-ms ms=259,120,139,159,159,140,180 index=133 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-14,15-17,18-22,23-26,27-30>Train And Going To Show You How
It Defined A
<X-word-ms ms=240,240,199,120,219 index=135 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-13,14-18,19-23>Fast Action Of That Trim
But Essentially Is
<X-word-ms ms=139,199,120,180,219,319,540 index=137 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-15,16-18,19-22,23-31>When We Get Into An Non-Volatile
Linear Tren So
There Are Just You
<X-word-ms ms=140,379,199,140,99,719 index=140 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-10,11-14,15-19,20-26>Know Have A Lot More Buyers
Than The 20 In
May That's The Type
<X-word-ms ms=140,299,340,120,219 index=143 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-13,14-16,17-23>Of Trend Which Is Called
<X-word-ms ms=139,120,80,159,439,259 index=144 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-9,10-13,14-22,23-28>You Know A Non-Volatile Train
Out None Non Volat
<X-word-ms ms=99,240,180,479,120 index=146 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-16,17-22,23-26>All These Because There Are
Just Mostly Buyers
So There Is No
Volatility They Know
<X-word-ms ms=460,159,99,99,360 index=150 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-18>And This Is The Way
It Stacks Really Move
<X-word-ms ms=319,120,199,219,539 index=152 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-18,19-25>When We Have Strong Linear
Market And Can
<X-word-ms ms=139,140,119,260,359 index=154 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-16,17-21>See This In Index Even
That Starts To Really
Move Higher With
<X-word-ms ms=259,180,199,280,199 index=157 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-19,20-22>You Know Their Range Of
<X-word-ms ms=120,159,80,159,159,80,359 index=158 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-15,16-18,19-21,22-27>The Kind Of Send To Be Small
10 Or No More
Less Smarter Or Medium
Or You Know Normal
<X-word-ms ms=480,100,119,220,220 index=162 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-10,11-17,18-22>But It Into Follow This
Linearity Move That
<X-word-ms ms=100,159,160,219,160,360 index=164 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-19,20-21,22-28>They Start To Moving A Linear
Way And There
<X-word-ms ms=159,379,160,280,219 index=166 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-17,18-20>Very Easy To Trade On
Right Obviously These
<X-word-ms ms=120,140,239,120,560 index=168 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-16,17-21>Are The Ones That Give
<X-word-ms ms=160,180,259,240,439 index=169 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-15,16-19>Us The Most Best You
Know Risk Reward Obviously
So We Want To
Capture You Know
Them Is Mid
Off Trend So Whenever
<X-word-ms ms=120,259,159,180,139,240 index=175 character_ranges=0-7,8-11,12-16,17-21,22-23,24-29>Breakout You Know From A Multi
Week Base And
<X-word-ms ms=259,139,100,359,160 index=177 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-23,24-28>Then In The Intermediate Term
<X-word-ms ms=279,380,139,79,120,220 index=178 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-16,17-20,21-25>Trend You Want To See Data
<X-word-ms ms=199,259,240,159,180 index=179 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-7,8-10,11-14>Net 20 M As You
<X-word-ms ms=60,160,120,199,199,139,100,139 index=180 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-17,18-20,21-22,23-27,28-31>Know Start To Line Up I Will See
<X-word-ms ms=100,240,159,360,159 index=181 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-15,16-20,21-22>That Train Above This E
<X-word-ms ms=180,120,420,139,139,200 index=182 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-13,14-17,18-21>Am Is But They Are Not
<X-word-ms ms=319,139,139,79,280,240 index=183 character_ranges=0-6,7-12,13-16,17-18,19-21,22-23>Closing Below The T Em S
That's The Medium Intermedia
<X-word-ms ms=319,120,240,219,100,120 index=185 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-14,15-18,19-21,22-24>Tram Going Show All Of It
Is Below Obviously By
<X-word-ms ms=160,159,140,279,120,180 index=187 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-20,21-25,26-28>Just Give An Overview That We
<X-word-ms ms=79,420,120,120,139,699 index=188 character_ranges=0-2,3-11,12-14,15-16,17-21,22-30>Are Focusing On A Very Specific
<X-word-ms ms=400,199,120,240,399 index=189 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-13,14-19,20-22>Section Of The Trend We
<X-word-ms ms=139,259,360,160,219 index=190 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-13,14-16,17-22>Are Not Trying To Trade
Everything Or Not
Trying To Trade Every
Single No Part Of
<X-word-ms ms=180,360,159,120,240 index=194 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-17,18-23>This Cycle Off The Train
Or Stock Is
<X-word-ms ms=179,140,339,199,339 index=196 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-19,20-24,25-30>Really Going Through With Entry
Breakouts From Big Basis
<X-word-ms ms=199,79,160,219,160,579 index=198 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-17,18-20,21-24>You Know They Tend Be You
<X-word-ms ms=100,199,479,180,100 index=199 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-15,16-17>Have To Try Them A
<X-word-ms ms=99,140,379,219,100,199 index=200 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-11,12-14,15-20,21-24>Lot Of Times In Order Too
<X-word-ms ms=319,220,120,120,120,159 index=201 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-16,17-20,21-26>Catch It And Once You Catch
<X-word-ms ms=160,79,180,219,200,239 index=202 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-14,15-18,19-26>It Had To Write Out Because
<X-word-ms ms=219,100,120,240,180,219 index=203 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-15,16-18,19-23>You Have To Make Up With
<X-word-ms ms=339,200,180,179,260 index=204 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-15,16-22>Know This Use Of Losses
<X-word-ms ms=99,120,120,579,439 index=205 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-14,15-26>That You Got So Essentially
<X-word-ms ms=279,259,200,259,399 index=206 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-17,18-19>That Turns It Into A
Low Success Rate System
And The Problem Without
<X-word-ms ms=259,180,220,180,60,259 index=209 character_ranges=0-6,7-8,9-13,14-19,20-22,23-30>Whether I Want Going To Discuss
<X-word-ms ms=139,259,259,120,80,120,79 index=210 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-15,16-20,21-23,24-27,28-30>This Again Don't Want To Get In
<X-word-ms ms=360,239,180,220,439 index=211 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-15,16-19,20-22>Detail Right Now But We
<X-word-ms ms=79,79,300,180,259,379 index=212 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-14,15-20,21-25,26-30>Would Do Discus About Just Keep
<X-word-ms ms=160,159,100,139,20,219,319 index=213 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-14,15-18,19-22,23-26>In Mind That We Are One Two
Camps Or Defend
<X-word-ms ms=199,180,60,259,300,199 index=215 character_ranges=0-6,7-10,11-14,15-20,21-25,26-31>Section Off The Train Then Trade
<X-word-ms ms=159,80,179,420,660 index=216 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-23,24-35>You Know From Volatility Contraction
To Expansion Within
That Fast Section Of
<X-word-ms ms=100,159,140,219,120,620 index=219 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-14,15-18,19-28>The Train So We Are Targeting
A Very Specific
Set You Know Movement
<X-word-ms ms=260,159,220,279,480 index=222 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-15,16-20>Off This Time So Then
That's Pretty Important And
That'S Essentially When We
<X-word-ms ms=120,199,220,379,319 index=225 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-17,18-22>Can Get These Fast Five
Day Moves That
Produce Profit
<X-word-ms ms=120,220,139,139,199,160,120 index=228 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-14,15-19,20-25,26-28>And Gives Us An Edge Which Is
<X-word-ms ms=139,120,199,160,99,220,220 index=229 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-14,15-17,18-22,23-25,26-30>The Whole Point Of This So What
<X-word-ms ms=120,99,220,379,139,139 index=230 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-14,15-16,17-22>It Up Stop With A Tight
Stop Again Tied
It's Relative Right Right
With Especially For Us
<X-word-ms ms=79,100,240,159,240,300 index=234 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-15,16-19,20-22>That We Trade Of Day It
Doesn't Might Not Look
That Tight But You
<X-word-ms ms=180,379,299,120,580 index=237 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-16,17-26>Know Can You Know Comparing
<X-word-ms ms=219,139,160,60,199,160,219 index=238 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-12,13-18,19-21,22-31>This To Buy A Whole Or Something
Like That Obviously Is
<X-word-ms ms=39,160,240,219,379 index=240 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-10,11-18,19-23>A Type Stop Because Your
Entering On The Breakout
<X-word-ms ms=79,79,220,540,159 index=242 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-17,18-19>Of The Day Putting A
<X-word-ms ms=240,240,99,160,79,100,79,79 index=243 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-14,15-17,18-21,22-24,25-27>Stop In All Bit Of The Lo Up
Today Only No Four
Long Order They Have
<X-word-ms ms=179,260,119,380,520 index=246 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-14,15-17,18-24>Ready For Short So That's
A Relatively Tight Stop
And We Want To
Look For Asymmetric Risk
Rewards So We
<X-word-ms ms=199,180,79,160,180,379 index=251 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-14,15-18,19-29>Have You Know A Big Percentage
Of Our Trades Are
Break Even So But
That'S Why The Average
Risk Reward And This
Accessory Which I Count
No Brick Events As
<X-word-ms ms=420,180,100,159,100,319 index=258 character_ranges=0-7,8-10,11-14,15-19,20-23,24-28>Positive Is But They Are Zero
<X-word-ms ms=240,159,280,279,300 index=259 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-14,15-19,20-22>So The Averaged Down By
Essentially The
<X-word-ms ms=399,220,199,180,420 index=261 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-17,18-21,22-25>Average Risk Award One Two
1.35 Includes
Break Evens As Positive
<X-word-ms ms=159,120,360,240,179 index=264 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-14,15-22,23-27>Is Not Negative Because It's
A Negative Doesn't Have
The Psychological Implication
<X-word-ms ms=120,139,120,180,240,119,100 index=267 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-9,10-18,19-25,26-29,30-31>Of Being A Negative That'S Why I
Include Them But
If You Include Deeper
Keepings In On The
Lost Side Off
The Things Right We
<X-word-ms ms=139,79,100,159,200,239,360 index=273 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-16,17-24,25-29,30-36>Will See That The Average Risk Reward
Infact Its Above One
To Two Point Something
With 45%
Success Rate So
<X-word-ms ms=260,239,160,160,199 index=278 character_ranges=0-8,9-11,12-15,16-19,20-26>Depending On How You Really
<X-word-ms ms=219,100,139,160,359,160 index=279 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-14,15-19,20-26,27-30>Count The Break Even Trades You
<X-word-ms ms=100,219,420,219,600 index=280 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-17,18-30>Will See But Their Relationship
<X-word-ms ms=199,120,280,259,39,160 index=281 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-15,16-19,20-27>There Is Same We Are Looking
For An Asymmetric Risk
Reward Scenario You
<X-word-ms ms=180,180,199,139,259,240 index=284 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-14,15-20,21-28>Want To Enter A Trade Knowing
<X-word-ms ms=199,219,180,180,259 index=285 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-13,14-15,16-21>Of Course Have A Train
<X-word-ms ms=199,180,180,340,79,819 index=286 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-14,15-18,19-32>How About It In Our Consolidation
Virtual With Momentum
And Volatility Contraction
Two Expansion And
When We Enter De
<X-word-ms ms=339,100,239,60,240,300 index=291 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-17,18-27,28-31>Brick Out They Are Obviously One
<X-word-ms ms=160,159,240,79,160,420 index=292 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-13,14-18,19-27>To Put Ours Up Into Position
That D Reward
<X-word-ms ms=160,139,120,100,120,359,239 index=294 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-13,14-15,16-24,25-28>Is Going To Be A Multiple You
Know Preferably Over Time
As An Average Of
<X-word-ms ms=139,199,120,60,180,340 index=297 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-21,22-28>The Risk We Are Really Taking
<X-word-ms ms=239,200,479,40,139 index=298 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-12,13-16>Right So If I Can
Get That Profit Protecting
The Downside And
Moving Detectives That Were
<X-word-ms ms=199,160,159,259,260 index=302 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-13,14-16,17-19>Used To Really Do So
To Control De
Losing Trades And Off
<X-word-ms ms=200,159,180,300,360 index=305 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-12,13-20,21-23>Course It Run Overall As
An Equity Core We
Want Always Look For
Symmetric Resour Scenarios
Will Write Five To
Make A
Lot Of Returns
Trailing In The Market
Condition Which By
The Way Since 2020
Probably We
<X-word-ms ms=99,139,240,200,99,280 index=316 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-18,19-23,24-28,29-35>Never Had Something Like That Before
So Yeah Few Stock
<X-word-ms ms=200,259,240,180,179 index=318 character_ranges=0-2,3-10,11-15,16-19,20-25>Are Running Here And There
But It's Just One
Stalking 5,000
<X-word-ms ms=159,100,220,159,100,339 index=321 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-15,16-19,20-23,24-30>Is Not Something You Can Repeat
Yourself And
Really Profit From That
Consistently And Predictably
Based On An
Edge Yeah You Bought
<X-word-ms ms=120,100,300,239,340 index=327 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-10,11-16,17-22>As In Decay Early Great
<X-word-ms ms=259,220,159,139,160,159 index=328 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-12,13-16,17-20,21-25>Great For You But How Many
Stocks Really Did
So In The Last
<X-word-ms ms=279,160,259,240,160 index=331 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-14,15-17,18-21>Couple Of Month Or The
Last Year You Know
<X-word-ms ms=320,179,240,100,99,180 index=333 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-16,17-23,24-28>How Many Stalk Is Really Made
<X-word-ms ms=80,120,159,160,99,100,139,220 index=334 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-10,11-12,13-14,15-16,17-18,19-22>A Move Like S N D K Are
<X-word-ms ms=159,180,160,120,139,439 index=335 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-16,17-22,23-31>Going To Base Our Whole Strategy
On One Stalk
In 10,000
<X-word-ms ms=200,319,139,80,159,440 index=338 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-7,8-9,10-15,16-24>In The U.S Stock Universe
Really Moved
<X-word-ms ms=220,139,240,299,280 index=340 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-15,16-25>It's Not That So Something
We Can Really Capitalize
On So You
Know People See
<X-word-ms ms=179,279,240,120,120,139 index=344 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-17,18-19,20-21>This Rule When The C S
<X-word-ms ms=259,100,179,400,299 index=345 character_ranges=0-0,1-2,3-4,5-11,12-17>N D K Moving There
Like But Why
<X-word-ms ms=280,159,299,259,340 index=347 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-13,14-16,17-20>Don't We Trail Of Its
Not A Repeatable Edge
<X-word-ms ms=179,100,139,179,160,139,139 index=349 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-14,15-22,23-28,29-31>In Or Some Time They're Going To
<X-word-ms ms=80,159,139,379,620 index=350 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-16,17-29>Be Able To Profit Consistently
And Really Let
<X-word-ms ms=120,360,200,99,200,240 index=352 character_ranges=0-0,1-13,14-16,17-21,22-28,29-35>A Distribution Of Your System Really
<X-word-ms ms=200,219,139,60,259,460 index=353 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-10,11-14,15-24,25-35>Play Out Is Not Something Repeatable
So If I'm The
<X-word-ms ms=259,379,100,179,500 index=355 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-14,15-19>Most Tend To Be This
<X-word-ms ms=300,100,279,299,399 index=356 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-16,17-19>It's Part In Fact If
You Average Everything Now
<X-word-ms ms=159,200,240,239,300 index=358 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-16,17-24>That Based On The Moments
Are Really Go With
Very Strong You Know
Trailing Trades If
<X-word-ms ms=139,139,220,200,259,299 index=362 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-15,16-19,20-24,25-28>You Have Reached Out Them The
<X-word-ms ms=200,359,160,139,220 index=363 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-13,14-16,17-19>Moment Then Do Is If
<X-word-ms ms=139,159,120,240,299,340 index=364 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-14,15-20,21-26>We Try To Trade Every Thing
<X-word-ms ms=440,120,239,140,99 index=365 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-12,13-16,17-20>In Our Market And Its
Not Favor For Trading
There Your Going
<X-word-ms ms=179,200,200,359,200 index=368 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-7,8-11,12-14>To Get A Lot Of
Very Small
<X-word-ms ms=419,60,100,240,440 index=370 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-12,13-16,17-21>Treats And If You Have
A Lot
Of Ingredients
That Makes Trading Easy
<X-word-ms ms=259,100,120,299,200,660 index=374 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-8,9-16,17-20,21-33>I Want To Discuss The Distribution
<X-word-ms ms=439,340,39,100,80,120 index=375 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-15,16-18,19-21>But We Are Going To Go
Deeper Into The
Next Session But
Again Five Day Moves
It's A Golden
Rule Is Going Keep
You Out Of You
Know Every Single
<X-word-ms ms=199,360,259,100,200 index=383 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-16,17-19,20-21>Time Buying Stock In A
Stock Or Setting Short
Of Whatever We Have
Risk As Were
Holding It That's
<X-word-ms ms=259,240,120,379,419 index=388 character_ranges=0-8,9-12,13-17,18-22,23-30>Something You Know That Happens
<X-word-ms ms=120,100,439,180,159,200 index=389 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-10,11-16,17-20,21-23>To Be There Going Can Be
Gap Gaps Up
No GAP Ups
<X-word-ms ms=79,140,299,240,299 index=392 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-14,15-21>Are Got Down So Things
Can Happen If You
Limit Any Single Exposure
<X-word-ms ms=220,179,299,139,320 index=395 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-12,13-17>To Start At 5 Days
<X-word-ms ms=220,319,139,200,180 index=396 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-15,16-21,22-24>Also The Meeting Their Is
Of Something Really
<X-word-ms ms=379,200,139,200,159 index=398 character_ranges=0-8,9-13,14-18,19-22,23-25>Happening This Just Way It
Is And You
Know It Is Proven
<X-word-ms ms=159,139,299,340,120 index=401 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-13,14-19,20-22>To Keep Equity Curve At
Highs Very Consistent
And The Most Importantly
It Tends To Capture
Profits In Most
Market Conditions In
More Most Market Phases
<X-word-ms ms=139,80,180,359,259 index=408 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-22,23-25>Which Is Most Important So
I Know A Lot
Of Traders That They
Have Higher You
Know Annual Compounded
Growth Rate Than I
<X-word-ms ms=220,289,280,159,199 index=414 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-12,13-17>Do But If You Look
At Them And See
Their Track Records This
Are January 2020 Just
<X-word-ms ms=179,279,200,39,220,310 index=418 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-16,17-21,22-25>Like Mine When We Just See
How The Systems
<X-word-ms ms=200,399,139,100,339 index=420 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-14,15-21>And You Know It Really
Compares They Kind
Of Front Loaded Like
<X-word-ms ms=179,200,139,580,500 index=423 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-11,12-15,16-16>I Don't Know 600%
Return On 2020
<X-word-ms ms=309,180,219,139,100,180 index=425 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-17,18-21,22-26,27-31>Because They Trail All That Time
Right Since 2021
<X-word-ms ms=440,159,200,100,199 index=427 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-15,16-20>Is Being Kind Of Flat
Yes Some Profit Here
There But Off
Course They Have Winning
Years Obviously But These
<X-word-ms ms=340,139,319,160,399 index=432 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-15,16-18,19-23>Stats Are Skewed Up From
Loaded By 20
By 2020 And
Trailing So That's
Not Something Repeatable That's
<X-word-ms ms=220,259,259,240,320 index=437 character_ranges=0-8,9-12,13-17,18-27,28-32>Something Not Know Something That
<X-word-ms ms=339,200,220,179,360 index=438 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-16,17-19>You Know Is Going We
<X-word-ms ms=80,120,139,99,120,60,240,220 index=439 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-15,16-20,21-22,23-27,28-33>Are Not Going To Have A 2020 Every
<X-word-ms ms=220,279,120,240,200 index=440 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-13,14-19,20-22>Single Time In Fight It
<X-word-ms ms=79,180,120,259,199,120,120 index=441 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-9,10-15,16-20,21-23,24-27>Has Been A While Like We Had
Didn't Have A 20
Year With Hope
Of One Right So
<X-word-ms ms=440,199,159,140,179 index=445 character_ranges=0-5,6-12,13-16,17-21,22-26>That'S Always The Best Case
Scenario But Whenever
<X-word-ms ms=179,159,140,119,220,180,179 index=447 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-15,16-22,23-28,29-31>No What I'm Just Really Going To
<X-word-ms ms=159,240,340,179,120 index=448 character_ranges=0-1,2-12,13-18,19-22,23-27>Do Especially Right Now With
Iran War Going On
And Its Currently
Not Stopping So
<X-word-ms ms=480,120,139,179,100 index=452 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-14,15-19,20-24>We Don't Really Know What
<X-word-ms ms=80,120,139,339,220,240 index=453 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-17,18-21,22-23>Is Going To Happen And I
<X-word-ms ms=200,179,139,259,540 index=454 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-10,11-15,16-20>Don'T See A 2020 Year
<X-word-ms ms=219,80,159,259,840 index=455 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-17,18-26>You Know Right Now Although
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,220,299,280 index=456 character_ranges=0-0,1-4,5-9,10-17,18-26>I See Some Bullish Pressure
<X-word-ms ms=199,200,139,120,139,240 index=457 character_ranges=0-7,8-11,12-15,16-21,22-26,27-31>Building Out But Again That Will
<X-word-ms ms=299,240,259,139,220 index=458 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-10,11-14,15-22>Be At Topic For Another
Day But Ready
In Five Days Months
It'S Super Efficient
Add So Many Level
<X-word-ms ms=220,240,120,240,259 index=463 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-9,10-13,14-18>There IS A Lot That
<X-word-ms ms=199,300,240,219,220 index=464 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-15,16-20,21-25>Really Goes Into This Rule
That Is Not
<X-word-ms ms=259,200,259,200,79,139 index=466 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-13,14-18,19-21,22-25>Just No Sudden Idea At The
<X-word-ms ms=40,120,179,340,179,100,379 index=467 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-8,9-12,13-17,18-22,23-29>End Of 50 And It'S Very Simple
<X-word-ms ms=200,440,200,99,200 index=468 character_ranges=0-1,2-9,10-14,15-17,18-25>To Execute That Is Another
Benefit IS You
<X-word-ms ms=480,99,120,240,279 index=470 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-13,14-19,20-24>Don't Have Too Think Much
<X-word-ms ms=180,120,319,300,179 index=471 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-19,20-22>You Know This Stress Of
Really Holding A Position
<X-word-ms ms=299,159,260,220,159 index=473 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-11,12-16,17-19>In Trying To Come Up
Discretionally Based
<X-word-ms ms=200,139,379,279,660 index=475 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-15,16-18,19-23>On Your Opinions Or What
<X-word-ms ms=259,159,220,360,199 index=476 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-12,13-18,19-27>Do See Social Media Whatever
To Pay When I
Exit The Trade We
<X-word-ms ms=139,59,139,200,360,240 index=479 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-14,15-22,23-27,28-31>Don'T Have That Problem Here I'm
<X-word-ms ms=120,179,279,140,359 index=480 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-15,16-19,20-28>Going Talk About The Benefits
<X-word-ms ms=140,259,159,120,100,219,220 index=481 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-14,15-17,18-20,21-25>Of Real What Do We Do Here
But We Don't Have
<X-word-ms ms=100,259,159,199,180,360 index=483 character_ranges=0-0,1-8,9-11,12-18,19-24,25-32>A Problem Of Really Going Through
When Should Be No
<X-word-ms ms=220,139,399,200,339 index=485 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-15,16-18,19-23>Close The Trades If This
<X-word-ms ms=200,139,259,200,259 index=486 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-13,14-19>Is Too Much It Isn't
<X-word-ms ms=279,200,120,139,120,39,159 index=487 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-14,15-20,21-25,26-30>Now You Know We Don'T Have That
Problem Luckily So
The Whole Point Off
<X-word-ms ms=200,299,400,99,139 index=490 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-16,17-19,20-24>Swim Trading This Is Most
<X-word-ms ms=280,279,159,159,219 index=491 character_ranges=0-8,9-14,15-17,18-22,23-27>Important Thing Is That They
Want To Compound Hundreds
Of Traits To Achieve
In Average Return Over
<X-word-ms ms=199,320,159,180,199 index=495 character_ranges=0-2,3-3,4-7,8-12,13-17>100% Per Year With
Low Drawdown So Compounding
<X-word-ms ms=219,300,319,160,159 index=497 character_ranges=0-7,8-10,11-17,18-20,21-24>Hundreds Of Traits Is The
Key Here We Are
<X-word-ms ms=100,299,240,279,260 index=499 character_ranges=0-2,3-10,11-14,15-19,20-24>Not Looking For Home Runs
Or This One Trade
And We Aren't Baiting
All Our Return On
<X-word-ms ms=159,419,240,120,740 index=503 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-15,16-20,21-26>Just Finding The Next Decay
Between You
Know Within $10,000
Stock In A Cycle
To Really Make
300% Per Year
<X-word-ms ms=220,99,200,179,400 index=509 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-10,11-13,14-18>When I Look At That
We Can Average
Over 100 Per Year
You Know Just
Compound Hundreds Of
Trades During The Year
<X-word-ms ms=220,340,159,259,240 index=515 character_ranges=0-1,2-9,10-12,13-16,17-21>On Average We Put Like
I Believe It's 250
To 140 Trades
Per Year So If
You Run The Numbers
<X-word-ms ms=200,120,199,180,120,379 index=520 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-15,16-20,21-24>Is Just Like You Know You
<X-word-ms ms=80,120,119,380,519 index=521 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-17,18-21>Have To Go Through The
<X-word-ms ms=199,220,279,160,179 index=522 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-15,16-19,20-25>Number Of Traits The Large
Sample Size Goes Throughout
The Year And
Once Compound Them Aggressively
<X-word-ms ms=339,200,220,179,120 index=526 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-15,16-18,19-21>During The Month As We
<X-word-ms ms=179,250,160,299,419 index=527 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-15,16-18>Do In The Server At
<X-word-ms ms=500,220,120,120,279 index=528 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-13,14-18>The End Of The Year
If You Continue
To Compound The
<X-word-ms ms=80,279,159,399,220 index=531 character_ranges=0-4,5-6,7-11,12-17,18-20>Month A True Power Of
<X-word-ms ms=200,219,240,259,600 index=532 character_ranges=0-4,5-12,13-20,21-26,27-28>Swing Trading Because Again I
Get This Question All
Time Hey Your Risking
<X-word-ms ms=139,260,219,360,600 index=535 character_ranges=0-0,1-1,2-5,6-11,12-16>1% Per Trade Yeah
Sure How Can Make
100 Per Year
Well It's
<X-word-ms ms=80,159,360,220,220 index=539 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-17,18-20,21-24>Not That Difficult If You
Stick To It We
Have Low Drawdown And
When Really
Big Months
Are Kicking In Because
<X-word-ms ms=120,220,299,240,179 index=545 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-14,15-22,23-25>Of Market Phase Already In
<X-word-ms ms=140,299,200,59,159,259 index=546 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-12,13-15,16-20,21-26>Our Favor And We Have These
5 10 15
Even 20
If You Have A
Second Semester
You Have 10%
Month Is Going If
<X-word-ms ms=159,139,360,299,180 index=553 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-14,15-20,21-24>You Have Profit Since The
<X-word-ms ms=159,100,139,100,199,500 index=554 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-15,16-21,22-30>Start Of Year In First Semester
<X-word-ms ms=580,120,120,100,379 index=555 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-16,17-20>You Know He Could Run
<X-word-ms ms=219,280,219,100,360 index=556 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-17,18-21,22-30>Around The Numbers And Compound
<X-word-ms ms=139,120,120,200,159,259,139 index=557 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-10,11-13,14-16,17-21,22-25>It Is Going To Do Over All
Return The
Overall Number
Counting From Seems This
<X-word-ms ms=179,139,80,259,120,179,379 index=561 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-11,12-14,15-20,21-25,26-32>Out Of There Is Going Much Higher
<X-word-ms ms=220,399,139,240,180 index=562 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-16,17-19>That Ten Per Cent In
The Second Semester Compounding
Makes A Lot Difference
From The Capital
You Started In January
<X-word-ms ms=300,240,120,79,100,100,240 index=567 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-12,13-16,17-19,20-25>So There Is A Lot Of Power
Compounding Monthly
And Especially With
<X-word-ms ms=120,320,240,240,160 index=570 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-14,15-17,18-19>Our System That Is A
Core Thing About Swing
<X-word-ms ms=259,180,120,219,240 index=572 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-14,15-18,19-21>Trading That Is Why We
<X-word-ms ms=360,220,120,159,379 index=573 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-15,16-18,19-27>Swings Tray Want To Compound
Hundreds Of Trails
<X-word-ms ms=179,240,220,339,240 index=575 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-19,20-22>Will Look For Volume Of
Trade Not Just
<X-word-ms ms=279,179,120,80,139,220 index=577 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-15,16-21,22-26>One Tree That Is Going Make
Us Rich Or Whatever
<X-word-ms ms=199,40,120,299,120,279 index=579 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-16,17-19,20-26>It Is The Mindset Of People
<X-word-ms ms=180,99,240,200,480 index=580 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-18,19-21>That They Just Find No
Single Tread Better
Risk Adjusted Returns
<X-word-ms ms=230,159,100,220,320 index=583 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-13,14-18,19-22>Versus Buy And Hold Now
Just For The
<X-word-ms ms=139,139,140,219,139,160,219 index=585 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-14,15-16,17-22,23-25>Sake Of This By A Whole Is
Not Bad I'm
<X-word-ms ms=159,300,179,139,120,259 index=587 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-14,15-17,18-20,21-27>Not Saying That It Is Better
<X-word-ms ms=180,120,240,419,460 index=588 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-14,15-20,21-23>Than My Holding Fight If
You Know Most People
<X-word-ms ms=179,240,139,300,219 index=590 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-10,11-17,18-20>Have Lot Of People In
<X-word-ms ms=120,240,300,279,220 index=591 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-17,18-23,24-28>The Server Running These Same
Thing When
<X-word-ms ms=180,259,220,259,230 index=593 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-17,18-25,26-30>Your Capital Start Growing Alot
<X-word-ms ms=160,99,120,160,199,459 index=594 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-14,15-17,18-23>What Do Want To Do Sorry
For This What We
<X-word-ms ms=100,179,160,360,459 index=596 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-12,13-19>Want To Do Is Really
Allocate A Percentage
Of Your Portfolio To
Some Type Longer
<X-word-ms ms=220,360,200,99,200 index=600 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-15,16-19,20-26>Term Holding I'm Not Saying
<X-word-ms ms=139,100,220,199,639 index=601 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-15,16-18>Buy And Hold But As
System That Really Gets
<X-word-ms ms=159,80,99,360,280,159 index=603 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-16,17-21,22-24>You In The Longer Term So
<X-word-ms ms=100,99,180,179,180,259,159 index=604 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-15,16-23,24-29,30-33>We Can Write The Overall Trend Off
<X-word-ms ms=100,320,199,180,199,560 index=605 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-13,14-18,19-26,27-37>The Market And Have Another percentage
Of The Portfolios
<X-word-ms ms=200,259,220,100,119,260 index=607 character_ranges=0-4,5-12,13-15,16-18,19-22,23-29>Swing Trading So It Can Really
Manages The Drawdowns
Even Better Although
Obviously The
Total Return
<X-word-ms ms=320,139,139,139,159,180 index=612 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-16,17-19,20-22>Per Year Is Going To Go
Lower But Again If
<X-word-ms ms=179,20,179,139,259,180,319 index=614 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-14,15-16,17-23,24-28,29-36>You Are Running A Decent Size Account
Getting 40
50 Per Cent 60
<X-word-ms ms=159,180,139,60,259,579 index=617 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-19,20-24>Per Cent In The Year It's
<X-word-ms ms=100,159,100,300,179,100,100 index=618 character_ranges=0-0,1-4,5-7,8-13,14-17,18-20,21-24>A Lot Of Money And If You
Can Compound It
Which Is Swing Trading
With A Portfolio
Construction Of Long
Term Following System
For Exam Pl Momentum
Gives You Its
Very Powerful
<X-word-ms ms=139,100,120,179,259,159,220 index=627 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-8,9-11,12-18,19-23,24-28>So I Want To Discus That Next
Session But
<X-word-ms ms=300,19,319,120,379 index=629 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-14,15-17,18-22>We Are Focusing On Swng
<X-word-ms ms=140,120,279,319,139,100 index=630 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-15,16-18,19-22>Tr Ting First So We Can
Get One Thing Going
On First Right
Then Add Other
Stuff Maybe This Is
The Whole Point Of
<X-word-ms ms=259,240,139,220,420 index=636 character_ranges=0-4,5-12,13-16,17-20,21-24>Swing Trading And How You
Really Roll It To
Begin With You
<X-word-ms ms=139,120,299,440,419 index=639 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-15,16-24,25-35>Have To Question Yourself Everything
<X-word-ms ms=299,120,40,199,240,200 index=640 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-7,8-13,14-18,19-23>Why Am I Doing This Well
At Least
<X-word-ms ms=79,180,240,159,159,1040 index=642 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-15,16-20,21-25>We Start Swng Tr Ting Next
How Do It Differently
<X-word-ms ms=459,299,80,59,379 index=644 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-10,11-14,15-21>There Are A Few Things
<X-word-ms ms=200,399,299,100,620 index=645 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-11,12-15,16-26>That Makes A Lot Difference
In How We Do
Stuff And How
Most People Do Stuff
<X-word-ms ms=219,180,319,240,180 index=649 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-18,19-23>And How Most People Have
Been Doing It For
Decades So I
Use System Trading
As A Foundation
For Swing
Tr Ting Stock This
<X-word-ms ms=360,159,220,179,240 index=656 character_ranges=0-1,2-11,12-16,17-18,19-24>Is Something That I Don't
Really Know Why But
I Don T O Anybody
In The Space Of
Swng Training That Applies
To Sw Ing Thinking
And Strategy To
Sw Ng Trade Everybody
Said Discretionary Tra
<X-word-ms ms=179,120,159,40,399,200 index=665 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-8,9-13,14-17,18-19>Tor I Don Know Why I
Mean There Is
More Systematic
<X-word-ms ms=439,140,199,220,299 index=668 character_ranges=0-6,7-10,11-13,14-17,18-23>Traders Out In The World
Than Discretionary Tra
Tors Right So I
Have This Background That
Run For Many
Years And Manage
Accounts With An Associated
And Was Running Systems
On Futures Again
My Job Was To
Develop Systems
And Build A Portfolio
Of Systems Really Run
These Account Because
<X-word-ms ms=219,80,360,319,379 index=682 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-13,14-20,21-24>It Was Getting Higher You
Need Diversify
In You
Know Building Different
Strategies Are Really Complement
Themselves They Cancel The
Drawdown Of Course
<X-word-ms ms=120,199,260,259,99,360 index=689 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-12,13-16,17-20,21-27>We Pay Always You Are Paying
For Some Return
Getting Hit But
<X-word-ms ms=259,240,220,139,100,279 index=692 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-14,15-17,18-20,21-25>The Whole Point Is To Keep
An Equity Stable Especially
When Once Your Dream
<X-word-ms ms=160,480,139,120,319 index=695 character_ranges=0-2,3-12,13-17,18-22,23-32>For Investors It's Very Important
But Again I
Brought That Thing
<X-word-ms ms=259,200,120,279,539 index=698 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-9,10-13,14-16>And Once I Saw No
Because I Had
Some Trend Models That
Showed When Have A
Strong Non Volatile Trend
<X-word-ms ms=240,359,160,240,279 index=703 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-18>You Make It Has The
Best Risk Adjusted
Returns That Can Possibly
<X-word-ms ms=220,279,339,99,120 index=706 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-13,14-17>Get But If You See
Futures They Don't
Train That Much There
<X-word-ms ms=159,200,319,120,159,100 index=709 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-16,17-22,23-24>Not That Trim Did Their A
<X-word-ms ms=139,60,139,220,440,180 index=710 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-10,11-15,16-25,26-30>Lot Of More Mean Reverting Yeah
<X-word-ms ms=319,240,140,139,140,159 index=711 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-17,18-22,23-25>Sure Right Now You Pull Up
<X-word-ms ms=220,200,259,220,180 index=712 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-14,15-19>An Old Chart At Gold
<X-word-ms ms=299,259,79,300,179 index=713 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-16,17-20>Chart In All Into The
<X-word-ms ms=100,279,240,259,200 index=714 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-12,13-16,17-20>To Define Say Hey Day
<X-word-ms ms=240,199,240,220,239 index=715 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-16,17-23>Tren Yes Sure But That's
Something Common Right So
And Then That's
<X-word-ms ms=100,279,139,100,180,79,220 index=718 character_ranges=0-2,3-12,13-16,17-20,21-24,25-26,27-33>Not Something You Can Get A Volume
<X-word-ms ms=200,339,180,240,139 index=719 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-13,14-17,18-21>Of Trades When You Are
Doing In All Few
Days Window Off
Trading That Is The
Best To Really
Control Equity Because If
<X-word-ms ms=120,79,359,240,240 index=725 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-10,11-15,16-19>We Go Lower Into The
Intraday Stuff It
Gets Harder I Know
Why People Make
<X-word-ms ms=279,279,180,240,220 index=729 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-13,14-17,18-21>Money That Way But Its
Hard There In Many
<X-word-ms ms=180,339,220,159,160 index=731 character_ranges=0-4,5-11,12-17,18-20,21-26>Every Single Sense Of Their
<X-word-ms ms=160,139,100,159,39,460 index=732 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-13,14-16,17-19,20-26>World Is Going To Be Harder
So What He Did
When I Saw Stocks
<X-word-ms ms=80,219,400,279,279 index=735 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-18,19-23>How They Move House Talk
Smooth And Stalk
Whenever You Have
<X-word-ms ms=180,279,279,159,420 index=738 character_ranges=0-0,1-7,8-10,11-15,16-18>A Period An Even In
Chubby Piros To Still
Get Stones That Have
These Linear
Moves With Various You
Know This Momentum
We Volatility Expansion
<X-word-ms ms=140,339,160,319,360 index=745 character_ranges=0-2,3-14,15-18,19-25,26-30>And Contraction And Expand Shun
The Dish Have
<X-word-ms ms=259,140,180,139,180,299 index=747 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-18,19-22,23-29>You Know These Dogs Are Having
This No Non
Bolts Of Linear Trend
Now It's Very Powerful
<X-word-ms ms=220,99,180,119,0,80,339 index=751 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-17,18-22,23-24,25-29>And I've Seen This Once I Went
Into Data And Have
Something To Share
Building It
Now So Just For
<X-word-ms ms=119,200,240,100,439 index=756 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-15,16-19>You Know We Know How
These Really Works
From The
System Training Foundation Point
<X-word-ms ms=119,240,500,140,159 index=760 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-14,15-20>Of View That Am Going
To Be Sharing Hopefully
Soon Gathering
<X-word-ms ms=219,120,139,400,960 index=763 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-17,18-27>All Of The Signals Delivered
Signal Systems Generated As
<X-word-ms ms=160,139,320,259,319 index=765 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-12,13-17,18-23>An Out Sample Data Since
1950 Until the
End Of 2019
Before I Started Training
<X-word-ms ms=140,79,220,160,399,600 index=769 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-19,20-29,30-32>With My Track Record Obviously Is
Big Out Sample
<X-word-ms ms=240,160,199,160,279 index=771 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-14,15-22>Data Of All The Signals
Generated In History So
I Am Again
Working With Nordgate
And Now Using
Some Of Python
And
Just Building An Interactive
Database
Historical Signal
That You Can Scroll
Up Before
Or After Chart It
<X-word-ms ms=200,79,59,100,240,139,340 index=784 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-7,8-10,11-15,16-19,20-27>Is A Lot Of Work But Getting
There To Have Thousands
Of Traits Since 1950
And This Way They
<X-word-ms ms=160,279,320,219,240 index=788 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-15,16-21,22-27>Are Really Built These Stuff
Up How We
<X-word-ms ms=420,179,160,160,99 index=790 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-9,10-14,15-18>Can I Know That You
<X-word-ms ms=79,120,160,279,399 index=791 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-17,18-20>Have An Edge Right It
Has Thousands Of Traits
Since 1950 Now
<X-word-ms ms=400,119,200,139,160 index=794 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-16,17-27>And Going To Show Historical
Things Um
You Have Thousands
Of Trades You
<X-word-ms ms=200,179,160,259,180,240 index=798 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-15,16-19,20-24>Know And You See How They
Perform The Move
Stocks Move Exactly Same
Way Again
<X-word-ms ms=299,180,199,160,240 index=802 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-12,13-18,19-21>And Again And Again Of
<X-word-ms ms=160,219,120,200,220,659 index=803 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-12,13-18,19-24,25-36>Course From A Daily Chart Perspective
He Just Moves
Again He Moved
Exactly This Same Way
<X-word-ms ms=140,119,180,299,580 index=807 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-17,18-20>In Your City Trade If
<X-word-ms ms=99,119,280,79,259,160,99 index=808 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-9,10-11,12-17,18-20,21-24>I Show You A Trade Of The
1970s And I Tried
From Yesterday Right They
Look Exactly Same You
<X-word-ms ms=140,220,119,180,139,140,220 index=812 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-7,8-13,14-18,19-22,23-29>Can If I Don't Take The Ticket
<X-word-ms ms=139,200,220,119,220,360 index=813 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-17,18-22,23-24>On Date You Wouldn Know I
<X-word-ms ms=99,140,119,240,360,299 index=814 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-22,23-28,29-38>Will Show Some Examples Later Obviously
<X-word-ms ms=419,240,100,159,140 index=815 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-17,18-20>But What Am Trying To
<X-word-ms ms=119,100,99,160,240,210,139 index=816 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-10,11-13,14-19,20-24,25-28>Say Is That We Start From The
<X-word-ms ms=220,279,200,200,220 index=817 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-11,12-17,18-22>Point That I Don'T Risk
<X-word-ms ms=199,240,200,160,99,360 index=818 character_ranges=0-0,1-7,8-11,12-14,15-18,19-26>A Single Pen In The Markets
<X-word-ms ms=220,219,280,139,140,259 index=819 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-11,12-15,16-23>If Not If Im Not Trading
Against Data This
<X-word-ms ms=139,180,319,180,559 index=821 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-16,17-19,20-22>Is Very Important It Is
<X-word-ms ms=200,279,220,220,279 index=822 character_ranges=0-0,1-9,10-15,16-21,22-25>A Starting Point Right Its
Fine But
They
Start Trading With Their
Money And Don't
Know Nothing When
The System Really Works
What Is
<X-word-ms ms=240,360,199,140,259 index=830 character_ranges=0-5,6-14,15-19,20-22,23-27>Normal Drawdown What Is Risk
Per Trade That Should
Be Getting To Optimize
<X-word-ms ms=140,119,360,240,359 index=833 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-17,18-20>You Know Draw Down In
Relationship To Good
Years
Or Periods
<X-word-ms ms=99,519,160,220,599 index=837 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-15,16-20,21-25>Right There Have This Risk
Reward Mentality They
Dont Know How Much
<X-word-ms ms=160,99,319,120,99,160,119,180 index=840 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-16,17-21,22-26,27-29,30-35>To Risk They Dont Know When It Works
<X-word-ms ms=180,119,140,420,139,180 index=841 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-14,15-18,19-22,23-29>They Don't Know The Max Number
Of Trades That You
Know That Can
<X-word-ms ms=240,140,319,220,180 index=844 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-7,8-11,12-15>Get In A Row And
<X-word-ms ms=139,340,159,59,240,460 index=845 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-13,14-17,18-21,22-26>Most Losers In Our Row Didn
<X-word-ms ms=120,259,339,160,220 index=846 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-19,20-23>Not Think On Getting Out
5 10 15 Some
Setups Call For
<X-word-ms ms=360,359,200,79,279 index=849 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-11,12-13,14-18>50 Lovers In A Role
As A Default Is
<X-word-ms ms=119,140,179,160,299,319 index=851 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-8,9-12,13-16,17-18>At This I See Its A
Distribution Statistical
Things Not An Opinion
<X-word-ms ms=240,180,440,139,180 index=854 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-13,14-17,18-24>And It Happens And People
Get Like Just
Them Because Of That
<X-word-ms ms=240,180,220,179,220 index=857 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-17,18-23>You Will Have This Stuff
It's A Mathematical Thing
<X-word-ms ms=160,99,99,300,139,240 index=859 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-17,18-20,21-29>Its Not An Opinion So Whatever
Your Trading Intraday Holding
Long-Term But With
Very Tight Entries
<X-word-ms ms=119,200,220,240,539 index=863 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-16,17-20>Are Going To Have Low
Success Rate Or In
<X-word-ms ms=79,200,220,319,279 index=865 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-14,15-20,21-27>The Daily Chart Swing Trader
Futures Stocks
Whatever The Distributions Play
Out The Same My
Point Is People Trade
Without Know Without Treat
<X-word-ms ms=179,460,180,139,160 index=871 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-15,16-20,21-23>Against Data You Need To
Have Data To Support
What You Are Doing
And Have A Pretty
<X-word-ms ms=160,279,299,140,480 index=875 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-16,17-25>Good Idea Of Your Drawdown
Or Best Case Scenario
<X-word-ms ms=240,319,200,200,159 index=877 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-11,12-17,18-20>And It Makes Sense To
Run It Obviously With
<X-word-ms ms=119,160,299,160,99,120,559 index=879 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-16,17-21,22-25,26-38>All This Data You Need The Distribution
Of Equity Curve
So How Much Can
Risk Because Some
Systems Is
Not A Case For
Exam Let's Say That
<X-word-ms ms=420,59,179,160,140,259 index=886 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-13,14-16,17-18,19-19>We Are Running At 1%
Per Trade But There
Might Be System If
<X-word-ms ms=200,119,259,240,480 index=889 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-14,15-23>You Run One Per Decision
<X-word-ms ms=319,299,140,119,140 index=890 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-8,9-14,15-19>Exam Pl I Don't Know
It Could Go Through
A Drawdown
Threshold That Doesn't Make
Sense Anymore With
The Reward You
Have To Really
<X-word-ms ms=220,160,240,119,160,240 index=897 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-14,15-17,18-23,24-28>Run This System So Begin With
<X-word-ms ms=200,200,339,19,140,139 index=898 character_ranges=0-4,5-11,12-15,16-17,18-22,23-28>Right People Don't Know These
Stuff And Again I
Pay My Use
In Systems Developing
To Begin With So
<X-word-ms ms=119,180,240,299,639 index=903 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-10,11-16,17-20>I Know This Stuff And
<X-word-ms ms=560,99,99,220,220 index=904 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-17,18-21>This Is The Reason Why
<X-word-ms ms=180,240,240,220,559 index=905 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-14,15-21,22-27>Most People Can Really Adder
To Trading System They
Don't Have Data To
Support The
<X-word-ms ms=340,139,19,240,140,99,240 index=909 character_ranges=0-8,9-13,14-17,18-23,24-28,29-34,35-40>Decisions That Are Taken With Their Money
So I Know
It Sounds Kind
<X-word-ms ms=99,340,299,259,180 index=912 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-12,13-19,20-24>Of Simple But People Don'
<X-word-ms ms=59,280,159,220,279,400 index=913 character_ranges=0-4,5-12,13-17,18-23,24-26,27-28>Think Through This Stuff So I
<X-word-ms ms=180,99,259,259,200,99 index=914 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-16,17-22,23-25>Don'T Know So The Point Is
<X-word-ms ms=140,319,299,119,460 index=915 character_ranges=0-7,8-9,10-16,17-20,21-30>Whenever A Trader Has Thousands
<X-word-ms ms=160,319,380,79,360 index=916 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-15,16-18,19-29>Of Traits Logged In Historical
<X-word-ms ms=259,259,140,159,600 index=917 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-17,18-28>Data In All Market Conditions
Taking Into Account
Different Markets Faces
<X-word-ms ms=220,100,220,419,279 index=920 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-9,10-20,21-26>And I Know Everything About
<X-word-ms ms=160,319,259,200,240 index=921 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-12,13-19,20-24>My System You Should Know
What Your
Trader Treats Like The
<X-word-ms ms=240,180,119,259,460 index=924 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-16,17-20>Palm Of Your Hand You
<X-word-ms ms=200,259,160,99,299 index=925 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-15,16-18,19-25>Should Know What Is Normal
When Getting
Out Of Parameters
<X-word-ms ms=160,139,340,200,99,160 index=928 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-13,14-17,18-24,25-29>Of Your System You Should Know
Absolutely Everything You
<X-word-ms ms=119,120,99,120,479,160 index=930 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-15,16-20,21-29,30-32>Should Know What Type Drawdown To
Expect For Example
I Know That We
<X-word-ms ms=39,160,199,200,279,220 index=933 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-15,16-20,21-22>Are Not Going To Have A
300%
Year And It
Will Never Happen
But I Know
<X-word-ms ms=319,180,319,100,220 index=938 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-17,18-25>This Right I'm Not Putting
High Expectations On My
System Because I Know
The Limits On Upper
Side And Lower Side
So I Have That
Risk Reward Relationship
As A Portfolio Level
Over Time Or Many
Cycles Having
Control Know
<X-word-ms ms=380,159,100,200,500 index=949 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-16,17-19>How What Is Going To
Do So It's
<X-word-ms ms=79,160,139,160,160,359 index=951 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-19,20-23,24-34>Going To Stay Within The Parameters
Are Want That
Makes Sense Me Right
So That
Thing About You
Should Never Is
<X-word-ms ms=140,319,240,220,119 index=957 character_ranges=0-4,5-14,15-20,21-25,26-28>There Something Could Take Up
From This Video Please
Listen Instead Of Putting
Money To Work In
The Markets On Something
<X-word-ms ms=180,139,120,200,480 index=962 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-18,19-23>That You Don't Have Data
<X-word-ms ms=240,139,100,139,259,140 index=963 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-12,13-15,16-20>To Buck It Up If Your
Putting A Trade
<X-word-ms ms=500,200,119,140,79 index=965 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-15,16-18>Right If I'm Put In
<X-word-ms ms=120,220,139,39,240,519 index=966 character_ranges=0-0,1-7,8-12,13-16,17-24,25-31>A Trader With The Liberty Signal
<X-word-ms ms=220,440,159,120,79 index=967 character_ranges=0-5,6-7,8-12,13-18,19-22>System I Know There Are
Thousands Of Traits
<X-word-ms ms=200,200,279,279,700 index=969 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-14,15-23>So Back Up That Decision
Is Like Keep On
Taking This Decission Off
<X-word-ms ms=159,180,299,300,119 index=972 character_ranges=0-5,6-12,13-19,20-25,26-28>Course Within Respir Tread At
Its No Makes Sense
For Distribution But If
<X-word-ms ms=79,259,200,220,359 index=975 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-8,9-15,16-21>I Keep On Making These
Trade Decision Again
And Again Consistently With
<X-word-ms ms=99,140,319,360,299 index=978 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-19,20-23>The Exact Same Rules And
<X-word-ms ms=180,279,139,360,279 index=979 character_ranges=0-4,5-11,12-16,17-24,25-28>Their Stocks Look Exactly The
Same But I Execute
It Executed Enough
Of Them My
<X-word-ms ms=160,99,140,119,200,140,119,140 index=983 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-15,16-20,21-24,25-27,28-33>Edge Is Going To Play Out In Going
<X-word-ms ms=159,80,299,460,279 index=984 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-16,17-23>To Make Money Off Course
<X-word-ms ms=200,59,180,259,359 index=985 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-9,10-14,15-19>In A Short Term They
Distribution Of That
<X-word-ms ms=140,140,139,100,439,380 index=987 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-13,14-21,22-24>Is Going To Be Decided By
<X-word-ms ms=139,220,220,259,240 index=988 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-15,16-20,21-24>The Market Phase Just The
<X-word-ms ms=160,399,100,39,200,339 index=989 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-12,13-18,19-21>Way This Is A Thing Of
The So Markets Some
Market Behaves All
<X-word-ms ms=160,59,299,39,640 index=992 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-12,13-16,17-23>Of The Stocks Who Behave
On The Type
<X-word-ms ms=159,220,160,139,240,240 index=994 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-16,17-20,21-23>Of Trend That You Get In
This To Market They
<X-word-ms ms=200,519,159,120,160 index=996 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-16,17-20>Have More Or Less The
<X-word-ms ms=179,200,180,99,180,160,199 index=997 character_ranges=0-3,4-13,14-16,17-22,23-27,28-32,33-38>Same Depending On Their Face Over Going
A Bear Market Everything
<X-word-ms ms=220,99,319,220,240 index=999 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-13,14-17,18-22>Is Going Lower And Most
<X-word-ms ms=319,420,79,140,539,539 index=1000 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-11,12-15,16-18,19-21>Dogs I Would Say 95 98
<X-word-ms ms=580,119,79,200,120 index=1001 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-13,14-19,20-25>Percent Of The Stalk Start
In A Downtrend In
<X-word-ms ms=160,200,200,299,579 index=1003 character_ranges=0-4,5-11,12-16,17-23,24-28>Every Strong Bull Market Ever
<X-word-ms ms=200,160,239,400,220 index=1004 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-18,19-22>Thing Goes Up Right And
You See It's Wrong
<X-word-ms ms=200,140,39,559,59,299 index=1006 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-17,18-21,22-26>One But All Trends The Ones
<X-word-ms ms=100,139,140,220,619 index=1007 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-15,16-26>We Want To Trade Everywhere
So You Know It's
<X-word-ms ms=159,120,180,139,180,160,500 index=1009 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-18,19-21,22-26,27-36>Kind Of And Because In That Reflected
<X-word-ms ms=119,220,339,200,220 index=1010 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-15,16-21,22-26>Any Track Record Right Here
<X-word-ms ms=160,99,359,220,200 index=1011 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-17,18-20>If You Study Month By
Month And You
<X-word-ms ms=200,460,119,140,259 index=1013 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-15,16-22>See What Type Of Market
<X-word-ms ms=200,179,80,200,500 index=1014 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-15,16-20>With That Are Or When
<X-word-ms ms=400,119,80,99,340 index=1015 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-22>You Look At The Signals
<X-word-ms ms=139,79,140,200,200,180,319 index=1016 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-17,18-22,23-27,28-31>You Will See After Once With One
<X-word-ms ms=359,80,199,180,259 index=1017 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-16,17-23>When He Take This Signal
<X-word-ms ms=200,199,100,319,279 index=1018 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-14,15-22,23-27>They Don't Look Exactly Same
They Look Exactly Not
<X-word-ms ms=279,300,139,220,140 index=1020 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-17,18-21>Only The Rules Are The
Same Obviously But They
Charge You Know Visually
They Look Exactly The
Same There Is A
So The Result
<X-word-ms ms=139,180,180,99,480 index=1026 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-15,16-28>Of That It's The Distribution
<X-word-ms ms=220,240,200,119,160,139 index=1027 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-16,17-23,24-26>Based On What The Market Is
Really Doing Right So
<X-word-ms ms=219,220,200,259,460 index=1029 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-8,9-13,14-16>By I Know That By
<X-word-ms ms=339,200,259,120,119 index=1030 character_ranges=0-8,9-11,12-18,19-22,23-25>Thousands Of Trades And If
I Keep Executing
<X-word-ms ms=199,340,220,220,179 index=1032 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-13,14-19,20-22>These Rules Am Going To
<X-word-ms ms=280,259,219,220,160 index=1033 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-12,13-17,18-23>See My Equity Corp Shoot
<X-word-ms ms=180,119,120,199,560 index=1034 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-12,13-19>Up In One Sea Profit
So That'S The Premise
<X-word-ms ms=259,380,79,180,259 index=1036 character_ranges=0-4,5-11,12-15,16-20,21-30>Write That'S The Most Important
Thing You Should Be
You Know
<X-word-ms ms=339,280,79,39,140,359 index=1039 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-15,16-20,21-29>Again If You Can Take Anything
<X-word-ms ms=339,160,220,119,160,160 index=1040 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-17,18-20,21-24>From Me This Would Be One
<X-word-ms ms=319,220,119,340,279 index=1041 character_ranges=0-4,5-6,7-12,13-16,17-24>Thing I Would Say Because
These Right Here
To Understand It And
<X-word-ms ms=140,359,200,160,579 index=1044 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-12,13-17,18-22>Apply Did You Know Your
Own Mean You
<X-word-ms ms=120,219,280,279,339 index=1046 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-21,22-25>Will Never See Trading The
<X-word-ms ms=360,279,140,139,160 index=1047 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-16,17-19>Same For The Rest Of
Life We Cannot Unsee
This Stuff Write Once
You Understand Is You
<X-word-ms ms=220,140,339,299,220 index=1051 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-13,14-19,20-22>Cannot Un Seen Right So
<X-word-ms ms=180,180,199,120,299,100 index=1052 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-19,20-23,24-27>This Going To Change The Way
You Behave So Most
<X-word-ms ms=200,240,180,299,240 index=1054 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-12,13-20,21-24>People Are In Trading Art
<X-word-ms ms=139,220,240,380,500 index=1055 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-17,18-21>In This Path Right And
<X-word-ms ms=240,119,380,159,220 index=1056 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-13,14-24>If You Want To Understand
<X-word-ms ms=319,160,140,119,140,199 index=1057 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-13,14-16,17-20,21-25>These Or Going To See This
<X-word-ms ms=300,319,140,159,240 index=1058 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-17,18-25>Path And This Path Doesn't
Make Sense So Uh
<X-word-ms ms=339,279,140,59,319 index=1060 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-13,14-19>An You Know It Leads
Too Frustration Probably
Losing Money And
<X-word-ms ms=100,59,180,200,139,120,240 index=1063 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-16,17-19,20-22,23-27>If You Make Money Is By Luck
How Many Traders Are
Discretionary Have
<X-word-ms ms=179,160,240,140,339 index=1066 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-9,10-12,13-18>Made A Lot Of Money
In Many Years Then
<X-word-ms ms=79,339,180,120,119,240 index=1068 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-14,15-18,19-23>They Blow Up In One Year
<X-word-ms ms=220,160,139,120,159,200,160 index=1069 character_ranges=0-0,1-4,5-9,10-12,13-19,20-25,26-29>I See This On Social Media All
<X-word-ms ms=59,220,279,400,160 index=1070 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-15,16-22>The Time So It's Better
To Know A Distribution
<X-word-ms ms=200,99,140,259,200,399 index=1072 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-13,14-19,20-23,24-29>Of What You're Doing And Trade
Based On That Principles
<X-word-ms ms=160,99,100,219,280,200 index=1074 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-7,8-13,14-16,17-21>But Is A Basic So What
<X-word-ms ms=79,440,200,220,279 index=1075 character_ranges=0-1,2-11,12-14,15-21,22-25>Is Advantage Of Course You
<X-word-ms ms=180,139,120,179,400 index=1076 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-18,19-21>Know What To Expect So
<X-word-ms ms=200,79,160,259,240,339 index=1077 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-16,17-19,20-24>You Have To Guess If What
<X-word-ms ms=200,319,180,139,180 index=1078 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-11,12-16,17-19>He Would You Have Is
<X-word-ms ms=220,220,220,240,179 index=1079 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-12,13-16,17-21>Normal Or Not You Know
<X-word-ms ms=120,399,180,100,139,140 index=1080 character_ranges=0-2,3-15,16-20,21-24,25-29,30-32>The Distribution Like The Palm Of
Your Hand So If
<X-word-ms ms=240,39,139,100,259,579 index=1082 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-15,16-22,23-28>You Know What To Expect Right
You Know For
Example The Average
Profit Per Trade When
<X-word-ms ms=120,139,360,379,279 index=1086 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-21,22-30>We Have Lower Approach Probably
<X-word-ms ms=440,140,119,200,480 index=1087 character_ranges=0-8,9-12,13-17,18-22,23-29>Portrayed You Know That Sooner
<X-word-ms ms=180,119,200,220,119,160,299 index=1088 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-14,15-17,18-23,24-26,27-33>Later In Market Is Going To Change
<X-word-ms ms=299,180,140,119,180,159 index=1089 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-18,19-21,22-26>And Then It's Going To Mean
River Because This
Been Reversion Thing Happens
In All Matters Of
Numbers Everywhere
So Once The Arrange
Perfect Retreat Slowers
<X-word-ms ms=79,279,200,299,420 index=1096 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-15,16-22>With Me Never Go Higher
So You
<X-word-ms ms=319,140,140,199,560 index=1098 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-14,15-20>Know We Can Get Ahold
<X-word-ms ms=159,220,240,360,279 index=1099 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-18,19-22>Of This Stuff Right And
<X-word-ms ms=399,100,99,79,200,220 index=1100 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-15,16-22,23-25>You Know What To Expect Do
<X-word-ms ms=279,460,79,160,220 index=1101 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-10,11-14,15-19>Know Once I Get Into
<X-word-ms ms=379,120,180,259,199 index=1102 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-14,15-18>In Our New Bull Leg
<X-word-ms ms=140,339,200,259,160 index=1103 character_ranges=0-1,2-11,12-14,15-21,22-25>Or Something It Starts You
Start Seeing Stops As
<X-word-ms ms=200,319,160,259,299 index=1105 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-14,15-18,19-27>Well Seen Right Now Breaking
<X-word-ms ms=220,160,200,199,539 index=1106 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-17,18-23>Up From Multi Week Basis
Is It Looks
Like Money Its Betting
On Your First
<X-word-ms ms=159,279,160,160,179,600 index=1110 character_ranges=0-4,5-11,12-14,15-20,21-27,28-42>Light Higher At First Valley Considerations
<X-word-ms ms=159,120,159,160,120,119,120,399 index=1111 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-16,17-18,19-22,23-25,26-33>Are Going To Have A Lot Of Signals
<X-word-ms ms=180,220,139,220,59,160,180 index=1112 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-13,14-17,18-22,23-29>So We Will See How This Really
Develops Obviously But
<X-word-ms ms=519,220,139,80,220 index=1114 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-10,11-13,14-20>I Know What To Expect
I Know Exactly House
<X-word-ms ms=220,59,180,200,220,139 index=1116 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-13,14-18,19-22,23-25>Talk Is Really More And Oh
<X-word-ms ms=140,119,220,480,220 index=1117 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-12,13-24,25-26>Home A System Performance I
Know When My Seas
Are Really Triggering So
<X-word-ms ms=220,140,139,140,200,99,180 index=1120 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-13,14-18,19-26,27-29,30-32>That's Why You Know Whether We Do
<X-word-ms ms=159,140,119,400,120,299 index=1121 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-20,21-25,26-30>All Of The Commentary With Here
Every Daily Brief D
Weekly Videos
Watch List High Monitor
Stops Breaking Up From
Basis Because Sorry
That It Really Interacts
<X-word-ms ms=139,120,119,180,319,220 index=1128 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-10,11-16,17-23,24-28>With All Of These Things That
Happen In The
<X-word-ms ms=299,160,140,139,140,119,120 index=1130 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-13,14-17,18-20,21-28,29-30>Market So Once You Go Through A
<X-word-ms ms=99,99,420,240,159 index=1131 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-15,16-19,20-23>Couple Of Cycles And You
<X-word-ms ms=140,180,399,100,299 index=1132 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-9,10-15,16-19>Can Know I Don't See
What The Markets
<X-word-ms ms=99,220,420,199,560 index=1134 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-12,13-17,18-19>Are Doing And Have A
Pretty Good Idea How
<X-word-ms ms=240,200,220,240,180 index=1136 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-16,17-21,22-27>Things Are Moving What Might
Come Later On Your
<X-word-ms ms=279,140,180,319,359 index=1138 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-14,15-17,18-24>System Is Going To Behave
So That's Very
Powerful To Have So
Again We Trade Hard
Rules So 95%
<X-word-ms ms=220,240,140,119,620 index=1143 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-15,16-26>Of The Rules Are Mechanical
I Know A
<X-word-ms ms=259,79,140,240,180,200 index=1145 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-12,13-16,17-21,22-26>Lot Of People Say Well This
<X-word-ms ms=99,180,99,160,399,160 index=1146 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-7,8-12,13-21,22-25>Is Not A True Mechanic Old
System While The
5% Discretionary
Element Of The System
It's Very Minor
Its Mostly Prioritizing
Signals Maybe
Deciding If Our
Stock Is No We
<X-word-ms ms=299,200,99,100,199,259 index=1155 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-13,14-17,18-23>Can Take It Or Not Where
To Draw Probably
A Breakout Candle
<X-word-ms ms=199,200,180,200,200,139 index=1158 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-13,14-20,21-24,25-28>If It'S Strong Enough For Not
If You Know He
<X-word-ms ms=139,140,179,340,500 index=1160 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-16,17-19>Has Too Much Week If
<X-word-ms ms=200,119,339,240,740 index=1161 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-15,16-21>It'S Too Big Its Minor
<X-word-ms ms=360,220,139,440,359 index=1162 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-8,9-10,11-11>Is Like A 1%
<X-word-ms ms=280,259,99,339,240 index=1163 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-13,14-20,21-23>Element Of The System So
I Mean
<X-word-ms ms=299,259,220,139,120 index=1165 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-12,13-15,16-18>As Signal For Us Is
A Signal There Are
<X-word-ms ms=139,340,220,199,120 index=1167 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-13,14-19,20-22>No Grades It's Black Or
<X-word-ms ms=240,500,119,80,279 index=1168 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-14,15-21>White This Is A Signal
Or Not Point Blank
<X-word-ms ms=220,240,259,120,139,120 index=1170 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-12,13-17,18-20>So Then If We Have To
<X-word-ms ms=379,240,100,139,100,200 index=1171 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-12,13-17,18-20,21-25>Enter And You Have To Know
<X-word-ms ms=179,120,79,259,240,259 index=1172 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-17,18-27,28-31>Look At The Spread Sometimes The
<X-word-ms ms=339,140,140,219,240 index=1173 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-13,14-17,18-21>Sprite Is Just Two Big
Compared To Both Up
<X-word-ms ms=100,319,319,160,200 index=1175 character_ranges=0-2,3-10,11-18,19-23,24-29>The Candles Doesn't Make Sense
To Enter Because It
<X-word-ms ms=180,440,39,139,320 index=1177 character_ranges=0-5,6-13,14-17,18-22,23-30>Really Excuses The Risk Rewards
<X-word-ms ms=199,259,180,120,179,440 index=1178 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-12,13-15,16-21>We Pass On It So There
<X-word-ms ms=59,140,79,160,399,320 index=1179 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-17,18-24,25-29>Are Kind Of Little Things That
Are Discretionary But
<X-word-ms ms=230,279,140,299,299 index=1181 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-13,14-18,19-22>This System Is Self The
Rules Be Entry D
X E T B
H Itself It's
<X-word-ms ms=220,419,180,119,80 index=1185 character_ranges=0-2,3-13,14-16,17-19,20-24>Not Discussion Or In That
<X-word-ms ms=179,240,180,279,320 index=1186 character_ranges=0-4,5-14,15-19,20-29,30-32>Sense Something Very Important So
And I Believe That
Demand Will Touch That
We Have On Really
Filtering Or Prioritizing
Signals Really Deciding
<X-word-ms ms=220,279,220,100,179,240 index=1192 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-14,15-17,18-21,22-26>All This Signal Is Not Good
Enough I Believe That
Really Give Us You
Know An Edge On
The Plus Of
Success Rate Probably And
Better Expectancy So
I Believe There's No
<X-word-ms ms=240,180,240,319,240 index=1200 character_ranges=0-7,8-11,12-17,18-22,23-27>Training How Rules It'S Much
<X-word-ms ms=480,119,120,200,579 index=1201 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-13,14-19,20-33>Easier In Just Going Discretionary
That'S The Point So
Less Advantage I
<X-word-ms ms=99,259,240,279,240 index=1204 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-21,22-25>Would Say They Started You
Show Up If There'
<X-word-ms ms=39,80,220,179,200,259,160 index=1206 character_ranges=0-0,1-2,3-9,10-12,13-17,18-20,21-24>S A Signal Do Take It You
<X-word-ms ms=279,159,260,139,79,60,119 index=1207 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-16,17-20,21-24,25-28,29-32>Manage Their Risk Can You Let The
Market Do Their Rest
Define Any Distribution
<X-word-ms ms=180,79,240,160,160,239 index=1210 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-11,12-14,15-19,20-22>Is As Simple As That So
Once You Start Trading
With Systems Training
As A Foundation Trailing
Becomes Simple Trading
Becomes Simple Predictable
Boring Profitable Again
They Are The Ingredients
Of Edge Patience
Discipline And
Consistent Execution
But Again Sometimes We
<X-word-ms ms=79,99,120,319,500 index=1222 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-17,18-21>Have To Be Patient And
I Will Were Discussing
<X-word-ms ms=139,259,140,159,340 index=1224 character_ranges=0-6,7-10,11-13,14-17,18-25>Without One Of Our Members
<X-word-ms ms=220,339,180,240,179 index=1225 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-16,17-21,22-27>Believe That Your Here David
Probably I
<X-word-ms ms=240,39,119,140,179,320 index=1227 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-13,14-16,17-23,24-29>Don't Know How To Really Check
<X-word-ms ms=179,200,200,99,220,259 index=1228 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-17,18-21,22-26>This Stuff But You Are Here
In The
<X-word-ms ms=240,279,240,220,519 index=1230 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-13,14-18,19-28>Sense That The Most Difficult
Thing About
Your Trading
Systems Is Not
Developing A System No
Finding An Edge I
<X-word-ms ms=180,119,200,220,379 index=1236 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-16,17-21,22-26>Believe That Some Data Hard
It's Not Hard You
<X-word-ms ms=39,140,159,180,180,139,160,140 index=1238 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-15,16-21,22-24,25-27,28-30>Know Its Just In Front Of Us In
<X-word-ms ms=119,319,340,119,100,179 index=1239 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-13,14-16,17-20,21-24>The Charts And If You Put
Some Work Into Even
One Two
Years Or Four You
<X-word-ms ms=59,119,159,380,59,400 index=1243 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-9,10-13,14-17,18-22>Can Have A Lot But What
<X-word-ms ms=119,19,180,120,139,100,19,139,160,379 index=1244 character_ranges=0-0,1-3,4-10,11-13,14-17,18-20,21-25,26-29,30-34,35-44>I Am Trying To Say Is That The Most Difficult
<X-word-ms ms=180,180,299,220,500 index=1245 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-17,18-20,21-29>Part About Trading Is Sticking
<X-word-ms ms=139,100,180,419,400 index=1246 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-20,21-28>Into It Going Through Moments
<X-word-ms ms=180,159,220,299,259 index=1247 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-14,15-19,20-22>When The Equity Core Is
<X-word-ms ms=399,200,139,140,319 index=1248 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-15,16-21>Not Going In Our Favor
Right We Are
<X-word-ms ms=180,200,119,180,160,579 index=1250 character_ranges=0-4,5-12,13-16,17-23,24-26,27-36>Going Through The Period Of Drawdowns
That's When You
Know Most People They
<X-word-ms ms=400,240,99,100,159,200 index=1253 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-13,14-17,18-24,25-32>Don't Stick To The System Because
Psychologically Need Keep That
Statistical Mindset
<X-word-ms ms=199,99,59,100,299,400 index=1256 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-13,14-22,23-26>And It's Not A Surprise You
<X-word-ms ms=199,360,99,160,119,340 index=1257 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-14,15-20,21-26,27-36>Don't Panic You Don't Start Panicking
About Thinking About All
<X-word-ms ms=240,220,180,160,219 index=1259 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-17,18-24>Is Does The System Really
Works Or None They
<X-word-ms ms=180,160,159,100,220,139,440 index=1261 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-14,15-22,23-27,28-35>Are Going To Go Through That Because
We Have Confidence Of
<X-word-ms ms=200,240,240,180,319 index=1263 character_ranges=0-5,6-13,14-18,19-24,25-27>Really Knowing What Doing As
Most Difficult Thing But
From Practical
<X-word-ms ms=240,139,180,379,220 index=1266 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-18,19-26>Point Of View Again Trading
<X-word-ms ms=299,99,220,99,59,220,259 index=1267 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-16,17-18,19-25,26-34>If Your Trim With A System Training
<X-word-ms ms=220,180,79,299,220,220 index=1268 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-8,9-19,20-24,25-29>Fund As A Foundation Just Show
Up Look For Signal
Manage Risk Take The
Trade And That's
<X-word-ms ms=119,279,120,99,140,159,420 index=1272 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-16,17-19,20-22,23-31>It You Don't Have To Do Anything
Else That Is The
<X-word-ms ms=199,140,140,179,259,259 index=1274 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-18,19-24,25-29>Power Of This Stuff Again Some
People Most Because
We Are Human They
Don'T Like Simple Boring
Effective
<X-word-ms ms=480,240,39,59,180,259 index=1279 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-7,8-12,13-16,17-23>I Don' T Know Why People
Like To Find Their
Way They Think
<X-word-ms ms=119,120,99,140,99,460 index=1282 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-14,15-19,20-27>That He Can Get Into Markets
<X-word-ms ms=99,320,220,279,259 index=1283 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-17,18-25>And Find There Way Through
Scans Through Stocks
Finding Something And They
Feel Going Hunting Or
Something Its Comes You
<X-word-ms ms=140,439,120,159,380 index=1288 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-18,19-22>Know Stops Are Like For
30 Seconds
It Leaves Either Get
<X-word-ms ms=179,360,299,140,199 index=1291 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-14,15-18>In The Train Or Not
<X-word-ms ms=400,140,259,120,139 index=1292 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-16,17-18>And Just Wait For A
Next One That's How
Training Really Works Is
Very Simple Boring
Unprofitable So If
Use Trading System Train
<X-word-ms ms=200,199,259,120,339 index=1298 character_ranges=0-1,2-12,13-16,17-21,22-32>As Foundation You Will Experience
That And Thats Ok
<X-word-ms ms=420,140,219,180,180 index=1300 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-14,15-18,19-21>That'S The Best Way To
<X-word-ms ms=259,240,180,199,100,140 index=1301 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-14,15-20,21-25>Trade If Ask Me That' Most
Sustainable Way
To Trade So Again
<X-word-ms ms=180,220,99,100,299,259 index=1304 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-13,14-15,16-26,27-30>Since Enter As A Foundation Has
<X-word-ms ms=160,179,80,559,639 index=1305 character_ranges=0-0,1-4,5-7,8-16,17-20>A Lot Of Benefits And
<X-word-ms ms=440,200,220,119,220 index=1306 character_ranges=0-0,1-8,9-12,13-17,18-22>I Believe You Know This
Is Something Non Negotiable
Once To See These
Even If You
Have A Portfolio
<X-word-ms ms=79,79,200,240,220,220 index=1311 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-14,15-19,20-24,25-30>In Your Holding Long Term Stuff
You Can Systematize
<X-word-ms ms=439,160,200,139,480 index=1313 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-12,13-15,16-18>Thing And Put It As
A Fundation
As Boundaries
<X-word-ms ms=159,220,160,240,200,99 index=1316 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-13,14-16,17-21>On What You Do On Your
Long-Term Holdings And
<X-word-ms ms=200,119,120,99,300,399 index=1318 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-12,13-19,20-23>Treat It As A System For
Entry Exit
Having A
Point Of Cutting
<X-word-ms ms=160,439,60,159,200 index=1322 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-12,13-18,19-23>The Losses Or Stuff Like
<X-word-ms ms=160,240,440,120,479 index=1323 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-16,17-25>That So It's Very Powerful
So I Mean
<X-word-ms ms=159,180,200,379,140 index=1325 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-22,23-27>We Just Been Discussing This
<X-word-ms ms=180,119,220,240,200,119 index=1326 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-10,11-13,14-17,18-22>For A While So You Know
<X-word-ms ms=160,119,180,200,259,299 index=1327 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-18,19-25,26-33>What If Think About System Trading
<X-word-ms ms=220,200,180,139,140,140 index=1328 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-15,16-19,20-22>This Is The Best Way To
Trade 100% So
<X-word-ms ms=439,220,180,139,500 index=1330 character_ranges=0-6,7-12,13-18,19-21,22-33>Another Thing Would Do Differently
Its End Of
Day Training So If
<X-word-ms ms=120,180,179,220,299,280 index=1333 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-19,20-27,28-33>You Know These Staff Already Being
In Community Off Stream
<X-word-ms ms=359,200,120,220,139 index=1335 character_ranges=0-7,8-11,12-13,14-18,19-23>Trailing For A Wile They
<X-word-ms ms=140,179,219,240,240 index=1336 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-13,14-19,20-21>Don't That And After A
Long Can Hold Overnight
If You
Don't Have Caution During
<X-word-ms ms=160,159,160,200,160,159,100 index=1340 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-17,18-19,20-24,25-27>The Day This Stuff I Hear It
Every Single Day And
Believe Or
Not Getting Into
There Is
<X-word-ms ms=120,299,200,119,140,299 index=1345 character_ranges=0-0,1-7,8-10,11-12,13-17,18-24>A System By A Very Famous
<X-word-ms ms=319,200,279,200,220 index=1346 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-14,15-25,26-31>Trader That Its Everything About
Buying At End Of
The Day Selling
In Open Because If
<X-word-ms ms=279,59,140,259,519 index=1350 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-9,10-15,16-25>There Is A Study Somewhere
Over 50%
Of The Overall Profits
Of SPY Right
More Than
<X-word-ms ms=180,319,140,119,400 index=1355 character_ranges=0-1,2-2,3-5,6-9,10-15>50% Of The Gains
Were Done In Overnight
Moves So Actually
Entering End Of Day
When You Have Confirmation
Of Breakout Has A
Lot Benefits Right And
<X-word-ms ms=180,179,80,359,200,99 index=1362 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-8,9-21,22-24,25-28>You Get A Conformation Of The
<X-word-ms ms=240,280,179,120,299 index=1363 character_ranges=0-6,7-13,14-18,19-22,23-28>Breakup Itself Your Not Guess
Or Trading Account
That Is Formed During
<X-word-ms ms=279,220,200,200,259 index=1366 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-17,18-20>The Day Don't Look At
Intermediate Charts You Don'T
<X-word-ms ms=40,199,140,200,419,240 index=1368 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-16,17-27,28-32>Have To Mess With Everything They
<X-word-ms ms=220,160,160,179,360 index=1369 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-12,13-18,19-23>Break Out Its There It's
<X-word-ms ms=259,279,99,320,119 index=1370 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-18,19-22>Close You Just Take The
Trade And In
Good Market Conditions
<X-word-ms ms=480,100,159,100,279 index=1373 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-16,17-21>You Will See That Best
Trades They Gap
Up Next Morning And
<X-word-ms ms=160,399,200,200,179 index=1376 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-16,17-19>Go Thats Just How It
Is So There
<X-word-ms ms=99,160,480,139,140 index=1378 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-16,17-19,20-24>Are Many Benefits To This
Stuff So First
<X-word-ms ms=120,159,300,359,119 index=1380 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-16,17-18>Of All 30 Minutes A
Day Required The
Whole Process Is Done
<X-word-ms ms=160,199,380,199,120 index=1383 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-12,13-15,16-19>In 30 Minutes At the
<X-word-ms ms=119,99,99,240,179,159,180 index=1384 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-13,14-16,17-20,21-25>End Of The Day So Its Very
Easy And Something That
<X-word-ms ms=199,100,239,400,400 index=1386 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-16,17-30>You Will See That Discretionary
Traders In Good You
Know In Good Years
They Can Make A
Lot Of Percentage They
Can Make 300
400 500 There
<X-word-ms ms=119,180,219,199,200,279 index=1393 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-13,14-16,17-21>Is No This Guy In 2025
He Did 900%
Returns Right During
Discretionary And
<X-word-ms ms=219,260,139,219,480 index=1397 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-10,11-14,15-18>Going For A Low Win
Rate Stuff I Know
And That's Great Thats
Awesome But
If You Look Into
It The Drawdown
<X-word-ms ms=200,179,139,280,279 index=1403 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-16,17-20>Seems To Be Quite Big
<X-word-ms ms=200,79,79,39,140,179,159,139 index=1404 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-10,11-14,15-17,18-25,26-30,31-35>There Are A Lot Of Problem With That
<X-word-ms ms=140,139,240,299,159,340 index=1405 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-16,17-20,21-23,24-29>And Not Everybody Can Be There
All
Day At Your
Computer You Know The
Market Is Open In
<X-word-ms ms=119,119,159,380,280 index=1410 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-19,20-27>Front Of Your Charts Running
Watch List Before The
<X-word-ms ms=200,279,159,300,519 index=1412 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-15,16-22,23-30>Market After The Market Working
<X-word-ms ms=400,219,140,159,159 index=1413 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-11,12-15,16-18>10 Hours Per Day On
This Stuff Again If
<X-word-ms ms=160,119,119,179,360,280,299 index=1415 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-13,14-18,19-22,23-23>You Want To Do Over 300%
Returns I
Would Say Yes Try
To Acquire That Skill
<X-word-ms ms=259,79,79,160,239,320 index=1419 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-9,10-13,14-18,19-26>Which Is A Big Gift Because
Most People
Discretionary Trading At
<X-word-ms ms=140,299,240,259,99 index=1422 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-19,20-23>That Level Now There Are
<X-word-ms ms=60,159,440,339,260 index=1423 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-13,14-18,19-24>So Many People That Spend
Years Trying To Perfect
Discretionary Trade And They
<X-word-ms ms=140,179,159,160,299,300 index=1426 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-18,19-24,25-30>Just Keep On Losing Money Right
What I Suggest Is
Instead Of Going
For 500%
Returns Go Lower
<X-word-ms ms=440,199,140,99,299 index=1431 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-13,14-18,19-20>Because If You Have A
Decent Size Account
<X-word-ms ms=299,139,160,259,420 index=1433 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-17,18-26>You Don't Need 500 Percents
<X-word-ms ms=200,159,199,220,239 index=1434 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-19,20-23>To Grow Your Account But
<X-word-ms ms=139,100,99,619,220 index=1435 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-13,14-16>If You Can Get An
<X-word-ms ms=299,260,179,199,140 index=1436 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-15,16-19,20-24>Average Over 100 Per Cent
Return With
30 Minutes Per
Day And You Don't
Stress About Anything You
Have To Look
<X-word-ms ms=159,59,220,259,320 index=1442 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-13,14-21,22-24>At The Markets Urinary If
<X-word-ms ms=99,179,140,239,599 index=1443 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-16,17-19>You Don´t Want To Do
Run Watchlist And
Manually Select
What You Think Is
<X-word-ms ms=199,180,199,179,260 index=1447 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-13,14-17>Going To Go Or Not
Whatever 30 Minutes
<X-word-ms ms=119,220,319,320,480 index=1449 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-19,20-26>Per Day It Something Doable
Efficient That
<X-word-ms ms=119,99,140,99,219,280,119 index=1451 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-13,14-18,19-20,21-25>You Can Have A Life I Mean
Job Business And
Other Businesses
Still Trade And
<X-word-ms ms=199,280,199,159,340 index=1455 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-14,15-17,18-25>Still Have Time To Deliver
<X-word-ms ms=119,180,319,280,139 index=1456 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-15,16-18>The Scene On Top Of
Everything So This End
<X-word-ms ms=159,140,339,320,500 index=1458 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-13,14-19,20-25>Of Day Trading Thing Again
<X-word-ms ms=260,119,159,280,539 index=1459 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-18,19-23>And The Other Thing That
A Keyword Here Is
Repeatable So
<X-word-ms ms=259,99,220,259,119,320 index=1462 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-16,17-19,20-23,24-28>This Is Something If You Have
<X-word-ms ms=99,240,239,340,159 index=1463 character_ranges=0-0,1-7,8-12,13-17,18-20>A System That Buys An
<X-word-ms ms=220,239,220,199,340 index=1464 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-12,13-15,16-18>Enough Day Or No Go
<X-word-ms ms=379,160,119,199,259 index=1465 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-14,15-19>Short In Up Day It´s
Something Others Can Do
Right This Is A
<X-word-ms ms=280,139,260,319,160 index=1468 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-17,18-22,23-26>You Know Assistant That Its
Transfer About Other People
<X-word-ms ms=220,199,320,239,259 index=1470 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-16,17-21,22-25>Can Really Follow With And
It's Not That You
<X-word-ms ms=100,179,79,480,340 index=1472 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-10,11-24,25-31>Know I'm At Discussionary Trader
<X-word-ms ms=259,0,280,460,119 index=1473 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-9,10-13,14-18>And I Just You Know
<X-word-ms ms=159,200,279,300,259 index=1474 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-10,11-14,15-18>Put A Trade And Say
<X-word-ms ms=160,239,160,59,259,160 index=1475 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-11,12-14,15-20,21-23>I Think This Is Going To
Go And It Just
<X-word-ms ms=159,180,179,259,220,500 index=1477 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-11,12-15,16-18,19-25>Put In There And No People
Try To Follow
Or Whatever I'm Showing
<X-word-ms ms=279,119,120,339,260 index=1480 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-18,19-25>You Know The Server Before
Actually Pulled That They
<X-word-ms ms=340,179,79,300,199 index=1482 character_ranges=0-4,5-6,7-9,10-18,19-23>Tried I Am Shooting With
Everybody So I
<X-word-ms ms=180,159,219,200,159,240 index=1484 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-18,19-21,22-27,28-32>Don't Think Anybody Is Doing This
And The
Way The Reason
Do It Because The
System Is Repeatable
Its Something That Is
<X-word-ms ms=160,319,240,99,219 index=1490 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-14,15-19,20-23>Like Buying You Know Put
<X-word-ms ms=180,380,99,59,179,120 index=1491 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-14,15-18,19-23,24-28>This Example At The Time It's
Like Buying A McDonalds
Franchise To
<X-word-ms ms=219,180,399,100,419 index=1494 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-15,16-24>Buy They Give Me Minimals
Do You Know Everything
You Have To Do
<X-word-ms ms=519,139,119,120,99,139 index=1497 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-15,16-18,19-22>You Put In There We Put
<X-word-ms ms=219,240,239,240,219 index=1498 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-19,20-22,23-27>Money But Everything To Work
<X-word-ms ms=160,119,139,99,220,440 index=1499 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-16,17-21,22-26>And Then You Will Have Copy
Of Coping Paste Mcdonald
With Your Power I'm
<X-word-ms ms=59,200,319,220,279 index=1502 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-15,16-21,22-24>Going Make Money Right So
<X-word-ms ms=219,60,219,119,140,159,99 index=1503 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-14,15-17,18-22,23-27>You Are Kind Of By It'S Like
Buying A Turnkey Franchise
<X-word-ms ms=260,219,159,280,139 index=1505 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-14,15-21,22-25>It'S Same Thing That's The
<X-word-ms ms=179,380,99,240,259 index=1506 character_ranges=0-2,3-11,12-18,19-25,26-30>Way Trainers Should Really Work
<X-word-ms ms=120,119,219,420,160 index=1507 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-13,14-20>By The Way You Should
<X-word-ms ms=119,159,199,240,460 index=1508 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-19,20-22>Be Dead Away Because If
<X-word-ms ms=119,119,240,440,220 index=1509 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-18,19-21>He Did Read Depends On
Discretionary Elements
The Mode
<X-word-ms ms=299,220,259,180,159 index=1512 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-14,15-17>Of How You Wake Up
<X-word-ms ms=139,200,159,240,220,139 index=1513 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-17,18-22,23-24>One Day Can Really Make A
Difference Or What Stalks
<X-word-ms ms=99,100,199,480,219 index=1515 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-19,20-23>To Do How Aggressive You
Go Is Very Dangerous
<X-word-ms ms=79,99,199,340,260,319 index=1517 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-12,13-18,19-21,22-25>And It Really Opens Up For
<X-word-ms ms=139,140,79,259,280,259 index=1518 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-8,9-13,14-19,20-23>A Kind Of Warm Study Its
Super Dangerous To Trade
<X-word-ms ms=259,320,139,119,140,230 index=1520 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-13,14-17,18-22,23-27>And That's Why You Know Very
<X-word-ms ms=220,340,139,119,79,139 index=1521 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-16,17-21,22-24,25-29>Good Traders They Tend To Blow
Up With Discretionary Way
After Making A
<X-word-ms ms=99,80,159,519,300 index=1524 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-11,12-16,17-22>Lot Of Money Many Years
So I Mean
<X-word-ms ms=239,99,120,99,159,199,220 index=1526 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-13,14-18,19-24,25-30>If You Look At This Stuff Right
Here On This Breakout
<X-word-ms ms=139,340,159,120,259 index=1528 character_ranges=0-2,3-10,11-15,16-18,19-23>For Example That We Took
In DC
From 2020 Fastly
So You
Wait Before The Close
So Right Here Waiting
<X-word-ms ms=380,99,120,39,219,300 index=1534 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-10,11-13,14-18,19-23>For It Kind Of Show Like
This You Enter At
<X-word-ms ms=139,159,200,259,240,159 index=1536 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-20,21-24,25-32>The Close Just Before Two Minutes
<X-word-ms ms=199,99,320,159,160,79 index=1537 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-14,15-19,20-24,25-27>Before To Close This Kind Of
Disclosing These
Took Again On Daily
Candles You Got
<X-word-ms ms=219,240,239,159,500 index=1541 character_ranges=0-9,10-13,14-20,21-23,24-29>Understand The Amount Of Money
And Order Flow
That Really Goes Into
A Single Daily Candle
No There's
<X-word-ms ms=119,260,179,139,340 index=1546 character_ranges=0-0,1-4,5-9,10-14,15-17>A Lot That Went In
To Discretion To Really
<X-word-ms ms=260,219,180,159,300 index=1548 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-16,17-21>Form Look Up Like This
<X-word-ms ms=99,119,139,340,99,119,120 index=1549 character_ranges=0-0,1-4,5-10,11-16,17-19,20-21,22-25>I Did Today There Is A Lot
<X-word-ms ms=99,420,199,260,239 index=1550 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-20,21-24>Of Money That Flowing Too
Add That Eventually
For That Day It
Opened Lower Test
<X-word-ms ms=200,179,200,379,160 index=1554 character_ranges=0-0,1-7,8-11,12-21,22-24>A Little Bit Overshoot On
The Lows And Close
With This Big Game
<X-word-ms ms=340,119,79,120,199,340 index=1557 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-9,10-12,13-19,20-26>With A Lot Of Volume Behind
It Money Flow No
Closing About The Resistant
Line So Taking
<X-word-ms ms=220,99,99,99,140,480 index=1561 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-14,15-20,21-26>These At End Up Today Gives
<X-word-ms ms=199,460,159,59,180 index=1562 character_ranges=0-2,3-15,16-18,19-22,23-28>You Confirmation In The Sense
<X-word-ms ms=239,139,160,239,139,120 index=1563 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-16,17-22,23-25,26-27>That What They're Doing Is A
Lot More Higher Probability
Than Trying To
Guess While This
Kind Of Forming If
<X-word-ms ms=79,230,99,120,159,139,179 index=1568 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-10,11-16,17-19,20-23,24-31>We'Re Going Enter Or Not Because
<X-word-ms ms=240,199,140,279,99,200 index=1569 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-20,21-23,24-29>This Could Be Closing Up There
I Could Buy
<X-word-ms ms=279,300,119,160,239 index=1571 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-9,10-14,15-20>Here Put A Stop There
And Then This Thing
<X-word-ms ms=200,119,220,159,79,59,320 index=1573 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-16,17-20,21-24,25-30>You Know Went All The Way Lower
<X-word-ms ms=199,180,279,340,519 index=1574 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-13,14-17>And Went Up On You
<X-word-ms ms=259,320,179,180,239 index=1575 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-15,16-21>See Kind Of Like These
<X-word-ms ms=200,159,99,159,240,539 index=1576 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-14,15-18,19-26>At End Of Today For Example
But This Probably
One Not
<X-word-ms ms=199,139,140,159,139,119,300 index=1579 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-16,17-20,21-24,25-32>This One But This One For Example
<X-word-ms ms=179,200,79,260,179,500 index=1580 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-14,15-18,19-23,24-26>Right They Just Say That Is
<X-word-ms ms=179,320,179,160,379 index=1581 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-13,14-17,18-24>During The Day Was Higher
It Was Strong Weighty
Behind It Than Just
<X-word-ms ms=239,200,159,179,160,199 index=1584 character_ranges=0-6,7-10,11-13,14-19,20-25,26-31>Looking For An Intra Rated Thing
So Imagine Instead Of
You Know This Candle
You Know A Five
<X-word-ms ms=199,280,199,139,180,279 index=1588 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-17,18-22,23-27,28-32>Minute Chart Might Look Like This
Right We Have And
Open Went Lower
In All Chop Free
<X-word-ms ms=139,200,199,179,140,139,79 index=1592 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-10,11-14,15-17,18-20,21-22>There For A Lot Of In A
Couple Of Hours Over
Shooting The Lows Then
<X-word-ms ms=320,139,219,300,720 index=1595 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-15,16-22,23-32>Decided To Train Higher Overshoot
<X-word-ms ms=139,159,220,219,260,99 index=1596 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-14,15-19,20-23>It No When Back They Are
Excited Too Move
<X-word-ms ms=159,180,139,280,219,220 index=1598 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-7,8-13,14-18,19-26>As I Was Right Here Imagine
Being During
<X-word-ms ms=219,240,300,159,139 index=1600 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-15,16-17,18-22>The Day Watching A Five
<X-word-ms ms=220,259,340,179,240 index=1601 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-18,19-21,22-25>Minute Chart Trying To Get
<X-word-ms ms=159,360,179,179,280 index=1602 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-14,15-20>An Entry On The Chart
You Know The Abs
<X-word-ms ms=180,319,59,160,239,760 index=1604 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-18,19-21,22-29>And Downs That Will Be Feeling
<X-word-ms ms=360,219,179,200,139 index=1605 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-15,16-20>Train To Say Hey This
<X-word-ms ms=99,119,220,239,280,219 index=1606 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-14,15-18,19-21>Is Good Time To Buy Or
Whatever If Just
<X-word-ms ms=239,100,79,139,79,119,240,480 index=1608 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-14,15-17,18-21,22-25,26-29>Look At The End Of The Day Not
Only The Breakout Confirmed
In Market Closing
But Again Probably No
Very Good
Entry Gives You An
<X-word-ms ms=259,120,99,119,99,220,440 index=1614 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-15,16-17,18-23,24-27>Edge And That Is A Point Yes
<X-word-ms ms=319,220,119,159,220 index=1615 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-16,17-23>Sure If You Enter During
<X-word-ms ms=179,179,180,239,340 index=1616 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-8,9-13,14-19>The Day I Knew Enter
For Example Here Any
<X-word-ms ms=199,239,120,159,79,280 index=1618 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-13,14-16,17-21,22-29>Close They Are In Your Writing
<X-word-ms ms=179,240,219,259,260 index=1619 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-18,19-25>This Move Your Risk Reward
<X-word-ms ms=119,99,100,119,139,99,160,159,119 index=1620 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-13,14-17,18-21,22-25,26-27,28-29>Is Going To Be One Two Ten 1 2
20 Right It Sure
But Know The Advantage
<X-word-ms ms=179,220,299,220,99 index=1623 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-16,17-20,21-22>Of Really Looking For A
Cool Scandal Gives
<X-word-ms ms=100,139,299,220,480 index=1625 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-14,15-22,23-27>You Much Higher Success Rate
Better Control Over
<X-word-ms ms=139,220,259,120,99,179 index=1627 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-15,16-18,19-25,26-31>Your Equity Corp We Aren't Going
<X-word-ms ms=200,59,259,340,420 index=1628 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-12,13-17,18-21>To Be Trading Less And
<X-word-ms ms=159,220,119,159,380 index=1629 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-16,17-20>The Point Is That The
Edge Still If
<X-word-ms ms=139,180,179,59,240,559 index=1631 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-13,14-15,16-21,22-24>There Isn't An H Their As
<X-word-ms ms=99,119,59,120,59,179,240,139 index=1632 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-15,16-17,18-21,22-24,25-26>Long As You Have A Net On A
Strong One It's
<X-word-ms ms=200,239,99,119,180,199 index=1634 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-16,17-19,20-22>Fine You Know How To Go
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,239,220,179 index=1635 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-12,13-17,18-21>Out Shoot For Them All
<X-word-ms ms=180,179,119,59,160,99,179,260 index=1636 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-9,10-13,14-18,19-21,22-26,27-34>Again If I Had This In Size Account
<X-word-ms ms=199,240,219,300,400 index=1637 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-17,18-18>You Don'T Need 400%
Returns Really Grow Your
Account I Mean Um
Define That Those
Ritual By
Default Will Bring
You To A
Much Sturdy System
And Robust System
That Might Give You
Lower Than 500%
Returns Obviously But
Lower Drawdown Something
<X-word-ms ms=279,120,199,300,199 index=1650 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-12,13-17,18-22>We Can Really Live With
An Execution Be Consistent
<X-word-ms ms=240,179,200,299,220 index=1652 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-18,19-21>On This Whole Point So
I Think
<X-word-ms ms=199,200,239,220,419 index=1654 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-17,18-21,22-29>Thing About Enough Day Trading
<X-word-ms ms=400,140,159,299,200 index=1655 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-16,17-20>Is That It Brings The
Success Rate Percentage
Of The System In
The Medium Bucket At
65 Percent Accessory
<X-word-ms ms=119,139,80,179,340,279 index=1660 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-18,19-25,26-31>Then There Are Many Things About
<X-word-ms ms=480,220,139,160,799 index=1661 character_ranges=0-11,12-18,19-22,23-30,31-34>Distribution People For Trading You
Know Why We
<X-word-ms ms=139,140,419,180,79,239 index=1663 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-18,19-21,22-25,26-31>Do This Differently If You Trade
It The Breakouts
In The Morning With
<X-word-ms ms=99,80,159,299,240,119,119 index=1666 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-11,12-16,17-21,22-27,28-30>A Very Tight Stop Your Going To
Have 30 35%
Success Rate You
<X-word-ms ms=160,179,360,159,119,140 index=1669 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-12,13-16,17-20,21-25>Would Say Yes You Can Make
Money Not Saying Wrong
Or Whatever If
<X-word-ms ms=139,179,240,179,300 index=1672 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-13,14-22>As An Edge Has Positive
Expectancy You
<X-word-ms ms=159,200,299,280,460 index=1674 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-17,18-23>Can Make Money But There
<X-word-ms ms=39,159,119,600,79,259 index=1675 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-18,19-23,24-29>Are Lot Of Problems That Comes
With These Just Makes
It Very Difficult
And Cannot Sustain A
System Like This With
<X-word-ms ms=200,219,260,319,260 index=1680 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-18,19-23,24-26>These Above Success Rate Is
It Profitable Yeah Did
Christian Kulamagi Need
200 Million
Doing This Yes Sure
But Its Most People
<X-word-ms ms=199,240,99,159,139,160,139 index=1686 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-10,11-15,16-18,19-21,22-24>Will Not Be Able To Do It
<X-word-ms ms=440,119,160,259,500 index=1687 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-12,13-14>If You Ask Me I
Would Prefer This Approach
<X-word-ms ms=159,179,120,379,200 index=1689 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-13,14-22,23-27>Without Of The Benefits That
Dan Brings And
<X-word-ms ms=159,180,199,300,739 index=1691 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-19,20-28>Just Grow My Account Modestly
Modestly Comparing 2
500% Returns
Obviously Because We All
Know Because This
Success Rate Percentage
<X-word-ms ms=59,99,400,240,219 index=1697 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-10,11-19,20-24>Of A System Although Many
People These Know
Discredit This Defines
Your Whole Distribution Again
<X-word-ms ms=139,140,199,220,239,239 index=1701 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-11,12-14,15-18,19-22>I Talk About Is All The
Time So At 30
<X-word-ms ms=139,239,320,280,339 index=1703 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-5,6-12,13-17>To 35% Access Rate
System They Could
<X-word-ms ms=219,199,180,219,260 index=1705 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-13,14-23,24-28>Record My Look Something Like
<X-word-ms ms=199,159,160,159,139,160,460 index=1706 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-15,16-19,20-23,24-31>This Have All Of His Big Winners
<X-word-ms ms=460,139,159,240,419 index=1707 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-15,16-22>And Then Up Huge String
Off Losers Maybe Another
<X-word-ms ms=319,140,339,200,219 index=1709 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-15,16-20,21-24>Stream Of Winner That Are
<X-word-ms ms=240,279,240,179,420 index=1710 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-10,11-15,16-18>Out Of Loos Come In
I Mean This
<X-word-ms ms=219,80,299,220,239 index=1712 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-16,17-21>Is The Point That This
<X-word-ms ms=79,400,159,220,199 index=1713 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-15,16-21>Is How It Really Looks
<X-word-ms ms=119,180,179,99,100,119,219 index=1714 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-11,12-15,16-21,22-24,25-29>Of Course If You Start To Grow
<X-word-ms ms=440,119,160,199,260 index=1715 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-17,18-21>He's Going To Grow And
<X-word-ms ms=119,139,180,159,119,199,500 index=1716 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-16,17-19,20-29,30-34>Then Its Going To Go Something Like
These But Most
Of Time In The
<X-word-ms ms=260,279,300,139,420 index=1719 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-15,16-19,20-22>Equity Curve Was All No
Systems Like This Most
<X-word-ms ms=159,99,240,199,180,139 index=1721 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-14,15-18,19-21>Of The Time You Are In
A Drawdown And This
<X-word-ms ms=99,100,199,440,239 index=1723 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-20,21-26>Is The Most Difficult Thing
For People To Digest
<X-word-ms ms=199,220,59,139,79,200,99,300 index=1725 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-12,13-14,15-20,21-25,26-29>If You Are In A Drown Down All
The Time Right
<X-word-ms ms=319,200,139,139,19,140,159 index=1727 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-15,16-19,20-21,22-26>All The Time You Are I Mean
In And You
<X-word-ms ms=219,140,379,220,320 index=1729 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-15,16-21,22-24>Make For Example There If
You May I Don't
<X-word-ms ms=119,219,340,139,79,260 index=1731 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-8,9-11,12-13,14-18>Know 300% In A Year
<X-word-ms ms=480,139,119,120,440 index=1732 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-13,14-21>But All Of The Profits
Came In November December
<X-word-ms ms=460,160,119,139,440 index=1734 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-14,15-18>Or Then Up Here Are
Going To Stand Since
January Until
October In A Drawdown
Waiting For Those Big
Hits Because Your Shooting
For Immune Every Time
<X-word-ms ms=250,199,119,79,100,419 index=1741 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-12,13-16,17-19,20-28>This Brings A Lot Of Problems
Massive And This You
Know Brings A Stuff
<X-word-ms ms=320,179,140,119,99,79,140 index=1744 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-13,14-16,17-22,23-25>About Is Que I Am Going To
Discus In The
Next Session But
<X-word-ms ms=200,359,140,179,400 index=1747 character_ranges=0-0,1-8,9-11,12-14,15-26>I Discuss It In Intelligent
<X-word-ms ms=299,240,179,240,219 index=1748 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-14,15-21,22-24>Trader Boot Cam Videos As
Well Is That Bigger
Standard Deviation Of The
Result Of The Traits
Against Immune Is
<X-word-ms ms=120,139,480,79,300 index=1753 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-15,16-18,19-24>Going Be Hardest To Trade
<X-word-ms ms=219,260,179,79,99,440,860 index=1754 character_ranges=0-6,7-12,13-15,16-19,20-25,26-28,29-29>Because Again We Are Going 10%
To 15% Losers
<X-word-ms ms=180,39,199,200,79,219,300 index=1756 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-7,8-12,13-14,15-21,22-27>In A Row It's A Common Thing
<X-word-ms ms=279,79,140,59,360,380,219 index=1757 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-24,25-26,27-29>And This Is Not Something I Am
Seeing As An Opinion
<X-word-ms ms=159,100,379,340,159 index=1759 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-17,18-23,24-27>It's A Statistical Thing And
Mathematical Thing On
<X-word-ms ms=159,179,60,239,639 index=1761 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-15,16-22,23-35>People That Have Traded Successfully
Say They Have
Regularly 15 Losers
<X-word-ms ms=139,59,140,199,240,39,159,119 index=1764 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-7,8-10,11-12,13-15,16-19,20-23>In A Row So I Am Not You
Know Throwing Out Numbers
<X-word-ms ms=179,440,119,120,179 index=1766 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-17,18-21>Just Right Off The Bat
<X-word-ms ms=300,139,179,220,299 index=1767 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-12,13-20>Yeah Me Now I Started
<X-word-ms ms=240,239,340,179,160 index=1768 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-14,15-17,18-23>These In Detail My Whole
<X-word-ms ms=259,159,120,159,179,200 index=1769 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-8,9-13,14-18,19-24>Life So I Know This Stuff
<X-word-ms ms=380,190,79,200,99,159 index=1770 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-7,8-10,11-15,16-18>So 10 To Do This In
<X-word-ms ms=100,179,119,440,360 index=1771 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-14,15-21,22-25>Our Always Very Common You
Know Being Months
And Month Most Of
<X-word-ms ms=160,279,239,220,419 index=1774 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-12,13-21>The Year In A Drawdown
It's Very Common So
<X-word-ms ms=239,180,199,320,139 index=1776 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-15,16-23,24-27>That'S Why These Traders Say
<X-word-ms ms=139,139,120,319,200,259 index=1777 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-21,22-24,25-30>Have To Be Comfortable In Drums
Yeah Sure But For
Most People Going 10
<X-word-ms ms=220,199,139,180,299 index=1780 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-9,10-15,16-18>Month In A Drawn Is
Not Something Doable I
<X-word-ms ms=139,119,140,179,139,180,199 index=1782 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-18,19-21,22-27,28-30>Mean Your Not Going To Stick To
<X-word-ms ms=119,300,159,180,259 index=1783 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-16,17-20>Eat That Did Just Say
<X-word-ms ms=159,120,139,519,279 index=1784 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-15,16-18>The Way This And If
You Pair With A
Big Percentage 1-20
Although It Sounds Really
Cool It Sounds Nice
In Practicality
<X-word-ms ms=220,19,239,180,99,420 index=1790 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-14,15-18,19-20,21-33>You Are Calling For A Distribution
That Is Very Hard
To Trade Psychologically So
<X-word-ms ms=289,260,239,159,340 index=1793 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-22>The Fact We Are Trading
End Of Day This
Just Simple Twist Brings
A Huge Puts
No Training Breakouts
In Stock Market
Into Another Bucket
<X-word-ms ms=319,200,39,289,580 index=1800 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-18,19-28>Into An Other Thing Different
And Then Releases
Easier To Execute
So They Could Go
On These Stuff Will
Resemble More
Of An Equity Curve
<X-word-ms ms=160,539,139,300,279 index=1807 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-13,14-16,17-17>That Follows A 30%
Degree Angle
So And If
<X-word-ms ms=119,139,100,119,279,280 index=1810 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-19,20-22>You Look At The Mean If
<X-word-ms ms=99,199,160,219,260,219 index=1811 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-15,16-20,21-29>You Draw Them In This Standard
Deviation So They
<X-word-ms ms=380,280,179,59,219 index=1813 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-13,14-17,18-24>Deviate On Off The Result
Of Each Individual Trade
Winner Loser From
The Mean It's Going
<X-word-ms ms=139,79,180,279,340 index=1817 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-13,14-16>To Be Very Low So
<X-word-ms ms=320,299,119,100,159,440 index=1818 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-13,14-19,20-28>We Have All Of These Benefits
As For Example We
Have Eight Having 80
Two Nine Losers
In A Row The
Probability Of This Happening
It's Zero Point
Twenty One Percent
At Per Quarter
So There Is
Just And Yes I
<X-word-ms ms=300,179,259,140,79,139 index=1829 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-14,15-17,18-22,23-26>Said This Right To Have You
Know These Huge Silent
<X-word-ms ms=280,179,139,220,99,159 index=1831 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-14,15-19,20-22,23-26>Table To Really Show It But
<X-word-ms ms=400,360,119,139,660,360 index=1832 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-12,13-15,16-16>If There Is 0.21%
<X-word-ms ms=379,180,79,159,539 index=1833 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-13,14-18,19-24>Chance That We Have Eight
<X-word-ms ms=139,180,380,199,99,180 index=1834 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-13,14-16,17-18,19-22>Or Nine Losers In A Row
Per Quater
So They Provide
<X-word-ms ms=120,339,260,199,260 index=1837 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-10,11-14,15-18>Us Having A Big You
Know At Least
<X-word-ms ms=220,279,240,39,320 index=1839 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-17,18-24>Not Draw Them That Signal
Is Going To Be
<X-word-ms ms=199,160,219,280,659 index=1841 character_ranges=0-0,1-4,5-8,9-15,16-25>A One Two Twenty Reservoir
Trader Right But
You Don't Know Before
And Obviously Are
<X-word-ms ms=99,159,220,359,240 index=1845 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-17,18-23>We Going Take This Trade
For The Sixteenth
Time If You Skipped
<X-word-ms ms=140,219,300,99,279 index=1848 character_ranges=0-1,2-9,10-13,14-17,18-20>It Because You Are In
Pain Whatever I
Do Skip These On
Your Just Blow
<X-word-ms ms=239,139,120,279,240 index=1852 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-22,23-25>Up The Whole Experience Of
<X-word-ms ms=79,359,200,279,120 index=1853 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-12,13-19,20-23>The System So That's Why
This Systems They
Are Not Done Durable
For Normal Human Being
<X-word-ms ms=360,220,199,179,160 index=1857 character_ranges=0-1,2-9,10-14,15-19,20-21>If Running This With A
System That Is Purely
You Know Mechanical It's
<X-word-ms ms=179,400,240,119,99 index=1860 character_ranges=0-6,7-12,13-16,17-20,21-25>Another Thing But You Will
See See Uh
<X-word-ms ms=320,139,219,200,159 index=1862 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-15,16-21>In Our Call Your Going
To Get The Heat
As Manager Of
The System Off
The Drawdowns The Peter
<X-word-ms ms=159,99,200,219,300,219 index=1867 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-15,16-18,19-25>Of The Drown And Of Course
<X-word-ms ms=159,420,139,180,139 index=1868 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-11,12-16,17-20>Be Losers In Arow Its
<X-word-ms ms=139,140,99,219,360,220 index=1869 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-16,17-24,25-30>Going To Be There Anyways About
The Durability Of These
<X-word-ms ms=240,259,219,160,159 index=1871 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-15,16-23,24-26>Systems Very Low Because If
<X-word-ms ms=79,120,339,139,80,419 index=1872 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-13,14-16,17-19,20-24>You Get Scared On It Only
16th Trade And
Skip This One You
<X-word-ms ms=159,240,99,119,99,360 index=1875 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-15,16-21,22-32>Just Blew Up The Whole Expectance
<X-word-ms ms=119,220,380,179,360 index=1876 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-12,13-21,22-26>Of System And Probably Have
<X-word-ms ms=159,340,139,79,99,220 index=1877 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-9,10-15,16-20,21-26>To Spend I Don't Know Three
<X-word-ms ms=219,300,39,79,300,99 index=1878 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-13,14-15,16-24,25-27>More Months In A Drawdown Or
Something So These
<X-word-ms ms=180,419,300,99,220 index=1880 character_ranges=0-2,3-10,11-15,16-20,21-28>Not Durable I've Been Through
<X-word-ms ms=179,340,119,279,220 index=1881 character_ranges=0-4,5-6,7-10,11-17,18-22>Stuff I Can Assure Your
Own Futures
<X-word-ms ms=240,259,219,280,79 index=1883 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-15,16-22,23-27>That Systems Are Worked Like
<X-word-ms ms=260,239,99,200,259 index=1884 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-17,18-22>This They Are Very Hard
<X-word-ms ms=200,239,199,100,199,159 index=1885 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-11,12-15,16-20,21-22>To Trade And You Miss 1
Trader Book
For Whatever Reason
Any Cons Cue
This Bucket Ratio Because
<X-word-ms ms=220,79,299,320,159 index=1890 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-13,14-17,18-20>We Are Entered End Of
<X-word-ms ms=320,289,259,119,100 index=1891 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-14,15-16,17-20>Day These Gives A Lot
<X-word-ms ms=99,239,160,179,179,460 index=1892 character_ranges=0-1,2-10,11-15,16-19,20-24,25-31>Of Benefits Will Get This Stable
Equity Corp The Success
Rate Is Much Higher
So On Average
<X-word-ms ms=280,199,280,179,199 index=1896 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-13,14-18,19-23>We Don't Spend That Much
Time In Drawdowns Yes
Right Now Since October
2025 As We
Got Into This Massive
Sideways Action That We
Haven Seen Since 2015
Really In The Markets
And Since
January 2020 Know All
Of The Pullback Phases
And Sideways Movements
In Markets Never
<X-word-ms ms=360,79,119,159,400 index=1909 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-15,16-17,18-24>Lasted More Than 2 Months
<X-word-ms ms=179,100,139,300,259,99 index=1910 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-17,18-22,23-25>That Is Why Equity Corp Is
So Stable Since January
<X-word-ms ms=340,240,219,179,120 index=1912 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-17,18-21>2020 But Right Now You
<X-word-ms ms=59,139,240,399,280 index=1913 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-15,16-18,19-23>Can See Although We Took
A Curve Heist
Mid February Not
<X-word-ms ms=139,240,259,159,280 index=1916 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-13,14-16,17-24>Going To Count It Because
We Briefly
<X-word-ms ms=159,179,180,219,180,399 index=1918 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-17,18-21,22-29>Made New High Seam Mid Febuary
<X-word-ms ms=400,59,79,160,119,219 index=1919 character_ranges=0-0,1-3,4-7,8-13,14-16,17-21>I Am Not Going To Call
That Not Starting Since
Mid February Obviously
<X-word-ms ms=300,200,339,100,559 index=1922 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-15,16-24>Not Going To Get Momentum
Out Of The
Drawdown But Just Showing
<X-word-ms ms=79,180,279,360,259 index=1925 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-18,19-22>You This Stuff They Are
Part Of Distribution
And Process You
<X-word-ms ms=300,239,180,219,360 index=1928 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-19,20-24,25-30>Cannot Trade Without Draw Downs
It Doesn't Exist
Because By Mathematical
Definition Unless 100%
Success Rate So If
<X-word-ms ms=480,59,99,180,339 index=1933 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-9,10-17,18-22>You Have A Crystal Ball
Or Insider
Trading Right You
<X-word-ms ms=119,240,219,180,159,260 index=1936 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-18,19-21,22-25>Will Have Draw Down So Use
Them To
Your Advantage Control Over
Equity Curve
<X-word-ms ms=279,60,119,159,200,299 index=1940 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-16,17-26,27-32>Which is the most important thing
<X-word-ms ms=0,79,259,140,159,460 index=1941 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-13,14-16,17-23,24-31>Is That Having An Update Trading
Brings The Success
Rate Of Swing Trades
To This Level And
<X-word-ms ms=340,79,320,119,159 index=1945 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-14,15-19>You Are Most Of Time
Very Close To Equity
Curve Highs Your
Very Very Close I
<X-word-ms ms=240,179,180,179,119,99,100 index=1949 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-16,17-19,20-23,24-28>Would Tend To Hit It You Know
During A Normal Year
We Aren't Hitting Equity
<X-word-ms ms=239,280,240,199,300 index=1952 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-18,19-24,25-30>Curved Heist Almost Every Month
So That's
Something Very Useful
And Easy To Stick
As Human Beings
<X-word-ms ms=159,179,19,340,539 index=1957 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-13,14-20,21-26>Because We Are Humans Again
Most People Cannot
Withstand This
<X-word-ms ms=360,239,219,180,199 index=1960 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-15,16-20,21-27>Stuff Right Here Most People
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,219,119,140,359 index=1961 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-13,14-18,19-24>Can Not But At This Thing
It's Much Easier
<X-word-ms ms=139,200,320,219,99,119 index=1963 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-15,16-19,20-23,24-26>To Really Advert You And Is
Much More Durable So
Then For Those That
Do System Trading Portfolios
Yes We Can Mix
Some Of These Yeah
If You Know
<X-word-ms ms=219,200,279,200,219 index=1970 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-16,17-20,21-23>Get Other Systems Are In
<X-word-ms ms=199,160,139,119,320,79 index=1971 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-21,22-25>The Side Of The Bucket You
<X-word-ms ms=59,200,219,219,220,159 index=1972 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-16,17-20,21-24>Can Even Now Stop And You
Can Work A Middle
Thing There If
<X-word-ms ms=119,179,320,99,219,480 index=1975 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-13,14-17,18-28>You Are In All The Respirator
<X-word-ms ms=419,200,99,199,180 index=1976 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-12,13-17>And It Run So That
Your Looking For
<X-word-ms ms=180,139,420,239,200 index=1978 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-15,16-23>We Can Take Them Because
<X-word-ms ms=159,219,160,99,299,360 index=1979 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-11,12-20,21-26>As More Of A Personal Thing
But Again Another
You Know Very Important
Benefit Offend Up
<X-word-ms ms=159,160,239,179,120,440 index=1983 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-17,18-21,22-25,26-32>They Trend Because You Can Easily
Refer Back On Data
<X-word-ms ms=240,139,340,279,120 index=1985 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-16,17-20,21-23>And Build Systems Out Of
<X-word-ms ms=139,159,300,300,299 index=1986 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-14,15-17,18-27>The Daily Close So Referring
To Daily Closer Has
A Starting Point To
Build Systems Not
Only Breakouts By Mean
<X-word-ms ms=399,59,139,380,99 index=1991 character_ranges=0-8,9-11,12-16,17-23,24-26>Reversion Is Much Easier To
<X-word-ms ms=139,139,220,179,260,539 index=1992 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-18,19-23,24-30>Work With This Than Just Trying
Look At The Intrinsified
<X-word-ms ms=220,199,160,219,240 index=1994 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-18,19-25>Mini Chart Of Every Single
<X-word-ms ms=279,119,100,319,180,239 index=1995 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-18,19-21,22-27>Day That You Trying To Place
<X-word-ms ms=139,320,219,219,120 index=1996 character_ranges=0-0,1-7,8-11,12-15,16-20>A Signal And You Will
<X-word-ms ms=179,159,100,139,179,440 index=1997 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-11,12-16,17-18,19-23>Need I Don't Know A Huge
Computational Power So
It Is Going To
Be Become More Difficult
<X-word-ms ms=220,299,220,119,119,440 index=2001 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-15,16-19,20-25>Yeah Sure If You Are These
Big Hedge Funds
<X-word-ms ms=59,200,480,99,519 index=2003 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-15,16-23>That Have All Of Servers
In Invest 100 Million
In Compositional Power And
Have 100 Traders
And Looking For Algorithms
<X-word-ms ms=200,199,159,80,119,159,179 index=2008 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-16,17-19,20-24,25-28>Yeah Sure You Can Do That But
Again The Value Of
Entry Is Higher
That Since It's Institutional
<X-word-ms ms=320,359,160,139,79 index=2012 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-15,16-19>It Start What We Are
<X-word-ms ms=260,159,119,300,299 index=2013 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-14,15-18>Doing In Us Not The
<X-word-ms ms=360,139,280,79,260 index=2014 character_ranges=0-8,9-15,16-18,19-22,23-29>Objective Before We Are Really
<X-word-ms ms=259,160,99,179,260,119 index=2015 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-11,12-16,17-22,23-25>Trying To Do Here Right Or
Just Try To Grow
Our Money
Compounded Over Time
<X-word-ms ms=230,159,140,159,119,180,159 index=2019 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-8,9-13,14-18,19-24,25-28>I Like To Take Some Money Out
<X-word-ms ms=179,119,120,159,380,440 index=2020 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-10,11-15,16-22,23-32>Put It Into Hard Assets Investing
Businesses And I Like
<X-word-ms ms=79,99,260,239,460 index=2022 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-11,12-15,16-22>To Be Spread Out That's
<X-word-ms ms=139,180,259,79,400 index=2023 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-13,14-15,16-27>The Way That's A Personality
Thing You Know
That'S Based On No
That'S Again
It'S A Personality Thing
Or Personal Decision
<X-word-ms ms=219,259,259,79,140,59 index=2029 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-13,14-16,17-20,21-23>Things So This Is End Of
Day Trading Before
We Get Here Into
Momentum And Volatility Contraction
Expansion There
Are Any Questions They
<X-word-ms ms=139,179,280,99,199,340 index=2035 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-15,16-20,21-26>Want Drop In The Chat Maybe
<X-word-ms ms=360,219,160,239,360 index=2036 character_ranges=0-0,1-8,9-11,12-18,19-24>I Believe Am Pretty Clear
<X-word-ms ms=179,119,80,119,159,280,299 index=2037 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-14,15-20,21-24,25-33>But If You Want Leave Any Question
<X-word-ms ms=280,179,240,219,219 index=2038 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-12,13-15,16-19>Right Now And We Are
<X-word-ms ms=140,99,99,119,340,179,120 index=2039 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-18,19-28,29-31,32-35>Going To Go Through Questions At The
End Anyways But Maybe
Just You Know Kind
Of Put A Cut
<X-word-ms ms=320,259,100,179,239 index=2043 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-15,16-20>Here If You Ever Want
<X-word-ms ms=160,319,140,299,160 index=2044 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-7,8-16,17-19>So Ask A Question Up
Until This Point But
It Not You Know
<X-word-ms ms=260,119,119,300,480 index=2047 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-15,16-17>Is Going Be Fine I
Believe Am Being Pretty
Clear On Everything Saying
And Attempt To Repeat
<X-word-ms ms=280,219,220,199,119 index=2051 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-14,15-17,18-20>All These Stuff In My
<X-word-ms ms=240,400,39,259,320 index=2052 character_ranges=0-4,5-11,12-15,16-26,27-29>Daily Briefs And Everything So
Really Engrain
Most Important Things
As You Know The
<X-word-ms ms=259,99,160,359,260 index=2056 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-19,20-22>Basis Of Our Trading So
Whenever Your Training Something
<X-word-ms ms=200,79,299,200,319 index=2058 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-15,16-18,19-26>And This Applies To Trading
As A Whole So
<X-word-ms ms=260,239,39,260,179,99 index=2060 character_ranges=0-7,8-11,12-15,16-21,22-24,25-29>Whatever You Are Doing In Your
Training The First
<X-word-ms ms=339,220,199,200,319 index=2062 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-14,15-17,18-23>Thing Is Should Be Doing
It's Really Ask Yourself
<X-word-ms ms=280,279,180,79,500 index=2064 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-14,15-21>On What You Are Basing
Or Training Around So
Me Just Hook Up
My Computer Just Incase
Once You Know You
<X-word-ms ms=179,519,140,79,299 index=2069 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-13,14-19>Know What Am I Based
<X-word-ms ms=160,139,179,220,420 index=2070 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-18,19-23>What Is The Overall Idea
<X-word-ms ms=219,159,140,259,160,139 index=2071 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-17,18-20,21-23>Of What I'm Trying To Do
<X-word-ms ms=219,320,259,200,119 index=2072 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-15,16-19>Here Right So If You
Ask That Question And
Your Trading Based
On Something That It's
There Its Real It
<X-word-ms ms=340,79,79,220,159,139 index=2077 character_ranges=0-6,7-10,11-14,15-19,20-22,23-26>Happens All The Time Is The
<X-word-ms ms=260,219,300,199,280 index=2078 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-15,16-22,23-27>Way These Stocks Really Move
<X-word-ms ms=440,160,119,199,760 index=2079 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-14,15-16,17-23>Because We Have A System
That Is Very Specific
On Rules That Mathematical
<X-word-ms ms=179,219,100,99,139,139,180 index=2082 character_ranges=0-2,3-10,11-15,16-19,20-22,23-25,26-30>For Example They Had To Do This
<X-word-ms ms=219,179,220,139,79,220 index=2083 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-16,17-19,20-23>And That And Then He Has
Go Up 4%
<X-word-ms ms=279,220,179,240,480 index=2085 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-17,18-20>And Then You Place At
<X-word-ms ms=100,59,360,199,39,119,79,320 index=2086 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-15,16-19,20-25,26-28,29-31,32-39>This Core Fitted I'm Going To Be Talking
<X-word-ms ms=199,80,99,339,160,139 index=2087 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-21,22-24,25-26>About The Core Feeding In A
Session Obviously But
These Systems Specifically
This Elaborational
System Look Train
Breakout It Works Based
On Momentum And
Volatility Contraction Expansion
<X-word-ms ms=139,179,479,140,199 index=2095 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-14,15-20>Is Just This Is Their
Way Stocks Really Move
<X-word-ms ms=180,179,139,480,519 index=2097 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-14,15-22>So What Is That Moments
<X-word-ms ms=99,240,199,180,199,260 index=2098 character_ranges=0-1,2-11,12-14,15-19,20-23,24-29>Of Essential Is When One Thing
Moves In One Direction
With Weight And
The Premise
<X-word-ms ms=199,139,119,160,59,279,380 index=2102 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-15,16-19,20-24,25-29>Off That Is That The More Time
<X-word-ms ms=259,100,119,380,179 index=2103 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-17,18-20>And The More Force It
Goes Behind That
Momentum This Really Is
<X-word-ms ms=260,299,220,139,579 index=2106 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-15,16-23>To Just You Know Reverse
That So If I
<X-word-ms ms=120,119,279,380,220 index=2108 character_ranges=0-4,5-13,14-17,18-25,26-28>Don't Remember For Moments In
The Daily Chart As
A Big Implication Yes
Markets Are Fractal
Of Course He Happens
<X-word-ms ms=99,279,320,199,480 index=2113 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-18>The Same In The You
<X-word-ms ms=200,280,360,119,199 index=2114 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-13,14-17,18-22>Know It Happen The Same
Intraday But
<X-word-ms ms=120,59,139,39,160,219,340 index=2116 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-13,14-17,18-23,24-29>If You Look At The Daily Chart
<X-word-ms ms=179,99,260,279,300 index=2117 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-20,21-26>You Have Every Strong Multi
Month Trend Is Going
<X-word-ms ms=159,220,219,220,199 index=2119 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-8,9-12,13-15>To Take A Lot Of
Time Or Force
To Really Correct
<X-word-ms ms=260,239,220,199,240 index=2122 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-18,19-25>This Stuff So Again Either
Has To Come A
Lot Of Selling Pressure
Or Top
Information Really Forms That's
<X-word-ms ms=79,160,99,279,420 index=2127 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-10,11-16,17-20>Why We Have Stage One
Stage Two Stage Three
And Stage Four Right
Because Before Something Such
Big Trend You Know
End We Need
See An Digestion Of
<X-word-ms ms=259,220,119,220,419 index=2134 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-14,15-22,23-25>Present In Time Because It
<X-word-ms ms=140,99,179,320,239,140 index=2135 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-9,10-17,18-24,25-29>Like A Big Freight Render Goes
<X-word-ms ms=99,199,460,200,259 index=2136 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-15,16-21,22-24>In One Direction Right So
<X-word-ms ms=500,299,59,119,180 index=2137 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-14,15-18,19-25>What Happens Is The Market
<X-word-ms ms=179,160,250,179,300 index=2138 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-17,18-22>Is That Stops When Once
They Get Into A
Very Strong Trend Defined
By Perfect Action
<X-word-ms ms=260,159,160,239,579 index=2142 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-14,15-25>At This For Our Definition
<X-word-ms ms=140,179,179,200,259,539 index=2143 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-13,14-15,16-18>Is We Have The 8 20
And 50 EMA Stocked
Up An Open Now
With Slow All Of
Them Write I Will
<X-word-ms ms=120,119,99,179,220,239,400 index=2148 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-9,10-11,12-13,14-19,20-25>Have The C M L Turns Green
<X-word-ms ms=139,120,379,250,140 index=2149 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-9,10-13,14-18>At 1 Point And That
Shows A Perfect Comb
Bination Is That
<X-word-ms ms=280,239,119,140,219,340 index=2152 character_ranges=0-7,8-9,10-15,16-18,19-25,26-32>Whenever A Stock Is Moving Higher
<X-word-ms ms=219,220,79,179,119,620 index=2153 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-11,12-16,17-18,19-32>It Starts To Form A Consolidation
And Its Right In
Building Or Everything About
The 20 EMA This
Is A Contraction On
Volatility So What Activity
Has A Cycle Of
Expansion Contraction
An Expansion And
When You Have All
Attitude Con Traction After
Expansions Write
Default Will Be Expanded
Like 10 1 Is
Paired With Momentum
Tends Up Buying
<X-word-ms ms=119,79,159,200,139,139,140,299 index=2169 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-10,11-13,14-19,20-23,24-25,26-36>Or Is Going On There See A Volatility
Contraction Right
It Contracts At This
<X-word-ms ms=219,539,100,119,159 index=2172 character_ranges=0-4,5-12,13-18,19-21,22-28>Point Sellers Might Be Taking
Profits And
<X-word-ms ms=339,200,119,99,119,340 index=2174 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-11,12-18,19-22,23-28>Price Goes A Little Bit Lower
But New Buyers
<X-word-ms ms=219,200,119,179,180,360 index=2176 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-16,17-19,20-24>Came In And Tried To Know
Get M
<X-word-ms ms=239,280,179,280,719 index=2178 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-12,13-19>By All Of The Higher
Loads Their And
<X-word-ms ms=320,79,219,340,340 index=2180 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-19,20-26>Then You See Setters Really
<X-word-ms ms=199,480,240,19,139 index=2181 character_ranges=0-6,7-16,17-21,22-25,26-28>Getting Exhausted They Are No
<X-word-ms ms=199,280,139,340,259 index=2182 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-15,16-20,21-24>More Seller Just Only Buy
<X-word-ms ms=160,179,139,219,720 index=2183 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-11,12-15,16-24>Yours And We See Breakout
And An X Like
Goes Higher So There
<X-word-ms ms=240,99,259,120,219,200 index=2186 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-10,11-14,15-21,22-27>Is A Supply And Demand Thing
Going On You Know
<X-word-ms ms=500,120,99,219,79 index=2188 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-13,14-19,20-22>Looking At The Stock Of
<X-word-ms ms=100,179,199,260,340 index=2189 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-20,21-26>How This Thing Really Works
Right But
<X-word-ms ms=460,239,19,220,319 index=2191 character_ranges=0-10,11-13,14-17,18-24,25-30>Essentially We Are Seeing Again
When I See Momentum
Write Moments In The
<X-word-ms ms=160,199,179,200,400 index=2194 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-16,17-23>Long Term And Can Define
That With Our Indicators
These Way To Do
It You
See No
A Moment Would
Alec Hire For
Activity Contracts An Expansion
Isn't That Momentum
<X-word-ms ms=340,360,99,199,380 index=2203 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-20,21-25>And This Is Something That
<X-word-ms ms=300,159,219,120,239 index=2204 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-16,17-20>Not Only You Will See
<X-word-ms ms=300,99,139,119,540 index=2205 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-12,13-19>If We Look At Stocks
<X-word-ms ms=159,480,159,139,160 index=2206 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-11,12-15,16-18>Right But It Can Be
Added In Of
These Studies Made
By No Scientist
There This White Paper
<X-word-ms ms=400,220,179,99,240 index=2211 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-13,14-17,18-23>Savory What If You Study
Markets A Moment To
<X-word-ms ms=219,240,119,179,539 index=2213 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-17,18-20>Just The Way Works So
An It's
<X-word-ms ms=99,319,200,199,79,240 index=2215 character_ranges=0-0,1-8,9-14,15-17,18-21,22-27>A Logical Thing If You Think
<X-word-ms ms=179,139,200,219,360 index=2216 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-15,16-25>About It From Us Supplying
<X-word-ms ms=139,140,179,119,119,220,199 index=2217 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-16,17-21,22-24,25-29>The Mind Point Of Your As Well
<X-word-ms ms=460,99,59,159,200,119 index=2218 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-15,16-18,19-22>But This Way Can Do The
<X-word-ms ms=199,180,79,159,119,320 index=2219 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-15,16-18,19-22>Same If You Want To Get
Conviction On These Stuff
<X-word-ms ms=179,120,139,219,280,400 index=2221 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-20,21-25,26-29>And When They Discuss That How
<X-word-ms ms=219,500,159,100,579 index=2222 character_ranges=0-5,6-16,17-19,20-22,23-32>People Confidence In An Excession
<X-word-ms ms=79,239,240,440,299 index=2223 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-14,15-19>Of This One But Just
<X-word-ms ms=180,99,440,219,440 index=2224 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-14,15-19,20-25>Give An Example Here Right
<X-word-ms ms=219,180,119,179,300,179 index=2225 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-8,9-14,15-20,21-26>This Is A Short Trade There
<X-word-ms ms=120,159,139,240,420 index=2226 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-15,16-20>We Took In March 2025
Right Here Right And
<X-word-ms ms=400,139,99,140,199,159 index=2228 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-14,15-20,21-25>You See That We Enter This
Day With C
D S New
Volatility Contraction Z
Know Distance
<X-word-ms ms=200,159,440,39,380 index=2233 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-13,14-20>At The Sock Of Strain
<X-word-ms ms=199,260,139,360,139 index=2234 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-12,13-19,20-24>Above All The Emails With
<X-word-ms ms=79,79,100,79,199,159,260,239 index=2235 character_ranges=0-0,1-2,3-4,5-6,7-12,13-16,17-27,28-32>A C M L Green And Everything Then
Crack Over Clock Lower
Below That 20 Didn't
20 Cross Lower I'm
<X-word-ms ms=200,239,460,99,80 index=2239 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-15,16-20,21-23>Sorry Guys We're Kind Of
Sick Today What Are
<X-word-ms ms=79,100,119,159,159,780 index=2241 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-14,15-20,21-23>They To Be Seek Right So
Have The First
Leg Going Lower Right
Here We Ended
<X-word-ms ms=80,379,240,99,780 index=2245 character_ranges=0-2,3-10,11-14,15-16,17-30>The Firstly Had A Consideration
The 1st Value Consideration
<X-word-ms ms=179,220,139,139,280,460 index=2247 character_ranges=0-6,7-10,11-12,13-15,16-20,21-26>Against The 8 In 2020 Amaze
With The Right Number
Of No Candles
Are Really Measure
What Is The Correction
Between Price And Time
<X-word-ms ms=160,119,59,79,79,200,239,260 index=2253 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-15,16-18,19-24,25-28,29-34>And Then We Have To Break Out Write
If You Look
At 4 I Put
<X-word-ms ms=159,340,119,79,180,159 index=2256 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-14,15-18,19-23,24-27>This Example In The Chat Not
Too Long Ago 40
1973 When
<X-word-ms ms=340,139,99,79,240,559 index=2259 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-20,21-23>You Look At The Chart It
<X-word-ms ms=179,220,219,99,519 index=2260 character_ranges=0-4,5-13,14-17,18-21,22-29>Looks Although Its Not Exactly
<X-word-ms ms=260,320,159,139,300 index=2261 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-17,18-25>Same But It's Very Similar
Inform See Know
<X-word-ms ms=160,119,159,139,180,179,340 index=2263 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-15,16-21,22-24,25-31>That His Top Was Going Up Higher
Right There It Cracked
<X-word-ms ms=119,140,219,200,119,159,199 index=2265 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-11,12-15,16-18,19-23,24-26>Below The 20 All Of Them Is
<X-word-ms ms=280,280,179,179,280 index=2266 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-16,17-20,21-26>Turned Lower Have The First
Leg Here We
<X-word-ms ms=100,139,159,140,679 index=2268 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-16,17-30>Have The 1st File Consolidation
<X-word-ms ms=219,79,140,79,259,320 index=2269 character_ranges=0-0,1-4,5-8,9-11,12-18,19-22>I Can See In Twenty May
Layer Measure By
The Distance And Be
Amplitude Off
<X-word-ms ms=99,140,259,139,140,159,280 index=2273 character_ranges=0-2,3-11,12-19,20-24,25-31,32-34,35-39>The Consider Diction That Number Of Bars
Are Really Measure The
<X-word-ms ms=340,199,180,219,500 index=2275 character_ranges=0-9,10-12,13-18,19-23,24-26>Correction Of Price Time To
Get The First One
Conclusion Then Go Lower
<X-word-ms ms=559,219,139,80,559 index=2278 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-14,15-23>And They Have A Breakout
<X-word-ms ms=319,180,179,99,240 index=2279 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-15,16-18>Of What You Have In
Week And
<X-word-ms ms=259,120,319,200,599 index=2281 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-14,15-17,18-22>It Just Changed No Take
Out Data Everything The
1974 Here
<X-word-ms ms=99,180,179,460,759 index=2284 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-9,10-16,17-21>I Just Put Around 2026
He Will Be Same
You Would Know The
Difference Because
Stocks Move Again And
Again And Again This
<X-word-ms ms=220,179,239,320,240 index=2290 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-7,8-13,14-20>Is A Way Stalk Smooth
<X-word-ms ms=379,280,119,199,280 index=2291 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-14,15-27>So What At City Construction
Expansion When Your
Period With Momentum
Is Just Away
Sucks Moved Any Gives
Us The Frame
Works Really Build
That System Upon So
<X-word-ms ms=139,119,220,159,320,599 index=2299 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-16,17-18,19-25,26-28>When You Building A System We
<X-word-ms ms=99,139,140,259,300,480 index=2300 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-14,15-19,20-24>Have To Be Sure That Your
<X-word-ms ms=319,160,159,119,159,480 index=2301 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-16,17-19,20-29>Build In It Based On Something
That Is There That
Works And Its Something
Or How Price
Really Moves Thats Why
<X-word-ms ms=279,180,219,139,160,179 index=2306 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-13,14-17,18-22>If You Look At The Most
Successful Systems You
Only Have Breakouts
Pullbacks Mean Reversion
<X-word-ms ms=280,259,220,199,139 index=2310 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-16,17-19>And Then Could Be Of
<X-word-ms ms=160,199,320,259,420 index=2311 character_ranges=0-5,6-13,14-17,18-25,26-33>Course Getting Two Options Trading
They Will Be
Different Way But
Did Profit From Same
<X-word-ms ms=339,19,280,219,720 index=2315 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-15,16-24>So And You Trade Momentum
On A Trend With
<X-word-ms ms=260,79,440,199,280 index=2317 character_ranges=0-8,9-13,14-23,24-26,27-34>Breakouts From Pullbacks Or Retrain
Mean Reversion Probably No
<X-word-ms ms=199,199,260,99,119,420 index=2319 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-15,16-20,21-30>Own Bull Buses I Mean Reverting
<X-word-ms ms=200,299,180,219,460 index=2320 character_ranges=0-1,2-10,11-14,15-20,21-23>To Continue The Train Or
<X-word-ms ms=139,120,199,320,239 index=2321 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-17,18-20>As At Top Training In
Reversion Know Some
<X-word-ms ms=200,159,139,340,260 index=2323 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-15,16-25,26-31>People Turn This Parabolic Short
Side They Go Very
<X-word-ms ms=359,300,99,160,179 index=2325 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-8,9-15,16-21>High In A Pretty Short
<X-word-ms ms=179,200,179,239,580 index=2326 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-13,14-18,19-23>Period Of Time Then They
Correct Through For
Price Not Time
They Don't Form Considerations
Just Crack Lower And
That's Mean Reversion
So That'S The Only
<X-word-ms ms=200,159,300,99,139,119 index=2333 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-14,15-18,19-22,23-29>You Know Things Are You Should
Be Basing A Successful
<X-word-ms ms=259,220,239,220,219 index=2335 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-18,19-21,22-26>System Some Because If Your
Basing It On Trainer
<X-word-ms ms=280,239,300,119,360 index=2337 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-19,20-24,25-34>Trend With Breakouts From Pullbacks
Or Train Me
<X-word-ms ms=39,360,119,200,219,99 index=2339 character_ranges=0-1,2-9,10-13,14-18,19-21,22-25>In Reverse And Even If You
<X-word-ms ms=59,100,219,400,219,480 index=2340 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-13,14-20,21-26,27-31>Are An Options Trader Right Here
Selling Premium We
Know With Credit
<X-word-ms ms=480,79,240,179,260 index=2343 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-19,20-24,25-29>Spreads Or Something Like That
They're Either No
Profiting From A
<X-word-ms ms=199,160,139,159,180,99,539 index=2346 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-18,19-21,22-26,27-32>Stock That Is Going To Stay Above
This Level Either Trending
Or Moving Sideways So
<X-word-ms ms=159,19,180,79,340,279 index=2349 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-14,15-24,25-29>You Are Kind Of Profiting From
Training Your Bidding
<X-word-ms ms=139,160,219,380,339 index=2351 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-9,10-12,13-20>On A Train Or Outside
<X-word-ms ms=240,259,250,240,119 index=2352 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-14,15-17,18-21>With Move Right At The
<X-word-ms ms=179,280,219,160,299 index=2353 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-16,17-26>Same Time But The Principle
Is The Same Price
Sorry Guys Priced
<X-word-ms ms=100,179,159,260,179,260 index=2356 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-16,17-22,23-29>Can Only Be Doing These Things
<X-word-ms ms=159,139,200,299,420 index=2357 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-18,19-22>Can Only Be Trading And
<X-word-ms ms=79,180,119,299,200,519 index=2358 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-12,13-17,18-25,26-35>You Couldn To Only Between Breakouts
In Pullbacks Or Mean
Reversion So Base
<X-word-ms ms=139,240,259,300,250 index=2361 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-18,19-23,24-27>Your Systems Around That And
That's The Only Way
You Can
<X-word-ms ms=239,400,199,120,379 index=2364 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-14,15-17,18-25>Really Build In My Opinion
A System Has Very
Good Framework
On How Things Move
<X-word-ms ms=259,260,199,199,420 index=2368 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-16,17-20>Right And Then If You
Build Rules Around That
<X-word-ms ms=139,199,300,340,419 index=2370 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-11,12-18,19-22>And Create A System Out
Of That And You
Know Waste Stocks Moved
<X-word-ms ms=260,159,119,140,79,279 index=2373 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-16,17-18,19-26>Are Going To Make A Killing
<X-word-ms ms=220,79,159,240,239,460 index=2374 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-15,16-19,20-22>There Is Just No Way If
<X-word-ms ms=119,120,59,239,760 index=2375 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-8,9-14,15-22>You Do It Right Process
On Doing Building This
System There Is No
<X-word-ms ms=199,120,39,79,320,139,139 index=2378 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-19,20-22,23-27>Way That We Can Lose On This
Stuff So The Thing
Is That We Focus
<X-word-ms ms=239,200,259,180,79,199 index=2381 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-15,16-19,20-23>On These This Is The Way
Stocks Really Move This
Is The Way Momentum
<X-word-ms ms=159,220,219,340,619 index=2384 character_ranges=0-4,5-11,12-16,17-20,21-26>Sucks Really More And Again
<X-word-ms ms=200,219,79,400,280 index=2385 character_ranges=0-0,1-7,8-10,11-18,19-23>I Showed An Example Here
<X-word-ms ms=519,179,199,140,299 index=2386 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-14,15-18,19-21>And Again There Are 52
Years Apart Same Structure
<X-word-ms ms=180,459,140,99,340 index=2388 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-16,17-23>Sim Setup If Just Switch
The Symbol To Date
<X-word-ms ms=239,140,139,300,379 index=2390 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-16,17-18,19-29>You Wouldn Notice A Difference
So The Point
Is That 50 Two
Years Apart This Looks
Look Very Similar
Now I
Haven't Know The Oldest
Signals That Could
Get It's 115
Years Ago On
The Dow Jones
Induced Rate Average Weekly
Index Pretty The
Oldest Other System Signals
150 Years Ago
<X-word-ms ms=199,180,99,99,160,319 index=2405 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-12,13-16,17-21>So If You Can See Here
<X-word-ms ms=539,59,60,279,159 index=2406 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-8,9-15,16-21>This Is A Weakly Chart
<X-word-ms ms=340,280,79,239,579 index=2407 character_ranges=0-8,9-11,12-16,17-20,21-25>Obviously So They See That
Price Was Just In
A Sideways Area
Right Here With
<X-word-ms ms=99,139,160,159,300,219 index=2411 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-8,9-11,12-17,18-22>The 8 And 20 Image Just
<X-word-ms ms=280,239,300,139,260 index=2412 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-17,18-23>Cross All Over The Place
Above 50 Then Had
A Trend Result
Of 15 May At
1st Leg Higher And
First Final Consideration
<X-word-ms ms=420,219,140,119,340 index=2418 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-12,13-16,17-24>The Length Of The Candles
And The Consolidations
Mark The Present
Time Relationship Correction
They Have To Breakout
<X-word-ms ms=99,120,139,139,260,239,400 index=2423 character_ranges=0-0,1-4,5-8,9-13,14-17,18-22,23-28>I Had The Five Day Move Right
This Is January On
1905 Right Then
<X-word-ms ms=179,139,140,199,260,179 index=2426 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-15,16-19,20-25>You Can See Also See These
Stuff Off Stage
One Stage Two
Stage Three Stage
Four Even
Then A Top In
Phase Long Term Then
<X-word-ms ms=219,260,299,100,219 index=2433 character_ranges=0-2,3-14,15-18,19-22,23-28>The Development Now And Trend
<X-word-ms ms=179,79,100,219,440 index=2434 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-17,18-23>This Is The Market Cycle
Itself As Well You
<X-word-ms ms=160,159,119,199,260,159 index=2436 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-17,18-22,23-25>Can See That Right Here If
<X-word-ms ms=100,279,240,299,280 index=2437 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-18,19-22>Look From My System DLS
<X-word-ms ms=320,319,119,140,719 index=2438 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-14,15-19,20-31>System Point Of View Perspective
Because Very Clearly
I Have Here First
Leg Lower 1st
Valley Consideration They
Break Out There And
<X-word-ms ms=119,139,139,240,219,120,119 index=2444 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-19,20-24,25-27,28-31>Then Have The Second Lake On The
<X-word-ms ms=179,300,279,120,179 index=2445 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-17,18-22>Bear Side And Then Just
No Reverse Up Higher
<X-word-ms ms=260,99,230,240,679 index=2447 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-14,15-19>So You Will See That
On The Bear
Side Of The
First Valley Consideration
It You Have
The 1st Lake The
<X-word-ms ms=279,200,119,159,99,200 index=2453 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-13,14-19,20-21,22-28>Second Leg And After A Second
<X-word-ms ms=279,220,79,179,320 index=2454 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-15,16-21>Like You Know We Don't
<X-word-ms ms=199,59,120,99,159,240,219 index=2455 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-13,14-19,20-26,27-31>Tend To Have A Third League Even
<X-word-ms ms=159,240,99,200,239,440 index=2456 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-14,15-17,18-20,21-31>The 3rd Leagues Be At Truncation
Attends To Be Kind
<X-word-ms ms=119,200,219,200,339 index=2458 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-12,13-15,16-25>Of Higher Low Or Something
<X-word-ms ms=460,180,59,159,320 index=2459 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-16,17-23>As I've Been Very Common
Then From After A
2nd Lake Because On
<X-word-ms ms=140,139,239,320,119,640 index=2462 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-23,24-26,27-33>The Bull Site Everything Is Fueled
By Greedy So
<X-word-ms ms=159,220,79,119,220,239 index=2464 character_ranges=0-8,9-14,15-17,18-22,23-28,29-31>Everybody Wants To Make Money So
<X-word-ms ms=440,119,139,140,339 index=2465 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-16,17-23>If The Stock Goes Higher
See Consideration And
<X-word-ms ms=260,319,160,59,179,119 index=2467 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-17,18-21,22-28,29-33>Another Lake There Are People That
<X-word-ms ms=180,139,19,139,140,99,340 index=2468 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-15,16-21,22-24,25-27,28-34>Believe They Are Going To Go Higher
And This Buying Just
Goes On You
Can Have A Second
<X-word-ms ms=300,99,239,100,99,179 index=2472 character_ranges=0-4,5-6,7-10,11-13,14-19,20-24>After A 2nd We Gonna Have
<X-word-ms ms=119,360,139,300,300 index=2473 character_ranges=0-0,1-4,5-9,10-19,20-21>A 3rd Even Sometimes A
<X-word-ms ms=279,220,159,179,579 index=2474 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-16,17-22>4th Leg But Again Their
Much Lower Less
Probability They Work
<X-word-ms ms=199,80,159,420,179 index=2477 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-8,9-17,18-24>In A Very Specific Market
Condition That You
Can Only Know After
<X-word-ms ms=180,279,80,219,199,380 index=2480 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-16,17-24,25-33>The 5th That Does Another Question
<X-word-ms ms=200,119,159,159,200,219 index=2481 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-14,15-19,20-24,25-28>You Don't Maybe Will Have Why
<X-word-ms ms=179,60,199,119,99,160,139,579 index=2482 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-14,15-18,19-24,25-29,30-43>Do You Focus On The First Part Consideration
<X-word-ms ms=159,100,239,200,339 index=2483 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-13,14-18,19-23>And The Second Lake Only
<X-word-ms ms=320,139,159,160,259 index=2484 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-13,14-17,18-25>Because It Has The Highest
Probability Of Working
We Want To
Build An Edge
That Is Durable
As A Very Good
Expectancy If You Start
To Add Third Out
<X-word-ms ms=39,260,379,140,179,320 index=2492 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-13,14-19,20-23>Or Four In All There You
<X-word-ms ms=239,280,199,139,120,179 index=2493 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-11,12-15,16-21,22-25>Try To Trade The Third And
The Fourth Lake You
<X-word-ms ms=159,260,219,100,119,259 index=2495 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-9,10-12,13-17,18-22>Have A Lot Of More Stop
<X-word-ms ms=340,79,260,219,280 index=2496 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-15,16-20>Outs Is Going To Hurt
<X-word-ms ms=159,179,140,99,179,180,199 index=2497 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-12,13-19,20-22,23-25>The Edge So I Prefer To Do
Fewer Trades With
Much Better Age
<X-word-ms ms=220,259,219,300,139 index=2500 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-15,16-20,21-26>Right On Overall They Going
<X-word-ms ms=120,119,179,300,199,99 index=2501 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-17,18-25,26-28>To Make More Money Believe It
<X-word-ms ms=60,199,440,79,99,200 index=2502 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-11,12-16,17-22>Or Not If We Just Focus
<X-word-ms ms=139,219,360,179,440 index=2503 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-13,14-19,20-24>On Second Like Write This
Is Cycle And These
Are Two All Signals
<X-word-ms ms=99,99,220,339,220,259 index=2506 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-16,17-21,22-27,28-30>That Can Actually Find Under 15
115 Years Ago
So Again Momentum Volatility
Construction And Expansion
Is Something That It's
<X-word-ms ms=239,180,159,199,160,279 index=2511 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-16,17-20,21-27>Just The Way This Top Market
<X-word-ms ms=380,199,100,159,559 index=2512 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-13,14-18,19-21>Works There Is Just No
<X-word-ms ms=199,160,259,220,219 index=2513 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-15,16-18,19-22>Other Way Around It I'm
From Contraction Comes
Expansions Right Even
If You Applied To
80 20 Amaze At
<X-word-ms ms=99,179,140,319,619 index=2518 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-7,8-10,11-15>the 8 10 15 Amaz
On The
C Ml Indicator
Right Here Turns Green
<X-word-ms ms=140,119,259,320,79,180 index=2522 character_ranges=0-0,1-4,5-10,11-18,19-22,23-29>A lot These Moments Are Should
Be Green I Mean
Even In Decorates
<X-word-ms ms=139,99,380,200,339 index=2525 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-16,17-24>We Have They Work Exactly
The Same 115 Years
<X-word-ms ms=320,99,79,139,140,299 index=2527 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-15,16-18,19-27>Ago And Is Going To Continue
In The Future When
The Market Stops Behaving
Momentum I Don't Know
<X-word-ms ms=340,199,120,239,579 index=2531 character_ranges=0-7,8-11,12-16,17-19,20-21>Probably You Know Uh I
<X-word-ms ms=159,40,259,480,320 index=2532 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-15,16-18,19-24>Don't Know Maybe No There
Were Answer Something Or
<X-word-ms ms=119,320,119,240,299 index=2534 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-11,12-15,16-20>I Don'T Know How What
Needs To Happen For
<X-word-ms ms=179,200,199,160,179,259 index=2536 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-17,18-24,25-32>This For These Two Really Happens
Because Why There
Is Moment Um Am
Volatility Construction Expansion
<X-word-ms ms=160,179,159,260,139,300 index=2540 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-15,16-19,20-25>Works So Well In The Stock
Market And For Example
<X-word-ms ms=179,139,160,99,420,279 index=2542 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-10,11-13,14-21,22-29>Not So Well In Futures Because
<X-word-ms ms=159,120,159,500,780 index=2543 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-17,18-23>In This Top Market There
<X-word-ms ms=159,139,280,219,400 index=2544 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-17,18-27>Is This Thing That Everybody
<X-word-ms ms=380,119,99,119,200,139 index=2545 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-15,16-22,23-25>Comes To The Sub Market To
<X-word-ms ms=119,260,280,280,179 index=2546 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-16,17-22,23-25>Make Money Nobody Comes To
<X-word-ms ms=79,119,440,360,279 index=2547 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-15,16-19,20-24>The South Market You Sell
Short Apple Shares
Too Hedge Something
Doesn't Exceed Doesn'T
Know Every Body Wants
To Buy A Apple
<X-word-ms ms=299,180,139,99,120,99,119 index=2553 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-17,18-20,21-24,25-27>Be Cause They Want To Set At
Higher Price Institutions
Funds Pension
Fonds Individual
Traders Everybody
You Know Social Media
<X-word-ms ms=279,140,199,179,180,299 index=2559 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-13,14-18,19-24>We All Want To Make Money
<X-word-ms ms=180,59,179,180,139,179,180 index=2560 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-15,16-21,22-24,25-29,30-35>That's The Whole Point Of This Right
That'S Why On The
<X-word-ms ms=179,179,100,139,300,480 index=2562 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-10,11-15,16-25,26-34>Bull Side I Have Sometimes Multiple
Legs Write And
<X-word-ms ms=140,99,380,179,99,159 index=2564 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-16,17-22,23-25,26-29>In Their Parasite Which Is How
One Crack
<X-word-ms ms=39,139,380,259,220 index=2566 character_ranges=0-0,1-7,8-13,14-19,20-25>A Little Lower There First
Valley Consideration And
<X-word-ms ms=119,260,239,99,140,339 index=2568 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-14,15-17,18-21,22-27>The Second Lake It The Flush
<X-word-ms ms=380,260,179,179,260 index=2569 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-13,14-18,19-23>Because On The Bear Site
<X-word-ms ms=199,200,299,99,300 index=2570 character_ranges=0-9,10-12,13-19,20-22,23-27>Everything Is Fueled By Fear
<X-word-ms ms=360,219,159,160,319 index=2571 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-15,16-18,19-22>Every Body Wants Be Out
That S Out On
<X-word-ms ms=260,119,239,120,859 index=2573 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-16,17-22>That Is Point The Flush
And It Reverses
So Have A Third
<X-word-ms ms=259,200,159,239,440 index=2576 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-8,9-13,14-19>Lake As I Said There
Should Be Truncation Or
<X-word-ms ms=239,300,219,180,259 index=2578 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-15,16-19,20-22>Higher Low Which Was In
This Case And We
Reverse The Trend
<X-word-ms ms=500,179,99,159,280 index=2581 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-14,15-19>On This One Was Same
After The Second Like
The Flash Everything
Turned Into Sideways
<X-word-ms ms=259,219,140,159,539 index=2585 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-15,16-23>Face And Then It Reverse
So On Their Parasite
Just Have The Second
Leg Fear And We
<X-word-ms ms=99,199,480,160,279 index=2589 character_ranges=0-3,4-12,13-17,18-23,24-30>Have Multiple Legs Going Higher
<X-word-ms ms=159,80,119,239,260,340 index=2590 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-8,9-15,16-21,22-26>In A Very Strong Stock Over
Time Because It's Fured
By Greed So That
Is Why Greer And
Fear Really Shape
Our You Know
The Markets Its Just
<X-word-ms ms=280,99,179,280,219 index=2597 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-14,15-19>The Way This So Many
<X-word-ms ms=220,179,179,180,219,440 index=2598 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-14,15-20,21-23,24-28>People Ask What About Ai Well
I Will Execute
Right Based On
One Human Is Returning
Them To Do The
Human Is Going To
Redesign AI To
Something Right And
<X-word-ms ms=269,119,219,100,419 index=2606 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-15,16-18>It's Going To Be No
From A Strategic Point
<X-word-ms ms=119,199,460,160,119 index=2608 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-15,16-18>Of View Is Going To
Be Fured By Green
By Greed I
Put Green Here
Sorry Grid
Or Fear That
Just The Two Things
Are Going To Motivate
Human To Really Use
Ai To Run Something
<X-word-ms ms=159,140,279,240,199 index=2618 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-18,19-26>And Make Money That Another
Thing Is Always
<X-word-ms ms=140,219,380,259,160 index=2620 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-13,14-21,22-24>Going This Way Because We
<X-word-ms ms=99,259,220,219,320 index=2621 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-16,17-25>Not Here To Hedge Anything
Which Want You Make
<X-word-ms ms=320,400,139,99,39,239 index=2623 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-16,17-19,20-23>Money When To Buy To Max
Fear That Point
Of Sphere Right So
And So
That's The Way We
<X-word-ms ms=339,240,139,240,179 index=2628 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-13,14-19,20-22>Really Do This Stuff On
<X-word-ms ms=199,220,199,100,479 index=2629 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-16,17-23>Why With Base Our System
On Volatility
Construction Expansion
Pair With Momentum Is
<X-word-ms ms=99,119,420,260,579 index=2633 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-14,15-20,21-24>A Very Powerful Thing And
<X-word-ms ms=79,180,359,140,239,139 index=2634 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-12,13-16,17-26,27-28>It Sounds You Saw Something I
Invented It Is
Not Something Nobody Invented
Just Away Stocks
Move Again If Can
Just Go
Historically Look
<X-word-ms ms=99,220,139,159,240,379 index=2641 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-14,15-20,21-25>At All Of These Stalk From
Since The Stock Market
Really Began Right
There Are Charts From
<X-word-ms ms=280,279,280,139,200 index=2645 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-13,14-21>The You Know I Believe
<X-word-ms ms=139,139,320,219,280 index=2646 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-14,15-17,18-24>That They First So Market
Open In The Netherlands
If I'm Mistaken In
the 1800s
<X-word-ms ms=159,159,260,239,260 index=2650 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-17,18-20,21-23>Maybe Some Correct Me If
<X-word-ms ms=159,280,139,179,400 index=2651 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-16,17-20>I'M Wrong On This But
<X-word-ms ms=119,119,60,199,159,420 index=2652 character_ranges=0-0,1-8,9-11,12-15,16-19,20-23>I Believe It Was The 1st
Stalk Market Ever
Invented And
You Know There
Were These Tulips
<X-word-ms ms=159,119,180,259,380 index=2657 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-11,12-17,18-20>A Bill Leave Chart As
Well Not Same Era
Any Trader Like
Momentum And Again So
<X-word-ms ms=239,200,139,99,160,240 index=2661 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-15,16-20,21-23>Just To Show You That On
The Basis That Own
Water We Are Building
Our System And
They Type Of Thinking
<X-word-ms ms=359,200,199,200,179 index=2666 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-14,15-17,18-23>You Should Have To Build
<X-word-ms ms=159,140,179,199,180,199 index=2667 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-16,17-21,22-27>Your Own Stuff As Well Which
<X-word-ms ms=79,139,300,220,99,359 index=2668 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-16,17-20,21-25,26-34>Is Very Important I'm Very Valuable
<X-word-ms ms=320,99,140,199,320 index=2669 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-12,13-15>If You Ask Me So
<X-word-ms ms=480,259,99,160,399 index=2670 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-12,13-17,18-21>Now Let's Get Into The
Trend Fundamentals
And Swim Training Rules
Some Process Probably
<X-word-ms ms=359,160,159,179,540 index=2674 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-12,13-21>Do Want To Do Probably
<X-word-ms ms=359,140,119,279,240 index=2675 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-7,8-10,11-17>Like A 5 10 Minute
Break Instead Of Okay
With People Because
<X-word-ms ms=400,220,139,159,139 index=2678 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-15,16-18>This Is Going To Be
<X-word-ms ms=200,139,79,260,500 index=2679 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-17,18-22>Like In The Second Part
I Probably Need Some
Water Or Something So
I Will Be Back
In 10 Minutes So
It's 20 Right Now
It'S Past 20 If
<X-word-ms ms=460,339,39,120,99 index=2686 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-7,8-13,14-16>30 We'Re Going To
<X-word-ms ms=99,219,180,79,260,440 index=2687 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-14,15-19,20-22>Be Here Is That Fine If
<X-word-ms ms=139,199,260,159,700 index=2688 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-15,16-22>You Can You Know Ascend
<X-word-ms ms=139,139,139,200,299,300 index=2689 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-18,19-28,29-33>There In Each Other Something That
<X-word-ms ms=300,199,219,220,139 index=2690 character_ranges=0-8,9-11,12-19,20-22,23-26>Everybody Is Hearing Me And
<X-word-ms ms=599,39,140,179,119 index=2691 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-15,16-17,18-21>We're Going Take A Ten
<X-word-ms ms=200,139,440,39,180,319 index=2692 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-17,18-21,22-26,27-32>Minute Break Let'S Get Some Water
Probably Like Coffee Because
<X-word-ms ms=119,19,120,139,159,180,239,280 index=2694 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-10,11-13,14-17,18-22,23-26,27-33>We'Re Going To Get Into The Second
Part Right Now I'M
<X-word-ms ms=99,179,180,239,280,359 index=2696 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-17,18-20,21-27>Going To Shut Down My Screen
<X-word-ms ms=260,219,200,119,320 index=2697 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-16,17-22>For Now But Don't Worry
And Here So
No Were Going Go
<X-word-ms ms=220,139,179,140,159,39,280 index=2700 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-12,13-16,17-18,19-25>In To You Can Add A Second
Part Of The Presentation
<X-word-ms ms=140,59,159,180,219,440 index=2702 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-14,15-17,18-20,21-25>Where Are Going To Go Talk
About It Trend Fundamentals
<X-word-ms ms=139,200,239,380,239 index=2704 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-18,19-24,25-27>And Stream Training Rules On
<X-word-ms ms=340,340,219,99,140 index=2705 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-15,16-21,22-24>Process So We're Going To
Go Into The Actual
Process And Scanning
<X-word-ms ms=180,239,239,320,239 index=2708 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-12,13-18,19-22>On The Second Video But
<X-word-ms ms=400,39,119,120,99,139,179 index=2709 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-10,11-13,14-16,17-21,22-24>We'Re Going To Go Some Of
<X-word-ms ms=160,480,119,199,340 index=2710 character_ranges=0-2,3-11,12-14,15-20,21-23>The Overview Of Rules Of
The Setup Itself Know
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,320,199,119 index=2712 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-16,17-21>How Its Rated You Know
Their Risk And Everything
<X-word-ms ms=219,39,99,140,139,480 index=2714 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-16,17-21,22-30>I'm Going To Show Some Examples
<X-word-ms ms=320,219,59,300,239 index=2715 character_ranges=0-8,9-11,12-15,16-22,23-26>Obviously In The Charts And
Not Only Should Know
The Other View Off
<X-word-ms ms=199,280,219,200,400 index=2718 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-13,14-18,19-21>There Rules Or What Do
You Want Really Want
To Here About The
Mechanics And Be
The Actual Concept Of
<X-word-ms ms=259,180,79,299,240 index=2723 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-15,16-18>What We'Re Doing In
The Relationship To Intermediate
Term Trend No Momentum
Volatility Contraction So
<X-word-ms ms=119,79,240,539,99 index=2727 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-17,18-20>You Can Apply Kind Of
<X-word-ms ms=119,440,139,40,139,279 index=2728 character_ranges=0-2,3-13,14-18,19-20,21-25,26-32>The Principles That I Just Showed
<X-word-ms ms=100,240,159,119,119,80,239 index=2729 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-15,16-18,19-22,23-29>You Put It There On The Screen
<X-word-ms ms=260,139,159,240,119,199 index=2730 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-18,19-25>For Your So You Can Really
Connect That And
<X-word-ms ms=140,379,280,159,140 index=2732 character_ranges=0-3,4-14,15-19,20-24,25-28>Real Understand That When You
<X-word-ms ms=59,299,260,239,200 index=2733 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-16,17-20>Are Doing Here Is Not
<X-word-ms ms=480,99,119,80,319 index=2734 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-10,11-14,15-21>It's Just A Way Stocks
Move Right Its Not
It'S Something That I
Invented Really Defines
<X-word-ms ms=79,100,440,299,180 index=2738 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-21,22-27,28-31>The Whole Distribution Right But
Of Course With A
Knowledge Of System Trading
<X-word-ms ms=539,119,119,200,179 index=2741 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-15,16-22>And How It Sucks Really
<X-word-ms ms=199,120,279,220,359 index=2742 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-19,20-21,22-27>Move When Everything I Built
<X-word-ms ms=180,359,140,139,199 index=2743 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-13,14-19,20-25>This System In Their Rules
<X-word-ms ms=260,199,120,99,299,400 index=2744 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-10,11-17,18-22>In Not In A Manner That
<X-word-ms ms=99,120,219,440,239 index=2745 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-13,14-21,22-28>You Can Really Control Equity
<X-word-ms ms=480,120,139,139,280 index=2746 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-10,11-14,15-21>Corp And We Can Really
Controll The Distribution Again
<X-word-ms ms=240,119,99,119,79,519 index=2748 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-14,15-16,17-29>Know It And Its A Distribution
<X-word-ms ms=260,139,99,180,299,220 index=2749 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-16,17-21,22-27>There We Can Work With Right
So If You Change
<X-word-ms ms=259,220,199,300,319 index=2751 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-11,12-17,18-22>One Of These Rules Here
I'm Getting Off Right
<X-word-ms ms=279,159,79,240,199,119 index=2753 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-15,16-19,20-22>Now On The First One Is
<X-word-ms ms=180,240,119,299,400 index=2754 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-10,11-16,17-19>That Find A Start At
1st Leg Of Move
There Should
<X-word-ms ms=100,260,199,220,300 index=2757 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-11,12-18,19-24>Be Coming Up Either Multi
Week Month Base Or
<X-word-ms ms=219,260,119,240,500 index=2759 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-14,15-17,18-20>Return Reset Of 50 M8
<X-word-ms ms=179,140,119,180,159,300 index=2760 character_ranges=0-3,4-13,14-16,17-21,22-27,28-31>It's Something To Talk About All
Time And
Again What
We Want
Achieve Intermediate
Term Trend So For
Exam P Let
Me Share Trading
<X-word-ms ms=199,199,320,199,119 index=2768 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-14,15-17,18-21>View Right Here So You
<X-word-ms ms=60,340,79,199,79,119,260 index=2769 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-15,16-19,20-24,25-30>Can Kind Of Show You This Stuff
Off And Share Application
Windows Trading View Share
So Everybody Should
<X-word-ms ms=140,300,159,220,239 index=2773 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-11,12-20,21-24>Be Seeing My Training You
<X-word-ms ms=239,340,199,180,199 index=2774 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-18,19-21,22-24>Yeah They're Seeing It So
The Point
<X-word-ms ms=199,279,239,240,219 index=2776 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-13,14-19>Is That If You Start
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,159,260,300 index=2777 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-14,15-20>To Look At This Trade
<X-word-ms ms=159,119,140,119,119,180,199 index=2778 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-14,15-18,19-20,21-27,28-30>Right Here This Was A Signal We
Got In January
2026 Right On
<X-word-ms ms=260,140,139,220,180,259 index=2781 character_ranges=0-8,9-13,14-16,17-21,22-26,27-31>Generally That We Made Some Nice
Money Some Net Returns
Things Were Working Nicely
<X-word-ms ms=239,240,119,99,100,140,759 index=2784 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-13,14-16,17-19,20-24>So If You Look At It Then
<X-word-ms ms=300,79,159,180,340 index=2785 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-14,15-18>What Do We Want See
And Achieve Is
That The Actual
Be Fast Section Of
The Trend Off Course
<X-word-ms ms=159,60,139,100,180,199,140,239 index=2790 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-16,17-19,20-24,25-27,28-32>You Will See That It Came Up From
<X-word-ms ms=279,300,159,300,359 index=2791 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-17,18-22>This Kind Of Multi-Week
Base Off Course I
<X-word-ms ms=399,159,140,199,340 index=2793 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-15,16-20>Can Call In Many Ways
<X-word-ms ms=180,179,100,159,119,240,239 index=2794 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-15,16-17,18-22,23-26>But This Is Just A Base For
<X-word-ms ms=239,140,260,119,339 index=2795 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-10,11-13,14-19>Me A Couple Of Weeks
<X-word-ms ms=120,239,180,159,179,320 index=2796 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-12,13-18,19-21,22-31>Maybe Not Two Month Or Something
Then To See They
May Start Adjust No
Cross Lower Around
50 Am So
<X-word-ms ms=239,239,220,279,360 index=2801 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-12,13-17,18-24>In The Higher Time Frames
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,119,300,199,279 index=2802 character_ranges=0-7,8-12,13-16,17-19,20-22,23-27>Remember That The 50 Am Kind
Of Resembles The
8 And 10 Weekly
In A Weekly
<X-word-ms ms=160,259,160,79,99,79,159,220 index=2806 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-8,9-12,13-15,16-18,19-22,23-27>Ema So If You Go To The Weak
<X-word-ms ms=159,180,220,260,159,79 index=2807 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-15,16-20,21-24,25-28>Lead Chart Right Here You Can
See That We Got
Our Signal There
As I Know It's
<X-word-ms ms=79,220,99,539,240 index=2811 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-11,12-25,26-31>At First One Consideration After
<X-word-ms ms=139,280,219,199,220 index=2812 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-16,17-21>The 1st Lake They Came
Up From The Detail
On 20 Em Is
On The Weekly So
Off Course Whoever Shoot
<X-word-ms ms=160,159,159,159,319,220 index=2817 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-13,14-17,18-20,21-23>It Right There The 50 So
<X-word-ms ms=199,140,180,179,180,100,380 index=2818 character_ranges=0-0,1-2,3-5,6-10,11-15,16-17,18-24>D 5 Is More Like A Detail
Or De 80 Ema
<X-word-ms ms=259,120,239,219,240 index=2820 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-12,13-18,19-21>In The Weekly Right So
<X-word-ms ms=299,119,120,79,199,279 index=2821 character_ranges=0-7,8-9,10-14,15-16,17-22,23-27>Whenever I Have A Multi Week
<X-word-ms ms=260,420,159,159,480 index=2822 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-14,15-20,21-26>Base Looking At Daily Chart
You Will See That
Price Just Has Data
<X-word-ms ms=199,199,180,399,480 index=2825 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-18,19-26>To Into Cross Lower Charges
<X-word-ms ms=119,199,119,240,219,240 index=2826 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-17,18-21,22-26>All Over The Place But It's
<X-word-ms ms=259,180,239,280,259 index=2827 character_ranges=0-7,8-10,11-16,17-19,20-24>Building Up Based So Once
It Breaks Out
And My Definition Of
First They Comes From
The 15 Am Train
Reset So Again
<X-word-ms ms=140,119,119,199,199,159,240 index=2833 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-11,12-16,17-20,21-24,25-29>I Talk About This All The Time
As Long Us We
<X-word-ms ms=159,140,180,259,360 index=2835 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-14,15-19,20-24>Count The First Lake From
<X-word-ms ms=139,280,239,199,260 index=2836 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-12,13-19,20-25>The Moment It Really Comes
<X-word-ms ms=220,139,260,380,119 index=2837 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-13,14-15>Off From 50 Am A
Why Would Do That
I Mean
Because If
<X-word-ms ms=79,119,60,140,420,139,220 index=2841 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-17,18-24,25-27,28-34>You Look At Higher Timers In Weekly
That's Their Point
Of Reset Of
D When In The
Weekly Chart There Is
These Shorter Term
Kind Assigned Pullback
Cycle That Ended
And Started Next New
Impulse And New Like
Higher So It's
<X-word-ms ms=199,180,159,100,639 index=2852 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-14,15-16,17-30>Coming Off From A Consideration
<X-word-ms ms=300,140,159,220,159,59 index=2853 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-17,18-20,21-24>That Is Very Tight In The
Weekly Of Course We
<X-word-ms ms=180,220,179,320,279 index=2855 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-16,17-22,23-28>Don't Trade These Bases Again
They Are Very Volatile
<X-word-ms ms=279,140,260,239,279 index=2857 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-16,17-22>There Not Easy To Trade
On This Success Rate
<X-word-ms ms=199,160,139,119,119,300 index=2859 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-13,14-16,17-22>On This End To Be Lower
<X-word-ms ms=279,160,119,99,240,399 index=2860 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-13,14-18,19-20>So You Need To Have A
System Going To
Be A Low Win
<X-word-ms ms=220,420,220,139,100 index=2863 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-15,16-19,20-22>Rate System With All Of
<X-word-ms ms=140,299,39,180,159,159,380 index=2864 character_ranges=0-2,3-11,12-14,15-19,20-24,25-27,28-40>The Problems Of That Type Of Distribution
<X-word-ms ms=220,39,140,159,279,180 index=2865 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-12,13-16,17-20>So We Have To Hit For
Home Run So Trade
<X-word-ms ms=159,199,460,160,219 index=2867 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-17,18-27>And Stuff It's Not Something
<X-word-ms ms=220,159,100,159,340,239 index=2868 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-17,18-27,28-31>That Is On Capital Efficient For
<X-word-ms ms=100,99,119,79,280,179,200 index=2869 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-9,10-15,16-20,21-23,24-26>Me I Don't Quite Like It So
<X-word-ms ms=500,99,180,139,100 index=2870 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-13,14-16>Its Not For Me So
<X-word-ms ms=159,380,239,159,359 index=2871 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-14,15-18>Just Dont Do It But
Essentially Once
<X-word-ms ms=139,119,79,220,199,180,119 index=2873 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-16,17-21,22-28,29-31>You See The First Lake Coming Up
<X-word-ms ms=119,260,460,79,480 index=2874 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-13,14-18>From 50 In May This
<X-word-ms ms=379,160,99,119,400 index=2875 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-16,17-20>Marks This Is The 1st
Leg After The Present
Time Relationship When
<X-word-ms ms=119,159,140,279,279,159 index=2878 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-19,20-23,24-27>They Pull Back Phase And The
Consideration Note That
But The Multi
<X-word-ms ms=199,340,220,100,219 index=2881 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-14,15-21>Wave Lower In A Weekly
<X-word-ms ms=280,319,260,119,819 index=2882 character_ranges=0-4,5-13,14-17,18-22,23-28>Chart Actually You Know Ended
<X-word-ms ms=199,140,119,180,219,200 index=2883 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-18,19-22,23-27>And Now We're Going For Next
Like Higher In
This Cycle Of Momentum
<X-word-ms ms=229,229,360,179,720 index=2886 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-16,17-30>First No Leg High Consideration
<X-word-ms ms=159,319,120,139,300 index=2887 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-14,15-18>Lake Hire On So One
So It Coming
<X-word-ms ms=119,119,260,399,500 index=2889 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-13,14-16>Up From 50 May Is
<X-word-ms ms=199,140,220,159,519 index=2890 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-9,10-12,13-16>What I See As 1st
<X-word-ms ms=239,160,239,340,259 index=2891 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-17,18-23>Lake Off Fresh New Trend
Of Course It Tipped
<X-word-ms ms=119,179,220,279,220 index=2893 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-14,15-20,21-25>You Don't Start Right Here
<X-word-ms ms=100,479,140,159,199 index=2894 character_ranges=0-1,2-10,11-13,14-16,17-22>In Breakout By We Count
It Since The
Start Of 50 May
<X-word-ms ms=239,119,60,199,460 index=2897 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-13,14-16>So You Can See As
<X-word-ms ms=100,139,80,219,159,79,200,299 index=2898 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-17,18-22,23-24,25-27,28-31>Long As It Started From A 15 May
<X-word-ms ms=180,180,139,40,159,579 index=2899 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-13,14-19,20-25>Is Going To Be Trend Reset
<X-word-ms ms=139,120,119,119,119,199,340 index=2900 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-16,17-19,20-25,26-30>And It's Going To Be First Like
For Me So This
<X-word-ms ms=139,79,220,159,100,140,139,159 index=2902 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-13,14-18,19-20,21-24,25-29,30-32>Is The Firstly That I Was Want To
<X-word-ms ms=220,159,140,99,260,180 index=2903 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-16,17-20,21-23>See Then You Will See At
These Moves Forward
The 80 20
and 50 Amaze Stucked
<X-word-ms ms=140,140,259,340,400 index=2907 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-13,14-16,17-20>Up On Training In The
<X-word-ms ms=79,359,119,220,220,300 index=2908 character_ranges=0-0,1-3,4-9,10-14,15-20,21-25>C Ml Would Turn Green Here
<X-word-ms ms=159,259,140,260,180,159 index=2909 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-15,16-18,19-23>So At This Point We Have
Momentum Linearity
With The Type
<X-word-ms ms=200,339,220,180,220 index=2912 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-15,16-20>Of Trend That We Want
<X-word-ms ms=179,239,200,139,159,500 index=2913 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-13,14-19,20-22,23-29>To Trade There Could Be Trends
<X-word-ms ms=120,99,159,440,99,280 index=2914 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-10,11-12,13-17,18-23>That I Have A Turn Reset
Off 50 Amaze
Obviously Is Are
<X-word-ms ms=119,340,379,140,140 index=2917 character_ranges=0-4,5-11,12-15,16-20,21-25>Going Higher And They Will
<X-word-ms ms=199,220,79,260,139,279 index=2918 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-11,12-14,15-19,20-23>Have These C Ml Turn Red
If That Happens
<X-word-ms ms=239,119,260,79,260,239 index=2920 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-15,16-27,28-32>Now The Seem All Essentially What
It Measures Is The
Over Lab Between
Candles Is Measures
The Highest You
<X-word-ms ms=59,140,300,159,299,260 index=2925 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-18,19-26,27-30,31-38>Know The Difference Between The Highest
<X-word-ms ms=100,180,199,179,400 index=2926 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-13,14-20>And Low On The Candle
Or Right Now Against
You Want Before That
I Need Draws
<X-word-ms ms=139,320,139,300,199 index=2930 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-16,17-21>Any Kind Of Drugs Like
<X-word-ms ms=100,340,220,319,699 index=2931 character_ranges=0-1,2-9,10-13,14-16,17-24>An Average Off 21 Candles
Going Back So Can
<X-word-ms ms=79,180,119,119,340,99,80 index=2933 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-11,12-14,15-22,23-25,26-29>It Gives You In Average Of The
<X-word-ms ms=139,180,220,259,140,199 index=2934 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-14,15-21,22-25,26-29>Last Twenty One Colors Are Saw
Or 14 Depends Set
<X-word-ms ms=119,460,140,239,279 index=2936 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-13,14-22,23-25>On Don't Quite Remember To
<X-word-ms ms=199,200,159,259,500 index=2937 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-16,17-22,23-26>Setting That Have There How
<X-word-ms ms=220,100,119,300,239,279 index=2938 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-15,16-24,25-30>You Know The Was Actually Built
When Because Of Candle
Overlap Too Much Kind
<X-word-ms ms=59,279,220,230,180,279 index=2941 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-11,12-15,16-20,21-24>Of Lover Lab You Will See
<X-word-ms ms=439,240,159,159,460 index=2942 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-14,15-21>That There Is A Choppy
Movement That's Why When
<X-word-ms ms=199,199,220,319,440 index=2944 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-15,16-21,22-33>This Thing Turns Green Essentially
<X-word-ms ms=230,159,179,120,239,260 index=2945 character_ranges=0-4,5-12,13-15,16-18,19-22,23-26>We're Looking At An Own Bot
The Mean They Also
Being Trading Not Non
Volatile Trend
Right Here These
<X-word-ms ms=260,179,200,119,199,220 index=2950 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-16,17-20,21-28>And Then It'S The Mid Section
Off The Train Are
Very High Let
<X-word-ms ms=179,360,159,300,439 index=2953 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-17,18-22,23-32>Just Support About Data Obviously
<X-word-ms ms=260,180,179,200,179,119 index=2954 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-16,17-20,21-24>But I'm Just Know Let You
<X-word-ms ms=140,119,140,239,199,340 index=2955 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-18,19-25,26-31>Know How This Thing Really Works
So After The First
<X-word-ms ms=220,279,279,160,179 index=2957 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-13,14-18,19-22>Lake Higher We Look For
The First Valley Consolidation
So Before Getting That
Is Did Know
These Concept Of
The 1st
<X-word-ms ms=199,300,159,119,220,259 index=2963 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-14,15-19,20-32>Like Hire Up In Term Intermediate
Turn Trend It Always
<X-word-ms ms=239,279,140,179,220 index=2965 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-11,12-16,17-22>Comes From A Tren Reset
Off 50 May You
<X-word-ms ms=99,180,39,159,320,159,300 index=2967 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-8,9-13,14-18,19-21,22-30>Can Be At Same Time No Breaking
<X-word-ms ms=159,159,140,159,199,220 index=2968 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-9,10-15,16-20,21-25>Out From A Multi Week Base
Honestly Because Sometimes That's
Where From Where
D Leg Really Originates
Right But We
The Trend Reset Off
Is Of 50 May
That's The Golden Rule
<X-word-ms ms=380,119,39,79,300,260 index=2976 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-12,13-18,19-23>And This Is A First Lake
<X-word-ms ms=140,119,19,199,480,279 index=2977 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-14,15-18,19-22>So You Will See The 1st
Like Developing D
M S Open Up
<X-word-ms ms=220,220,180,339,200 index=2980 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-12,13-17,18-20>And Stuck Top Ride At
<X-word-ms ms=159,159,140,59,180,220,119 index=2981 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-15,16-20,21-24,25-28>This Going To Be Same For The
<X-word-ms ms=139,220,500,100,259 index=2982 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-17,18-25>Bear Side On Their Similar
<X-word-ms ms=340,100,79,239,199,140 index=2983 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-18,19-21,22-26>Green In That Point Or Have
<X-word-ms ms=100,219,180,119,199,180,340 index=2984 character_ranges=0-0,1-4,5-8,9-10,11-15,16-19,20-25>A Leg Off A Tren New Fresh
<X-word-ms ms=239,140,99,200,200,199 index=2985 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-8,9-14,15-18,19-22>Look Of A Train And You
<X-word-ms ms=180,119,219,260,319 index=2986 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-16,17-21>Want To Find Then Find
The First Valley Consideration
To Trade The
Breakout For This
<X-word-ms ms=280,199,140,199,159,180 index=2990 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-13,14-20,21-25,26-28>Second Lake We Always Want To
<X-word-ms ms=119,139,119,320,179,480 index=2991 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-15,16-19,20-23>Look For The 2nd Leg Not
<X-word-ms ms=220,239,199,300,199 index=2992 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-15,16-20,21-24>Third Lakes Even Here You
<X-word-ms ms=100,179,100,180,279,220 index=2993 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-15,16-22,23-27>Will See How The Second Like
There Than The Second
Value Conservation Of
<X-word-ms ms=159,199,180,179,220,220 index=2996 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-14,15-18,19-26,27-30>Course Was This One Because The
Ballet Constitution Is Measured
Really By Time
<X-word-ms ms=260,140,19,279,160,379 index=2999 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-7,8-14,15-17,18-25>Buy In A Number Of Candles
<X-word-ms ms=260,279,240,119,440 index=3000 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-14,15-17,18-30>After High That Is Consolidated
<X-word-ms ms=239,119,220,269,319 index=3001 character_ranges=0-6,7-10,11-15,16-19,20-26>Against The Lake And Before
The Breakout Candle
<X-word-ms ms=160,159,159,199,279,140 index=3003 character_ranges=0-4,5-11,12-14,15-17,18-23,24-29>There Should Be At Least Seven
Candles In Between That
So That Marks
That The Correction
In Time As
Decoration I'm Sorry
Yet The Collection After
Deprized Really Made A
Move Higher Right
<X-word-ms ms=419,100,140,300,199 index=3012 character_ranges=0-8,9-11,12-19,20-25,26-30>Incorrect Is Through Price Then
<X-word-ms ms=139,140,119,159,240,299 index=3013 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-18,19-26,27-31>It Needs To Correct Through Time
And Once You
Have This Number Data
Showed Me That Dad
It's Very Good Indication
<X-word-ms ms=140,180,99,199,160,639 index=3018 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-18,19-23,24-37>That Does The First Part Consideration
<X-word-ms ms=140,439,159,20,340 index=3019 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-13,14-22>And If You Are Treating
This One Right Through
<X-word-ms ms=140,179,240,219,220,119 index=3021 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-13,14-18,19-25,26-29>The Second Leg Your Routes Are
<X-word-ms ms=159,280,419,140,159 index=3022 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-17,18-20>Very High But Then If
You Wait For The
<X-word-ms ms=340,220,180,139,199 index=3024 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-15,16-19,20-24>Third Lake Which Was This
<X-word-ms ms=100,180,159,99,200,139,180 index=3025 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-14,15-22,23-25,26-31>On Race Here To Concede It Tends
<X-word-ms ms=79,159,39,440,659 index=3026 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-7,8-16,17-23>To Get A Volatile Choppy
These Decades Formost
Stocks In Most Cycles
<X-word-ms ms=159,139,140,159,279,600 index=3029 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-12,13-17,18-24>So We Want Do That Things
That Consistent With
<X-word-ms ms=300,279,140,259,579 index=3031 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-17,18-23>More Stops Or Most Cycle
<X-word-ms ms=240,219,240,179,260 index=3032 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-16,17-22>We Don't To Build Rules
Around How A Stock
Moved In 2020 And
Have Four Legs Higher
<X-word-ms ms=180,100,179,420,180 index=3036 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-10,11-17,18-25>All Of Them Leaner Looking
Great Right But Then
<X-word-ms ms=239,99,200,119,800 index=3038 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-15,16-20,21-29>That's The Point When Trailing
Really Works Right
<X-word-ms ms=270,239,199,260,239 index=3040 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-13,14-18,19-23>But We Haven't Seen Such
A Period In
A Big Basket Of
Stops Since 20 So
They're Not Something Repeatable
That's Why Our Routes
Are Focused On Start
<X-word-ms ms=340,180,179,180,269 index=3047 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-19,20-23>On House Talk Smooth The
<X-word-ms ms=480,139,300,59,279 index=3048 character_ranges=0-7,8-10,11-15,16-18,19-25>Majority Of Time No Single
<X-word-ms ms=340,220,119,260,439 index=3049 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-14,15-19,20-22>System That Can Work In
All Market Phases
It Doesn't Exist But
At Least If
We Can You
<X-word-ms ms=119,260,139,120,139,320 index=3054 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-14,15-19,20-24>Know On The One Side When
<X-word-ms ms=279,179,160,119,179,220 index=3055 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-13,14-15,16-20,21-25>They Market Is A Week That
This Does Not Work
To Limit Drawdown
<X-word-ms ms=239,220,159,79,140,159,199 index=3058 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-14,15-20,21-26,27-34>Based On All Of These Stuff Because
Were Very Selective
Just The First
Leg And We Only
<X-word-ms ms=199,140,199,260,479 index=3062 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-13,14-18,19-29>Won The Second Like Everything
<X-word-ms ms=220,140,179,440,260 index=3063 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-18,19-23>Will Be More Select Even
That's Another Way Of
Doing This That's Why
We Get
The Drawdown Based
On Profit
<X-word-ms ms=79,79,239,220,159,220,319 index=3069 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-13,14-19,20-25,26-28,29-30>That We Expect Right There Is A
<X-word-ms ms=260,139,140,420,680 index=3070 character_ranges=0-11,12-14,15-21,22-27,28-30>Relationship It Always There So
At First Like
<X-word-ms ms=239,79,280,199,260 index=3072 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-18,19-21,22-27>They Are Everything Is Their
So These Are Consideration
Seven Counts In
Between Here Dismars
The 1st You
Know The 1st
<X-word-ms ms=79,380,260,199,320 index=3078 character_ranges=0-2,3-13,14-17,18-21,22-24>One Conclusion Per See If
<X-word-ms ms=39,159,79,199,220,220,99 index=3079 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-7,8-14,15-20,21-23,24-26>I Have A Signal Great If We
Don't Which Not Write
But This Is Very
Important Because We
Are Second Legs
<X-word-ms ms=119,219,240,299,240 index=3084 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-14,15-20>Of The Trend We Don't
<X-word-ms ms=139,159,100,199,220,220 index=3085 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-18,19-23,24-29>Want To Mess Around With Third
Or Fourth Leg And
<X-word-ms ms=300,179,159,320,599 index=3087 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-14,15-17,18-20>Stuff Like That So At
<X-word-ms ms=159,220,239,240,279 index=3088 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-17,18-20>This Point All The 80
20 50 Mase
<X-word-ms ms=180,159,119,460,520 index=3090 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-14,15-23>Are Going Up On Trending
With A Good Slope
Right The Similar
Indicator Will Be
<X-word-ms ms=220,260,139,200,239 index=3094 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-15,16-22>Green As We Just Talked
<X-word-ms ms=179,200,159,119,220,139 index=3095 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-13,14-19,20-24,25-27>About So These Would Kind Of
The Initial
Trend In Know
Things You See
Before Even Start
To Consolidate The Candles
Before Breaking Out Obviously
I Discussed
This Thing It Needs
<X-word-ms ms=100,140,119,139,240,239,239 index=3104 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-15,16-21,22-26,27-28>To Have At Least Seven Days A
Consideration Minimum
<X-word-ms ms=199,320,339,140,279 index=3106 character_ranges=0-6,7-10,11-17,18-22,23-31>Between The Candle That Actually
End There First
Leg And Breakout
Candl In Between
These Should Be Something
<X-word-ms ms=199,79,140,239,239,320 index=3111 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-19,20-23,24-32>Kind Of Seen Between Two Counties
<X-word-ms ms=99,79,180,260,219,240 index=3112 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-9,10-17,18-25,26-32>As A First Falling Concern Dition
Whatever There's A
Common Question That If
<X-word-ms ms=380,180,199,159,119 index=3115 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-15,16-18>You Know We Have At
Least 7 Candles
<X-word-ms ms=159,239,180,239,539 index=3117 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-11,12-16,17-26>Right And If This Continues
To Go Continuous
To Just Consolidate
Here Sideways At What
Point You Just Call
It Out Right Well
<X-word-ms ms=319,119,100,219,260 index=3123 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-8,9-13,14-18>We Have A Rule That
Is The Stock In
Know After The
First Leg Closes
Below 20 Me
If It Close Below
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,279,199,260 index=3129 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-13,14-17,18-23>The Twenty May Any Given
<X-word-ms ms=260,159,79,159,240,259 index=3130 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-14,15-20,21-26>Point Time Of A Daily Cause
<X-word-ms ms=199,120,319,239,39,619 index=3131 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-17,18-19,20-24,25-30>Below The Twenties I Mean Which
Has Disregarded Style
<X-word-ms ms=399,159,220,199,519 index=3133 character_ranges=0-6,7-10,11-17,18-21,22-29>Because The Moment Was Because
Volatility Is Getting
<X-word-ms ms=319,180,180,179,100,119 index=3135 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-18,19-24,25-27>Into The Stock It's Going To
<X-word-ms ms=60,259,280,210,100,340 index=3136 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-15,16-18,19-29>Be Lower So This Is Everything
<X-word-ms ms=259,180,180,119,100,119,59 index=3137 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-12,13-16,17-20,21-22>We Do This Is The Way I
<X-word-ms ms=220,220,159,279,300 index=3138 character_ranges=0-5,6-7,8-14,15-20,21-24>Design A System Truly Get
The Outs Stuck
<X-word-ms ms=79,180,300,299,300 index=3140 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-15,16-20>In Your Favor As Much
<X-word-ms ms=199,420,200,179,199 index=3141 character_ranges=0-1,2-10,11-14,15-21,22-27>As Possible And That'S Again
Have To Focus On
One Specific Thing
<X-word-ms ms=210,420,100,199,500 index=3144 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-17,18-21>Right Bait On That And
<X-word-ms ms=220,199,239,199,180 index=3145 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-14,15-18,19-21>Then That Thing Has An
<X-word-ms ms=260,460,79,159,279 index=3146 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-17,18-24>Edge You Know Just Hammer
<X-word-ms ms=180,239,119,119,240,419 index=3147 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-18,19-21,22-27>Down You Don't Have To Bring
A In Reality I
<X-word-ms ms=180,180,180,119,420 index=3149 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-14,15-19,20-29>Didn't Today Is Very Difficult
<X-word-ms ms=199,420,39,139,440 index=3150 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-15,16-18>So You Can Enter 30
<X-word-ms ms=500,19,119,100,60,219 index=3151 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-12,13-15,16-19,20-23>Stocks At End Of The Day
Unless Your Running
<X-word-ms ms=139,240,199,99,100,100,139 index=3153 character_ranges=0-0,1-7,8-11,12-16,17-19,20-23,24-26>A Script But Then It Has To
Be Fully Automated
<X-word-ms ms=180,159,179,220,300 index=3155 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-17,18-27,28-32>And Number Talking Something Else
<X-word-ms ms=199,199,199,140,139,220 index=3156 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-16,17-19,20-24>So Just Bear With Me Here
So Whenever We See
<X-word-ms ms=39,280,159,279,319 index=3158 character_ranges=0-0,1-7,8-12,13-15,16-19>A Closer Than 20 May
I Completely Disregard
This Talk On
<X-word-ms ms=439,159,120,159,300 index=3161 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-15,16-20>Each As Go About City
<X-word-ms ms=199,139,160,239,199,100 index=3162 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-16,17-19,20-25>Into This Time So In Order
To Consider To See
Another A New
Fresh Leg Of A
Fresh Intermediate Term
Trend So For Example
Right Now This Stock
<X-word-ms ms=119,100,260,199,239,239 index=3169 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-13,14-19,20-25,26-30>That We Traded Right There Came
<X-word-ms ms=239,140,100,119,159,420 index=3170 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-13,14-16,17-20>All The Way To 50 May
Just Like Here And
<X-word-ms ms=259,260,340,99,240 index=3172 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-15,16-21,22-27>Now It's Forming Their First
<X-word-ms ms=259,220,220,260,239 index=3173 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-14,15-17>Lake With Up 80 20
15 Me Stucked Up
On Training I Will
<X-word-ms ms=279,119,319,220,340 index=3176 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-13,14-19,20-23>Have Be Seemly Still Red
<X-word-ms ms=239,239,420,100,79 index=3177 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-17,18-20,21-23>But This Continues To Go
<X-word-ms ms=140,159,500,180,219 index=3178 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-17,18-22>For Life Two Three Days
<X-word-ms ms=260,199,140,140,159,559 index=3179 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-18,19-25,26-34>More And Then Start Moving Sideways
This Will Turn Green
<X-word-ms ms=159,159,300,260,239 index=3181 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-15,16-20>At Some Point So This
<X-word-ms ms=119,260,119,260,139,460 index=3182 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-12,13-15,16-26>Is In The Way Of Developing
<X-word-ms ms=120,259,280,159,79,199 index=3183 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-11,12-15,16-20,21-25>A First Lake I'm When That
Happens Only Had 80
20 50 Amaze
Stucked Up
<X-word-ms ms=180,99,160,79,239,239,460 index=3187 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-14,15-20,21-23,24-32>On The Seam All Green An Eclosion
<X-word-ms ms=220,139,180,359,240 index=3188 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-14,15-18,19-24>About It Twenty May Dance
We'll Show In
<X-word-ms ms=179,280,259,180,60,199 index=3190 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-14,15-17,18-21,22-26>The Breath Scan On The Bull
<X-word-ms ms=300,119,199,79,180,260 index=3191 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-13,14-17,18-20,21-25>Sider So There Are So Many
Stocks Right Now We're
Going To See
<X-word-ms ms=479,199,220,79,60 index=3194 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-17,18-20>That But There Are So
<X-word-ms ms=179,260,119,159,220,140 index=3195 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-16,17-20,21-27,28-32>Many Stocks Right Now Having This
First Lake Forming
Ride Out
<X-word-ms ms=199,159,380,199,100 index=3198 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-13,14-20,21-24>Of Fresh Basis That's Why
<X-word-ms ms=159,220,139,40,179,320 index=3199 character_ranges=0-0,1-9,10-11,12-15,16-18,19-26>I Expected A Lot Of Signals
Breakout Seasons Coming Later
<X-word-ms ms=199,179,240,259,140 index=3201 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-17,18-22>Into The Month And Into
Next Month Expect A
<X-word-ms ms=179,160,239,179,140,119 index=3203 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-13,14-17,18-20,21-25>Lot Of Singles And It Just
Way They Market
Cycle Really Works
<X-word-ms ms=319,260,159,159,120 index=3206 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-16,17-20>Write Is Just The Way
It Is If
<X-word-ms ms=179,100,79,159,420,140 index=3208 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-15,16-22,23-25>You Look At Past Cycles In
What Second Same Internal
To Stock They Just
<X-word-ms ms=239,220,219,220,460 index=3211 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-15,16-19>Move This Way So You
<X-word-ms ms=119,220,279,199,100,239 index=3212 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-15,16-19,20-26>Will See Many Of The Stacks
<X-word-ms ms=199,300,159,300,300 index=3213 character_ranges=0-4,5-11,12-17,18-23,24-28>Being Making These First Lake
Fresh No New
Legs Coming Up From
Corrections Or From Chopping
Faces At Same Time
<X-word-ms ms=500,159,119,120,259 index=3218 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-10,11-15,16-22>Then When A Bull Market
Develop Cds
<X-word-ms ms=519,100,140,159,300 index=3220 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-11,12-16,17-23>All Of These Dogs Really
Get Into The State
And Having Breakouts You
Know In An
Uncorrelated Manner
Every I Know Every
<X-word-ms ms=159,260,119,119,360 index=3226 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-13,14-18,19-26>Single Week We Have Singles
Over The Place
You Know Many Different
<X-word-ms ms=560,180,119,79,340 index=3229 character_ranges=0-6,7-14,15-20,21-23,24-32>Sectors Because There Is Rational
<X-word-ms ms=279,140,59,180,219,240 index=3230 character_ranges=0-7,8-11,12-14,15-19,20-25,26-28>Rotation All Of This Stuff So
But Again
In The
Consolidations Right Here If
<X-word-ms ms=119,59,120,399,239,420 index=3234 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-7,8-14,15-22,23-25>I Have A Closer Between Tm
It's Completely Disregarded
<X-word-ms ms=319,180,199,260,359 index=3236 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-14,15-22,23-29>On The Consider Edition Itself
<X-word-ms ms=520,139,120,59,159,159 index=3237 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-16,17-21,22-26>Once They Kind Of Made High
For The Leg You
Want To Look At
Least Seven Candles
<X-word-ms ms=279,220,199,199,260 index=3241 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-18,19-24>After The High Rate Their
Before The Breakout To
<X-word-ms ms=279,180,219,200,539 index=3243 character_ranges=0-7,8-12,13-18,19-24,25-38>Conceder That First Value Consideration
So A First
Value Consolidations Could Give
<X-word-ms ms=79,100,180,299,260,520 index=3246 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-10,11-13,14-17,18-23>Us A Signal Or Not Right
<X-word-ms ms=239,100,219,159,180,319 index=3247 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-15,16-19,20-29>This One Gave Us But Sometimes
The Correct Incorrect
Seven Candles For
<X-word-ms ms=159,200,159,180,519 index=3250 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-14,15-19,20-23>More After They High And
<X-word-ms ms=159,119,119,160,420,379 index=3251 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-16,17-23,24-31>Then It Just Goes Higher Without
<X-word-ms ms=220,159,60,239,279,180 index=3252 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-10,11-17,18-24,25-29>Giving As A Signal That's Fine
Because These Conditions Were
<X-word-ms ms=180,319,260,159,159 index=3254 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-15,16-19>Not Met There Is Not
That We're Going To
Be Getting Into Every
<X-word-ms ms=300,260,159,139,119,300 index=3257 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-16,17-21,22-24,25-32>Single Stock That Made At Freshly
Of Their 50 I
<X-word-ms ms=219,100,140,259,580 index=3259 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-11,12-19,20-33>Have A Seven Counter Consideration
<X-word-ms ms=319,140,99,180,239,239 index=3260 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-15,16-20,21-23>All Of The Rules Must Be
Met There And
<X-word-ms ms=280,279,140,119,260 index=3262 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-14,15-18>Also We Need To See
A Volatility Contraction
Pattern So This
One Was An Ascending
Triangle With Just Trade
Take Two Type
<X-word-ms ms=180,300,279,199,240 index=3268 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-19,20-26,27-31>Off Trades Obviously You've Seen
<X-word-ms ms=139,260,279,280,279 index=3269 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-17,18-21,22-24>These Every Single Day In
The Server Data Which
<X-word-ms ms=140,199,159,340,320 index=3271 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-14,15-17>Is Say Too Type Of
A Know Or Really
Conservation Patterns
<X-word-ms ms=440,159,139,160,179 index=3274 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-15,16-18>So It's Going To Be
An Ascending
Triangle Obviously Right
An Ascending Triangles
That Has A Flat
You Know Line
Of Resistance And No
Higher Lows There Right
So This Is An
<X-word-ms ms=279,279,159,79,180,100 index=3283 character_ranges=0-8,9-17,18-23,24-27,28-31,32-34>Ascendant Triangle These Are One We
Have Their Also Have
Normal Triangles
Write That We Have
Trend Lines To Trade
From Right It's Very
Simple Stuff With Just
Trade These Two They
<X-word-ms ms=119,360,300,219,420 index=3291 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-14,15-18,19-26>Are Others Like For Example
<X-word-ms ms=420,180,119,220,79 index=3292 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-19,20-23>Flags Or For Example The
<X-word-ms ms=179,120,119,179,420 index=3293 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-16,17-19>Half For You Know We
Have A Leg
Higher And
Then You Have Like
Down Trending
Channel And It Breaks
Out From There I
Liked The Whole Point
<X-word-ms ms=159,140,179,480,739 index=3301 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-15,16-20>Of This Why Just Look
For The Ascending
Triangles On The
Triangle Themselves Is
Very Important Because These
Are Considered
If You Will BCP
<X-word-ms ms=319,380,59,240,359 index=3308 character_ranges=0-0,1-3,4-5,6-15,16-20>B Cp S Something Very
Common Talking In Markets
Made Famous By
Marguer Vini Obviously
Volatility Contraction Pattern
<X-word-ms ms=119,300,240,59,140,119,260 index=3313 character_ranges=0-2,3-14,15-17,18-19,20-24,25-27,28-31>But Essentially If I Have To Sum
<X-word-ms ms=239,260,79,180,119,159 index=3314 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-15,16-20,21-25>Up You Know It's Very Easy
To See What Is
The BCP Action Which
<X-word-ms ms=99,100,180,179,520 index=3317 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-11,12-15,16-18>Has A Higher Low So
<X-word-ms ms=239,220,140,340,119 index=3318 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-10,11-16,17-20>I Know That There Are
Been A Lot Of
Courses Books
Written On Volatility
Construction Patterns But If
<X-word-ms ms=79,79,60,319,220,199,319 index=3323 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-9,10-17,18-22,23-26,27-37>You Have A Defined Area For Assistance
With Momentum
Or Activity Contracting
<X-word-ms ms=500,79,119,199,319 index=3326 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-15,16-19>And You See Just One
Higher Law Right
<X-word-ms ms=480,159,100,159,619 index=3328 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-23,24-36>Here Have All Volatility Contractions
<X-word-ms ms=180,240,299,240,99 index=3329 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-14,15-19>So Right Here I Know
<X-word-ms ms=159,280,59,340,360 index=3330 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-18,19-22>It's Kind Of Simple But
<X-word-ms ms=139,180,99,140,239,159,100 index=3331 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-14,15-19,20-22,23-24>Just The Way Is This Is A
Low Right There And
<X-word-ms ms=159,239,279,300,399 index=3333 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-13,14-17,18-24>Of Course This Was Higher
<X-word-ms ms=460,239,140,100,179 index=3334 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-8,9-12,13-14>Law So If You A
Higher Law Within
<X-word-ms ms=260,119,159,180,679 index=3336 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-11,12-15,16-24>One Of These Two Patterns
About Activity Contracting
You Have BCP Action
<X-word-ms ms=199,99,200,379,360 index=3339 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-16,17-19>In This Show That In
This Case Bulls Are
In Control They
Just Contract In Buying
Dips And Deprize
<X-word-ms ms=160,39,219,520,239 index=3344 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-16,17-20>Is Just Not Going Out
<X-word-ms ms=300,239,199,180,220 index=3345 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-15,16-21>Even Go Into The First
<X-word-ms ms=199,220,279,159,260 index=3346 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-16,17-23>Slow But You Know Having
This Higher Step Information
<X-word-ms ms=219,140,20,139,440,139 index=3348 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-17,18-27,28-31>That They Are Just Absorbing The
<X-word-ms ms=380,119,159,80,139,119,100 index=3349 character_ranges=0-6,7-10,11-17,18-22,23-25,26-30,31-32>Cellars And That's When We Have A
Breakout These
<X-word-ms ms=240,139,340,199,200 index=3351 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-12,13-16,17-21>App Of Action Has Much
Higher Probability For
Working Than This
One Right There
Is Very Cool Book
<X-word-ms ms=319,159,260,220,380 index=3356 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-15,16-19,20-22>That It'S Called How To
Help To Reach Aren't
<X-word-ms ms=140,219,280,219,200 index=3358 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-17,18-20>How Too Use Charge So
<X-word-ms ms=79,199,99,80,239,199,159 index=3359 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-16,17-23,24-25,26-30>Many Money In The Summer I Have
The Triangles That
Are Low Volatility
And These Are The
<X-word-ms ms=60,199,480,259,180 index=3363 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-15,16-20,21-24>Most Higher Lows This One
Is Down Trending Channels
And Even Worse Ones
Are Volatile Are
The Lowest Success
Rate To Take
You Know Momentum
<X-word-ms ms=39,80,239,479,159,80 index=3370 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-12,13-22,23-25,26-29>In A Bolarity Expansion To The
<X-word-ms ms=159,279,319,240,179 index=3371 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-14,15-21,22-31>Upper Side With Moment Obviously
Right I Have
This Below Success So
Again This
<X-word-ms ms=180,319,159,240,519 index=3375 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-17,18-20>Goes Down To Focus On
A Very
Specific Point
<X-word-ms ms=280,139,240,339,119 index=3378 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-17,18-20>Of The Trend Cycle Of
<X-word-ms ms=100,220,230,159,79,180,420 index=3379 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-11,12-14,15-18,19-24,25-30>A Stock This Is The Trend Cycle
Remember First Like Higher
First Value Consideration
Second Leg Then
<X-word-ms ms=159,79,100,99,159,220,279 index=3383 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-12,13-18,19-24,25-33>If You Have A Third Level Whatever
<X-word-ms ms=280,119,119,180,579 index=3384 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-15,16-22>It's Going To Be Choppy
Volatile Depending On Market
Phase And On
<X-word-ms ms=139,220,180,220,139,140 index=3387 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-14,15-20,21-26,27-29>Their Bear Side We're Going To
See Our First Crack
Know I First Cracking
<X-word-ms ms=140,259,300,140,340 index=3390 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-15,16-18,19-26>They Lower First By Concern
Edition Secondly Which
<X-word-ms ms=119,100,300,319,260 index=3392 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-15,16-20>Is The Flush All Fear
Was Counted In Into
That Contraction One We
<X-word-ms ms=199,260,119,239,300 index=3395 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-10,11-17,18-21>Just Need A Higher Low
<X-word-ms ms=220,99,100,100,139,220,239 index=3396 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-11,12-17,18-22,23-26>It Will Be A Lower High For
<X-word-ms ms=79,180,239,220,140,119,399 index=3397 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-19,20-22,23-27,28-33>The Short Side Right If This Makes
Sense So Want
<X-word-ms ms=480,119,79,239,199 index=3399 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-7,8-14,15-19>To See A Higher Load
Building Up Obviously These
Is BCP
Action Is Exactly What
<X-word-ms ms=99,160,159,340,319 index=3403 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-9,10-15,16-19>I Show You Right Now
No Daily Close With
<X-word-ms ms=79,159,360,239,139,140 index=3405 character_ranges=0-1,2-9,10-13,14-18,19-21,22-26>Or Between TMA This Is Very
Important Thing That
<X-word-ms ms=240,139,220,79,340 index=3407 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-12,13-18>If You Have A Close
Below 20 May And
Completely Disregard Stock
So They Are
In Trading You
<X-word-ms ms=119,100,299,340,180 index=3412 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-17,18-22,23-28>Have To Understand That Every
<X-word-ms ms=199,300,279,180,279,539 index=3413 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-12,13-17,18-20,21-24>Single Day We Have 10,000
<X-word-ms ms=140,559,60,139,100,640 index=3414 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-13,14-17,18-21,22-33>New Stocks And You Can Potentially
<X-word-ms ms=359,159,79,180,479 index=3415 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-16,17-22>Trade If You Want Right
<X-word-ms ms=279,119,79,159,500 index=3416 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-7,8-9,10-16>So It Is A Narrow
Things Down As Much
As Possible The
Fewer Number Of More
You Make With The
Fewer Trades
Better More
Durable More Robust
System Really Is I
<X-word-ms ms=279,100,279,199,180 index=3425 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-15,16-21,22-24>Am Just Focusing Again On
Second Leg Now Don't
<X-word-ms ms=239,180,199,220,140,259 index=3427 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-15,16-18,19-25,26-29>Care About Third Or Fourth Leg
<X-word-ms ms=200,479,199,100,140 index=3428 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-16,17-19>Right Even If You Go
<X-word-ms ms=139,340,119,260,100,179 index=3429 character_ranges=0-6,7-13,14-18,19-23,24-27,28-35>Through Cycles That They Are Working
<X-word-ms ms=239,440,159,140,159 index=3430 character_ranges=0-5,6-12,13-14,15-20,21-25>Really Nicely I Don't Care
<X-word-ms ms=220,500,159,119,119 index=3431 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-10,11-15,16-18>Just I Just Want My
<X-word-ms ms=239,180,199,220,159,140 index=3432 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-15,16-18,19-21>Edge To Play Out It Is
<X-word-ms ms=179,159,240,380,139 index=3433 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-20,21-25>One Of The Objectives From
<X-word-ms ms=239,180,279,220,119 index=3434 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-14,15-20,21-23>Off Mine System Which Is
Beating In This
Is With Lower Drawdown
Having Consistency
Of Profits Made
<X-word-ms ms=159,260,239,200,420 index=3439 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-15,16-16>Up Make Over 100%
<X-word-ms ms=199,199,220,199,359 index=3440 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-14,15-17,18-25>Return Per Year On Average
And Just Write
Three Cyles And
Grow Money I
Don't Care About Anything
Else Really Right That's
<X-word-ms ms=99,119,60,119,199,239,240 index=3446 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-8,9-14,15-21,22-26,27-29>What I Do Every Single Year So
<X-word-ms ms=399,200,79,239,199 index=3447 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-10,11-14,15-17>I Don'T Get Mad At
<X-word-ms ms=199,300,140,159,100,159 index=3448 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-13,14-19,20-26>All This Was A Close Better
Return Tma And
<X-word-ms ms=140,219,300,180,239 index=3450 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-13,14-15,16-20>Going To Disre I Mean
<X-word-ms ms=560,119,159,159,159 index=3451 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-17,18-21>I'm Going To Still Use
<X-word-ms ms=119,199,160,399,220 index=3452 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-12,13-15,16-20>The Stock Now It Just
<X-word-ms ms=199,240,159,239,260 index=3453 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-10,11-16,17-21>Went Out Of There With
The Parameters I Jump
<X-word-ms ms=140,239,199,200,199,119 index=3455 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-15,16-20,21-24>On Just Going To Wait For
Volatility Subside
If You Know
Regroups Like
<X-word-ms ms=199,159,200,119,159,319 index=3459 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-14,15-16,17-20,21-26>These Are Makes A New Decay
<X-word-ms ms=119,100,119,340,199,539 index=3460 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-8,9-14,15-17,18-25>Or I Just Trade My Signals
<X-word-ms ms=100,159,279,140,59,300 index=3461 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-16,17-19,20-24>And Just Trade In My Edge
An Exploit
<X-word-ms ms=199,220,159,140,159,180 index=3463 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-7,8-13,14-18,19-21>My Age I Don't Care If
This Is A
<X-word-ms ms=400,219,260,100,139 index=3465 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-14,15-18>Rate Of It's An Oil
<X-word-ms ms=200,359,260,119,99 index=3466 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-13,14-18>Gas Name Or It Says
MDK Or Its
<X-word-ms ms=160,379,180,79,560 index=3468 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-14,15-20>No Tesla In The 2020s
I Don'T Care I
<X-word-ms ms=199,280,119,119,119,199 index=3470 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-18,19-22,23-29>Just Tried You Know The Scenes
Are Pop Up Because
<X-word-ms ms=220,199,279,239,79 index=3472 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-14,15-17,18-19>I'm Doing These In A
Quantitative Manner
<X-word-ms ms=319,159,119,360,319 index=3474 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-9,10-21,22-27>It'S Not A Qualitative Thing
<X-word-ms ms=279,120,239,220,379 index=3475 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-14,15-18,19-22>I'm Not Looking For The
Stocks Like My Trade
Or Pops Up In
My Scan Meets The
Criteria Has An Edge
<X-word-ms ms=179,100,220,159,220,229 index=3480 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-8,9-13,14-18,19-23>If I Take This Rate Over
<X-word-ms ms=160,179,220,319,280 index=3481 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-13,14-20,21-25>A Large Series Sample Size
<X-word-ms ms=219,140,260,179,220 index=3482 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-16,17-20,21-27>And Going Through Two Market
Phases At Least That
Really Defines Distribution
<X-word-ms ms=230,119,119,100,59,440 index=3485 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-13,14-17,18-24>We Want To See Our Profit
It'S Nothing More Than
Them Mean Is Kind
Of Simple Its Kinda
You Know Boring
But It's Robust
It'S Profitable Repeatable
<X-word-ms ms=199,239,159,400,199 index=3492 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-13,14-21,22-28>And That's How Trading Should
Really Be That'S The
Thing Train Shouldn't
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,259,200,639 index=3495 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-13,14-16,17-26>Not Should Not Be Something
That You Enjoy
<X-word-ms ms=340,119,160,119,119,139,120 index=3497 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-12,13-17,18-20,21-24>If You Will I Know We All
Love Training Obviously But
At The Act Of
<X-word-ms ms=99,460,220,140,139 index=3500 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-18,19-22,23-25>Free Trading Should Not Be
Something Joyful They
<X-word-ms ms=220,199,159,79,260,339 index=3502 character_ranges=0-8,9-12,13-21,22-24,25-32,33-41>Shouldn'T You Shouldn' Be Fitting Anything
For That Matter Right
<X-word-ms ms=440,139,180,180,619 index=3504 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-18,19-27>Any Type Of Feeling Feelings
On Both Extrems
<X-word-ms ms=100,140,159,439,200 index=3506 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-16,17-21>Are Going To Hurt Your
Returns Hurt Yourself
So This
Is The Way That
We Approach Stuff
<X-word-ms ms=399,200,139,119,200 index=3511 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-12,13-16,17-22>And Again You Can Build
Other Systems Yes Sure
But I'M Very
<X-word-ms ms=480,119,159,79,180 index=3514 character_ranges=0-8,9-11,12-16,17-18,19-21>Selective On What I Do
Because I Know Repeatedly
That Data Gives Me
An Edge So
A Defined
Resistance Level Of
<X-word-ms ms=519,100,140,239,180 index=3520 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-18,19-23>Trend Line To Trade With
<X-word-ms ms=299,260,159,100,119,479 index=3521 character_ranges=0-4,5-6,7-11,12-13,14-18,19-27>Again I Have A Very Specific
Way To Draw Trend
Lines To Draw Horizontal
Lines With Specific
Swinging Points I Don't
Draw Although They Look
Like Handheld And Just
Do It Like That
There Is
A Very Specific Way
To Draw Trend Lines
<X-word-ms ms=100,140,179,380,180,359 index=3532 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-10,11-17,18-23,24-34>Of Course I Cannot Share Everything
Absolutely Here These
Are Things For The
<X-word-ms ms=500,140,180,139,180 index=3535 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-16,17-20,21-25>Mentees Or People Who Have
This System Trying
Obviously Protect The
<X-word-ms ms=220,119,119,200,179,420 index=3538 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-15,16-18,19-23,24-27>System And Going To Make The
<X-word-ms ms=119,199,320,319,159 index=3539 character_ranges=0-4,5-11,12-18,19-22,23-28>Whole System Public But Again
If You Take Everything
<X-word-ms ms=360,260,259,119,300 index=3541 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-15,16-19,20-22>Sharing Here You Can Go
Back On Data You
Can Study Stocks Come
<X-word-ms ms=380,159,100,139,140,140 index=3544 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-8,9-12,13-15,16-18>Up With A Way To Do
<X-word-ms ms=79,220,159,119,119,420 index=3545 character_ranges=0-1,2-10,11-13,14-17,18-22,23-34>It Yourself Is Not That Complicated
Anyways But The
Foundations I Am Just
<X-word-ms ms=199,140,79,199,159,239 index=3548 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-11,12-14,15-18,19-27>Giving It So We Can Actually
<X-word-ms ms=300,119,140,319,159 index=3549 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-16,17-19>Put In Our Twists On
This Stuff You Can
Add Some Of
Your Own Salt Or
<X-word-ms ms=260,260,99,200,219 index=3553 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-12,13-17,18-20>Pepper If You Will To
The System That Lines
<X-word-ms ms=119,140,119,380,229,180 index=3555 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-23,24-27,28-33>Up With Your Personality And Build
Something Out Because The
Principle Is
Same Its Volatility
Contraction And Expansion
With Momentum In
<X-word-ms ms=359,60,159,359,240 index=3561 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-13,14-19,20-24>Stocks It Just Works This
<X-word-ms ms=219,140,140,220,440 index=3562 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-16,17-22>Way You Can Enter Every
Single Breakout Put A
Like Two ATR Stop
<X-word-ms ms=359,199,199,220,220 index=3565 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-15,16-19>And Put Like Fix One
<X-word-ms ms=179,240,319,159,239 index=3566 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-16,17-22>To One Maybe That Works
<X-word-ms ms=160,19,140,279,100,219,180 index=3567 character_ranges=0-0,1-3,4-8,9-17,18-21,22-31,32-34>I Am Just Throwing Out Something Of
<X-word-ms ms=220,220,260,220,519 index=3568 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-17,18-23>The Hand Right But There
<X-word-ms ms=39,140,260,99,100,79,199,159 index=3569 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-17,18-21,22-25,26-30,31-35>Are Many Ways That You Can Take This
Information This Way
That Stacks Really Move
<X-word-ms ms=260,119,399,160,380 index=3572 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-14,15-27>On The Cycle In Relationship
<X-word-ms ms=199,219,100,140,500 index=3573 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-17,18-23>Also To The Weekly Cycle
<X-word-ms ms=119,239,199,159,180,239 index=3574 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-17,18-23,24-26>And Build Your Own Stuff Or
From Here Built
If You Build Something
Off From This Information
<X-word-ms ms=260,79,260,279,300 index=3578 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-15,16-25,26-30>You Are Building Something That
<X-word-ms ms=140,159,180,359,840 index=3579 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-10,11-18,19-31>Has An Edge Because Structurally
<X-word-ms ms=260,219,180,140,299 index=3580 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-14,15-19,20-25>It Is Something That Works
<X-word-ms ms=520,260,159,60,119 index=3581 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-13,14-17>Then To Have A Net
<X-word-ms ms=199,140,159,260,139,140 index=3582 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-16,17-22,23-26>You Have To Build Their Own
Rules Your Exposure Rules
<X-word-ms ms=159,220,219,220,199 index=3584 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-16,17-27>Or Risk Rules And Everything
Really Works
Together Remember If You
Modify One
Single Element Of
<X-word-ms ms=279,260,159,119,520 index=3589 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-14,15-17,18-24>System Is Going To Affect
The Whole Not
Just One Thing Even
<X-word-ms ms=220,100,99,140,140,139,500 index=3592 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-14,15-17,18-22,23-35>If You Start To Do This Frankenstein
<X-word-ms ms=380,239,120,179,300 index=3593 character_ranges=0-6,7-12,13-15,16-24,25-31>Systems Which Is Starting Adding
Things From Other People
Then Really
Come Out Together And
<X-word-ms ms=179,140,100,239,279,500 index=3597 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-7,8-13,14-17,18-22>See As A Whole How That
Looks And Make
Modifications To Control
<X-word-ms ms=260,119,359,239,240 index=3600 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-14,15-17,18-22>The Equity Core To Your
Will Have A
<X-word-ms ms=380,199,79,340,279 index=3602 character_ranges=0-11,12-16,17-19,20-26,27-30>Distribution That We Accept And
<X-word-ms ms=159,340,199,260,180 index=3603 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-15,16-20>Can Trade With I Want
<X-word-ms ms=119,220,199,239,340 index=3604 character_ranges=0-1,2-9,10-12,13-17,18-25>To Discuss In Next Session
Probably But It
<X-word-ms ms=139,340,260,119,119,159 index=3606 character_ranges=0-1,2-9,10-13,14-17,18-20,21-24>Is Exactly The Way Of The
Right Here You
<X-word-ms ms=180,99,120,279,359 index=3608 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-9,10-18,19-26>Look For A Breakout Candles
<X-word-ms ms=140,159,159,119,180,500 index=3609 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-12,13-19,20-26>Want To See A Strong Candle
<X-word-ms ms=260,139,300,140,119,119 index=3610 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-14,15-18,19-24>With No Weak On The Upper
<X-word-ms ms=260,279,159,159,119,140 index=3611 character_ranges=0-3,4-13,14-17,18-21,22-26,27-29>Side Obviously Not Too Much Of
A Week Breaking
And Closing Through Resistance
Having One Or Two
Three Ty Cannons
Before Them Better It
<X-word-ms ms=199,319,199,60,119,159 index=3617 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-13,14-16,17-20,21-27>Is They Bought Up The Candel
<X-word-ms ms=119,180,300,199,140,139,0 index=3618 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-13,14-18,19-22,23-26,27-27>Must Be Higher Than The Pre-
<X-word-ms ms=140,359,200,279,159 index=3619 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-13,14-21,22-29>State Candl If There's Another
Rule But Talk
<X-word-ms ms=139,240,79,119,239,479 index=3621 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-15,16-20,21-28>About It All The Time Another
Thing The
Way To Measure A
Week On Breakout
I Put
<X-word-ms ms=159,159,180,179,300,220 index=3626 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-13,14-16,17-21,22-25>In The Channel At Time You
Take The Financial Levels
<X-word-ms ms=119,199,180,260,480 index=3628 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-16,17-19>From High Too Low On
The Range Of Candles
So You Have This
0.786 Level
<X-word-ms ms=300,159,179,220,480 index=3632 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-14,15-19>Is Your Point 7 Zero
<X-word-ms ms=239,159,159,239,400 index=3633 character_ranges=0-5,6-7,8-9,10-11,12-17>Points 6 1 8 These
Are Limits Where Deprived
Because Higher Sometimes
Above 0.76
<X-word-ms ms=240,239,300,159,199 index=3637 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-6,7-9,10-15>But 80% Of Times
Would Say This
Year 0.786 Or
<X-word-ms ms=159,260,260,180,199 index=3640 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-16,17-22,23-25>Zero Point Center Going To
<X-word-ms ms=99,159,200,59,140,140,219 index=3641 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-14,15-20,21-23,24-26>Be The Ones Are Going To Be
<X-word-ms ms=199,359,220,140,239 index=3642 character_ranges=0-6,7-10,11-13,14-19,20-23>Looking For In Order Too
<X-word-ms ms=199,159,60,180,299,240 index=3643 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-16,17-22,23-26>They Kind Of Took Close But
<X-word-ms ms=119,119,179,399,159,220 index=3644 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-16,17-19,20-23>You Need To Check It Out
<X-word-ms ms=479,140,119,180,239 index=3645 character_ranges=0-4,5-6,7-13,14-17,18-21>Sumar A Little Bit Put
Into Putting Two Contents
<X-word-ms ms=140,199,199,279,420 index=3647 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-14,15-18,19-27>Off Course This Can Discount
<X-word-ms ms=119,280,179,300,239 index=3648 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-19,20-24>Was Very Very Strong Once
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,199,199,200,119 index=3649 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-13,14-18,19-22>We Took It And This Was
<X-word-ms ms=159,199,480,139,79 index=3650 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-13,14-17>Do Know What I Was
Saying About So
Being Linear Am Been
Non Volatile From Trend
<X-word-ms ms=279,39,180,99,240,839 index=3654 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-14,15-19,20-25>You Can See How This Price
<X-word-ms ms=400,279,140,139,260 index=3655 character_ranges=0-5,6-11,12-14,15-20,21-26>Really Moves It Right Above
The 80 May With
<X-word-ms ms=179,200,299,320,179 index=3657 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-18,19-22,23-28>Very Low Volatility The Range
<X-word-ms ms=100,140,119,79,159,159,119,159 index=3658 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-14,15-20,21-23,24-26,27-32>Of They Kind Of Stand To Be Kinda
Small And
<X-word-ms ms=159,159,159,420,160 index=3660 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-20,21-23>They Just Go Linearly Go
Up And Think Its
Very Similar Another
<X-word-ms ms=319,220,59,159,160,399 index=3663 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-19,20-22,23-30>Thing That We Should Be Looking
<X-word-ms ms=319,160,279,239,100 index=3664 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-14,15-17,18-20>Into New Cities If Is
<X-word-ms ms=179,260,220,279,180 index=3665 character_ranges=0-4,5-14,15-17,18-24,25-27>Study Thousands Of Traits Is
That The Second Leg
Tends To Have Similar
Personality To The Log
<X-word-ms ms=319,260,159,140,219 index=3669 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-19,20-23>So That Is Something You
Can Really See And
Check Into The
<X-word-ms ms=279,140,99,140,59,560 index=3672 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-14,15-18,19-21,22-28>Charts And Will See It Pretty
Well On
Trade Management Side
Of Things I
<X-word-ms ms=259,140,199,199,320 index=3676 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-6,7-10,11-16>Risk 1% Per Trait
<X-word-ms ms=279,239,119,260,359 index=3677 character_ranges=0-3,4-12,13-15,16-20,21-30>From Entering To Stop Obviously
<X-word-ms ms=480,220,119,179,140 index=3678 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-16,17-19>Your Place Or Top At
<X-word-ms ms=100,119,159,340,420 index=3679 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-14,15-20>The Low Day For Lungs
<X-word-ms ms=219,180,140,219,240,479 index=3680 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-18,19-23,24-30>Are They Have Today Four Shorts
Every Person Portray
Did This Question All
Time Why Not Rease
Zero One Point Two
<X-word-ms ms=239,140,139,280,159,119 index=3685 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-16,17-23,24-29>Or One Point Five You're Going
<X-word-ms ms=100,139,159,440,220 index=3686 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-17,18-23>To Make More Money Makes
Sense It's Logical
In Fact If
We Would Have More
Leverage You
Know Sometimes Not Now
<X-word-ms ms=300,139,60,180,139,60,260 index=3692 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-14,15-16,17-21,22-30>But In The Past I Will Probably
<X-word-ms ms=219,200,220,159,279 index=3693 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-13,14-21>Do That By The Problem
Is Start With
Stocks We Don't
<X-word-ms ms=79,159,220,519,260 index=3696 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-20,21-23>Have That Much Margin To
<X-word-ms ms=220,199,260,180,119,399 index=3697 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-16,17-18,19-26>Work With Its Not A Futures
Is Not Options We
Have This Rective
<X-word-ms ms=239,220,140,159,279 index=3700 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-13,14-20>Or You Know Us People
<X-word-ms ms=199,119,200,419,300 index=3701 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-22,23-30>And Even With Portfolio Marging
<X-word-ms ms=79,119,140,199,240,339 index=3702 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-18,19-23,24-28>You Don't Have That Much Room
<X-word-ms ms=240,239,240,199,260 index=3703 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-7,8-11,12-17>To Go In The Sense
That Sometimes We
<X-word-ms ms=159,199,280,239,159 index=3705 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-11,12-16,17-19>Have A Great Wave Of
Signals But All Them
<X-word-ms ms=239,279,140,179,240 index=3707 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-12,13-13>Are Like At 2%
<X-word-ms ms=359,260,99,180,359 index=3708 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-15,16-17>Stop And You Put 3
<X-word-ms ms=479,200,139,159,300 index=3709 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-11,12-15,16-18>Signal So Me How We
<X-word-ms ms=79,420,100,260,759 index=3710 character_ranges=0-2,3-10,11-13,14-17,18-25>Are Exposed By 150 Percent
They Were Way
<X-word-ms ms=179,100,159,479,239 index=3712 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-15,16-19>To Make Money So You
<X-word-ms ms=100,239,340,239,119 index=3713 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-15,16-19>Can Risk More On The
Lower ADR Stocks
<X-word-ms ms=119,180,159,399,360 index=3715 character_ranges=0-6,7-10,11-16,17-20,21-26>Because The Lower Adr Stalk
<X-word-ms ms=340,159,219,200,339 index=3716 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-12,13-19,20-23>I'm Sorry The Higher Adr
Stock Percentage You
<X-word-ms ms=139,180,159,460,340 index=3718 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-19,20-24>Are Going To Require Less
Capital Of Your
Own Money Off Margin
So Have The Same
<X-word-ms ms=179,220,180,139,260,460 index=3722 character_ranges=0-0,1-1,2-6,7-10,11-16,17-19>1% Risk Per Trade On
Any Given Trader And
No Funny Thing Those
<X-word-ms ms=119,180,199,79,180,239,420 index=3725 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-16,17-20,21-25,26-34>Are The Ones That Are Most Volatile
<X-word-ms ms=219,320,179,220,180 index=3726 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-18,19-23>Then When They Move Them
<X-word-ms ms=139,80,259,220,319 index=3727 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-15,16-20>All The Most And Make
More Money It's
Really Way Is But
In One Person
<X-word-ms ms=220,399,180,140,199 index=3731 character_ranges=0-5,6-12,13-17,18-19,20-25>Risper Trails Just A Sweet
Spot For Me I
<X-word-ms ms=359,119,279,220,239 index=3733 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-14,15-19,20-22>Wouldn Go Above That By
Any Means And If
<X-word-ms ms=399,160,99,199,180 index=3735 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-17,18-20>You Want To Change It
<X-word-ms ms=100,79,239,119,100,179,200 index=3736 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-9,10-13,14-18,19-21,22-24>I Would If You Have To Go
<X-word-ms ms=339,180,119,100,420 index=3737 character_ranges=0-4,5-6,7-11,12-14,15-20>Lower I Will Go Lower
0.5 As
Your Point 3 Is
<X-word-ms ms=319,159,160,179,79,260 index=3740 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-15,16-22,23-30>Great As Well If You're Trading
<X-word-ms ms=140,139,140,300,179,160 index=3741 character_ranges=0-0,1-7,8-10,11-18,19-20,21-25>A Couple Of Million I Want
To Have Very
Low Drawdown You Can
<X-word-ms ms=200,159,79,199,340,260 index=3744 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-12,13-20,21-22>Do The Add No Problem I
Mean For Sure And
If You Are Running
<X-word-ms ms=199,240,139,199,340 index=3747 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-15,16-21,22-29>This System With Other Systems
As Well If
<X-word-ms ms=99,140,140,359,119,500 index=3749 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-9,10-10,11-13,14-17>You Risk 1% Or You
<X-word-ms ms=360,79,220,139,100,59,60 index=3750 character_ranges=0-4,5-6,7-12,13-15,16-19,20-23,24-26>Close A Trade At The End Of
50 If You
Weren't Stopped Out At
This Top Level Or
The Procurement Level Is
The Tree Open In
The Fifty You Close
<X-word-ms ms=219,140,220,139,159,420 index=3757 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-17,18-20,21-25>It And Again There So Much
Going On Closing
<X-word-ms ms=159,39,79,100,119,239,240,500 index=3759 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-12,13-16,17-22,23-26,27-30>At The End Of The Fifth Day For
Exam Even
If You Trail
Here So If
<X-word-ms ms=139,220,279,250,220 index=3763 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-13,14-18,19-22>We Enter Their Your Put
<X-word-ms ms=119,280,279,139,160,239 index=3764 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-17,18-22,23-27>The Stop Just Like With Data
Deload Today Day Right
There And You Write
For Five Days It's
<X-word-ms ms=220,259,240,219,220 index=3768 character_ranges=0-8,9-15,16-21,22-24,25-28>Somewhere Around Their So Its
<X-word-ms ms=220,179,260,199,180 index=3769 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-9,10-15,16-21>Like A Two Point Eight
<X-word-ms ms=159,159,79,260,239,160 index=3770 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-11,12-19,20-23,24-26>I Don't Know Exactly How He
<X-word-ms ms=179,119,120,159,99,180,460 index=3771 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-14,15-17,18-19,20-21>Was But Is Like At 2.8
Our Trade So If
<X-word-ms ms=139,100,139,420,210 index=3773 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-18,19-21>Your Is One Percent Is
<X-word-ms ms=80,179,180,260,219,180 index=3774 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-7,8-8,9-11,12-14>To Put 8% In On
<X-word-ms ms=159,300,100,179,199,40,299 index=3775 character_ranges=0-2,3-10,11-13,14-20,21-24,25-27,28-33>The Trailer By Future Try To Trail
Lead I Don'
<X-word-ms ms=40,159,119,460,219,200 index=3777 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-16,17-21,22-25>Know If You Write This Top
<X-word-ms ms=199,239,79,380,579 index=3778 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-17,18-20>Rate They Are Only 80
<X-word-ms ms=319,420,119,139,99 index=3779 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-14,15-17,18-22>May We're Going To Have
The Same Result
<X-word-ms ms=399,260,100,159,119 index=3781 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-13,14-18>And If You Try With
<X-word-ms ms=99,260,239,140,119,140,159 index=3782 character_ranges=0-0,1-3,4-6,7-12,13-15,16-19,20-24>A 20 Or Going To Get Even
Worse So As
<X-word-ms ms=159,520,220,99,279 index=3784 character_ranges=0-3,4-12,13-15,16-17,18-22>Well Trailing As I Said
Works Really Well
When It Just Enter
<X-word-ms ms=159,220,139,140,720 index=3787 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-17,18-24>This Stock In Just Shoots
Up Massively And
Doesn't Look Back Like
Its Indicate For Example
Is Indicated
We Trade By The
<X-word-ms ms=139,119,119,100,180,279,220 index=3793 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-14,15-17,18-26,27-30>Way Isn That He Is Breaking Out
<X-word-ms ms=179,260,260,239,199 index=3794 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-14,15-19,20-25>From Multi Week Base Right
<X-word-ms ms=220,560,79,139,180 index=3795 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-15,16-19>Now Needs On His Way
<X-word-ms ms=180,279,140,239,239 index=3796 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-9,10-15,16-19>To Build A First Leg
Of Fresh New
Trend So I
Believe We Trade This
Indicate Down Here
It Was And Which
Rated These One Building
What Is Where This
<X-word-ms ms=259,240,239,199,319 index=3804 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-16,17-21>Thing Was That We Made
<X-word-ms ms=200,119,179,240,479 index=3805 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-11,12-16,17-23>Like A Break Even Trader
Can Really Ability With
<X-word-ms ms=160,239,239,180,59,119,200 index=3807 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-16,17-19,20-23,24-29>Us Right Yeah But He Was Right
<X-word-ms ms=279,159,119,199,660 index=3808 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-15,16-18>Here On This Day We
Enter On This
Days In Decay
34 Yeah Are
Exited There Obvious
Was Like Nothing Trade
And Then Since
We Close The Trader
<X-word-ms ms=400,179,159,140,319 index=3816 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-13,14-18,19-24>It Just Should Have Hired
<X-word-ms ms=200,319,140,199,239 index=3817 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-16,17-19>And Moved This So If
You Were To Trail
These One You
<X-word-ms ms=140,180,179,200,99,279 index=3820 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-15,16-17,18-22>Will Be Out With A Nice
Multi Don't
<X-word-ms ms=140,139,100,380,59,240 index=3822 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-18,19-21,22-30>Want To Take Profit Or Whatever
<X-word-ms ms=579,99,79,60,239 index=3823 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-9,10-12,13-23>But I Have To Understand
That This Is Not
Common Not Only Start
<X-word-ms ms=220,159,140,380,460 index=3826 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-14,15-22>Come On By Your Capital
Would Tied Into
Disposition And
<X-word-ms ms=140,140,99,160,139,119,180,239 index=3829 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-14,15-17,18-22,23-26,27-31>You Won Be Able To Take New Once
So It Kind Of
Goes Against The Principle
<X-word-ms ms=119,180,260,199,140,579 index=3832 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-15,16-19,20-26,27-35>Of Swing Trading Off Really Rotating
Capital Because Want To
Rotate Capital In
Order To See
I
<X-word-ms ms=289,219,289,200,159 index=3837 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-16,17-21,22-28>Believe That Yeah When Almost
Changing This Screen And
Wasn't Changing Everything
Let Me Just Share
<X-word-ms ms=140,119,260,359,289 index=3841 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-14,15-19,20-25>My Whole Screen Here There
So Was Talking About
You Know These Rules
Here Annotated Stuff
Are Not Much But
A Little You
<X-word-ms ms=140,220,340,239,319 index=3847 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-17,18-24,25-27>Were Seeing Trader Beyond By
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,140,199,159,119,159 index=3848 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-15,16-19,20-24,25-27,28-35>Don't Worry Just The Same Is Because
It's Right Here So
The Point Start Right
Here Doesn't Work
Always The Same I
Mean You Always Want
To Do In
<X-word-ms ms=180,180,179,120,99,100,79,99 index=3855 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-15,16-19,20-23,24-26,27-30>That Be Close At The End Of The
Fifth Day Really Gives
<X-word-ms ms=79,119,199,260,199,320 index=3857 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-14,15-18,19-24>You The Best Of All Words
<X-word-ms ms=259,180,159,280,119,159 index=3858 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-8,9-15,16-19,20-24>And I Can Assure You That
If Your Trail
<X-word-ms ms=180,20,139,180,119,119,220,340 index=3860 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-18,19-20,21-24,25-30,31-33>They Are Going Make A Lot Money In
Certain Years But There
<X-word-ms ms=179,140,180,260,279 index=3862 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-14,15-18>Rest Of Time Or Not
So I Prefer To
Even Out Things If
<X-word-ms ms=140,19,420,340,239 index=3865 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-14,15-17,18-24>You Are Trading To Really
Leave Off Training Or
Grow Your Capital Consistently
Because Humans
We Like Consistency
We Don't Like If
<X-word-ms ms=119,239,159,239,640 index=3871 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-9,10-14,15-17>I Told You What Do
You Prefer The Exact
<X-word-ms ms=420,180,159,119,399 index=3873 character_ranges=0-6,7-12,13-16,17-19,20-22>Numbers Right But It Is
<X-word-ms ms=119,220,260,399,320 index=3874 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-12,13-17>You Make 200% This
Year And Then
10 Percent For
That Rest Of Five
Years Would Be Like
<X-word-ms ms=289,460,140,79,159 index=3880 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-13,14-17,18-22>Every Year For The Past
<X-word-ms ms=180,259,159,340,200 index=3881 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-8,9-13,14-22>5 Years I Know Probably
<X-word-ms ms=239,159,119,119,260,220 index=3882 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-18,19-28,29-32>It's More Than That Obviously But
<X-word-ms ms=199,220,299,240,219 index=3883 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-15,16-21>You Get My Point Right
I'm Not Good With
<X-word-ms ms=439,180,119,180,439 index=3885 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-14,15-18>Math On The Fly But
<X-word-ms ms=159,120,299,240,179,220 index=3886 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-13,14-16,17-23,24-26>Again My Point Is Better To
Even Now Distribute
Evenly Their Returns
Over Time And Have
A Consistently All
Profitable Years Beating
<X-word-ms ms=219,260,220,260,199 index=3892 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-14,15-19>In This Is Then Just
Having One Big Spike
In 1 Year Because
<X-word-ms ms=159,119,279,260,220 index=3895 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-12,13-18,19-21>Of The Market Phase At
<X-word-ms ms=119,99,180,340,140,139 index=3896 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-14,15-22,23-25,26-31>Its Kind Random Because We Never
<X-word-ms ms=220,119,199,79,100,180,219 index=3897 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-14,15-17,18-21,22-26,27-33>Know When Going To Get This Market
<X-word-ms ms=260,440,139,119,140 index=3898 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-18,19-22>Phase And Then Have The
<X-word-ms ms=100,119,259,260,260,359 index=3899 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-21,22-26,27-36>Rest Of Years Probably Even Sometimes
Underperforming The
Index Is Not Something
That As
Humans Really Like
<X-word-ms ms=199,220,279,140,159,239 index=3904 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-14,15-19,20-23,24-28>That Some Thing That You It's
<X-word-ms ms=140,179,200,179,280,139 index=3905 character_ranges=0-8,9-11,12-16,17-19,20-27,28-30>Something We Need To Address On
Discuss So
This More Or
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,100,399,479 index=3908 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-18,19-23>Less What Are Doing This
Is Exactly Know The
Overview Off The
Signal Can See
That Its Very Might
Sound Simple Which
It Is On Purpose
But It'S Profitable It'S
Repeatable Its Boring
<X-word-ms ms=279,100,159,359,280 index=3917 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-12,13-22,23-27>Profit Of All Efficient That
<X-word-ms ms=119,199,260,259,300 index=3918 character_ranges=0-1,2-9,10-13,14-21,22-28>Is Exactly How Trading Should
Really Be If
<X-word-ms ms=119,119,239,260,260,359 index=3920 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-16,17-23,24-27>You Start To Miss Around Too
Much Going Try Day
And Stuff I
<X-word-ms ms=260,239,220,180,359 index=3923 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-16,17-21>Found This In Out From
<X-word-ms ms=239,180,239,239,380 index=3924 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-11,12-18,19-24>All My Years Really Doing
System Development That
The Simpler
Things Are The More
Easier These
<X-word-ms ms=199,140,159,119,140,260 index=3929 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-15,16-22,23-28>Here They Are To Really Stick
To See The
<X-word-ms ms=180,299,180,279,260 index=3931 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-16,17-21,22-24>End Result Really Show Up
So Let Me Just
Go This Is The
<X-word-ms ms=199,79,100,239,159,240 index=3934 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-15,16-20,21-24>One Of Our Train List You
<X-word-ms ms=159,220,179,400,139 index=3935 character_ranges=0-2,3-10,11-15,16-24,25-27>Run Through Some Examples To
See Same Thing You
<X-word-ms ms=360,199,139,260,300 index=3937 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-17,18-22>Can See Right Here That
<X-word-ms ms=229,180,239,159,240 index=3938 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-14,15-18,19-25>On These Trades And Things
<X-word-ms ms=259,40,279,159,180,259 index=3939 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-12,13-17,18-22,23-28>We Are Seeing They Stop Going
From Below
Two Upwards In The
15 May Right There
This Was A Reset
<X-word-ms ms=119,180,139,539,140 index=3944 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-13,14-21,22-24>Right There At Closest To
<X-word-ms ms=79,239,100,199,260,279 index=3945 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-15,16-19,20-26>It Did He Really Get Before
Shooting Higher So I
<X-word-ms ms=400,99,280,179,180 index=3947 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-17,18-23>Have The First Leg Going
High Right Here This
<X-word-ms ms=100,239,380,260,299 index=3949 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-16,17-19,20-23>Is Part Obviously Of The
<X-word-ms ms=280,179,159,80,199,179 index=3950 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-16,17-20,21-24>First Leg This Is Not Big
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,240,139,159,180 index=3951 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-17,18-19,20-25,26-32>Enough To Consider A First Valley
Consolidation Because We Need
Seven Candles After
Decan That Ended High
So Until These Two
<X-word-ms ms=320,319,199,79,220 index=3956 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-15,16-20>Days It Was Just Part
<X-word-ms ms=119,119,220,239,240,259 index=3957 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-16,17-20,21-23>Of The First Lake And As
If Continued Going
Higher Its Still
<X-word-ms ms=179,239,240,239,119 index=3960 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-15,16-18>Wall So It Ended Up
There We Have The
Conservation Here So You
<X-word-ms ms=139,140,260,300,259 index=3963 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-18,19-21>Have The First Like Or
<X-word-ms ms=180,119,319,260,180 index=3964 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-18,19-27,28-31>First Value Concern Relation The
<X-word-ms ms=260,179,160,239,739 index=3965 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-11,12-15>80 20 And 50 Are
<X-word-ms ms=260,119,140,219,159,140 index=3966 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-16,17-21,22-26>Stuck Up On Trend Then Have
<X-word-ms ms=180,99,159,180,199,220 index=3967 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-7,8-11,12-16,17-22>This C M All Turn Green
Here If Consider
<X-word-ms ms=159,220,479,100,100 index=3969 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-13,14-16,17-21>It Was Forming We Have
<X-word-ms ms=239,199,279,199,240 index=3970 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-13,14-19,20-25>The Higher Low Right There
Riding Is Volatility Contraction
<X-word-ms ms=399,79,119,279,240 index=3972 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-14,15-19,20-23>Pattern Will Be Hire Low
<X-word-ms ms=399,199,20,159,140,199 index=3973 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-8,9-14,15-17,18-23>For Me In Their So These
Is A BCP Type
Of Market
<X-word-ms ms=239,159,100,180,179,100,340 index=3976 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-16,17-21,22-25,26-35>Again If You Just Look For Ascending
Triangles And Triangle
<X-word-ms ms=180,239,159,140,119,19,199 index=3978 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-15,16-17,18-19,20-23>Or Going To Have A B BCP
<X-word-ms ms=420,240,119,19,140,159 index=3979 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-12,13-18,19-23,24-26>Anyway So You Don't Have To
<X-word-ms ms=140,279,180,139,199,660 index=3980 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-14,15-17,18-23,24-27>Really Look For It Right And
<X-word-ms ms=420,79,159,119,159,460 index=3981 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-16,17-20,21-29>Then We Just Have The Breakout
<X-word-ms ms=199,239,220,159,260 index=3982 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-9,10-13,14-19>U Enter At The Close
Right Here
This One W Interred
There With
You Stop On
<X-word-ms ms=220,140,99,79,279,680 index=3987 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-11,12-15,16-18>The Low Of A Day In
The Fifth They Was
Somewhere Around Their Ride
So Is Like Run
1 2 1 In
Reservoir Trade
Again If You Try
<X-word-ms ms=100,279,159,199,240,219 index=3994 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-13,14-19,20-27,28-31>To Trail These Stuff Because See
<X-word-ms ms=60,119,140,79,280,119,119,199 index=3995 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-15,16-25,26-28,29-34,35-37>That You Can The Reservoir Is Going To
<X-word-ms ms=119,480,159,39,180,279 index=3996 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-16,17-22,23-24>Be Lower It's Not Going 1
2 10 Obviously But
Because The Resort
Is More Modest This
Accessory Is Higher We
<X-word-ms ms=119,100,99,159,500,200 index=4001 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-15,16-24,25-27>Get All Of These Benefits Of
The Equity Curve Being
A You Know As
Sustainable Stables
<X-word-ms ms=360,159,119,100,279 index=4005 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-11,12-15,16-20>Agree That I Can Work
With Month After Month
<X-word-ms ms=219,120,299,180,180,179 index=4007 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-18,19-22,23-27,28-35>You Know Throughout The Year Through
The Cycles And
<X-word-ms ms=119,179,240,359,239 index=4009 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-15,16-23>Its Going To Pay Because
On What Is Really
Based On The We
<X-word-ms ms=140,220,179,60,159,39,159,480 index=4012 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-14,15-17,18-21,22-26,27-30,31-34>Are Seeing Kind Of You Know The End
<X-word-ms ms=359,319,200,99,100 index=4013 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-14,15-16,17-20>Product Here Of A Lot
Of Work Logically But
<X-word-ms ms=380,119,120,139,199,320 index=4015 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-16,17-22,23-30>Once To Have This Stuff Running
Out And You
<X-word-ms ms=220,220,340,199,519 index=4017 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-21,22-24,25-31>Went Through Thousands Of Stocks
<X-word-ms ms=100,140,159,199,119,100,139,140 index=4018 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-19,20-23,24-26,27-30,31-35>And You Went Through All Of The Past
Phases Your Going What
They Do In Exactly
<X-word-ms ms=600,119,20,139,260 index=4021 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-15,16-25>Where Is It Most Efficient
Way For You Right
So Very Good
Trade You Know CNX
<X-word-ms ms=299,320,199,119,260 index=4025 character_ranges=0-6,7-10,11-15,16-18,19-23>Another One That We Took
<X-word-ms ms=260,159,179,320,699 index=4026 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-15,16-19>Not Too Long Ago And
<X-word-ms ms=220,79,159,79,79,119,260,319 index=4027 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-15,16-18,19-22,23-27,28-33>You Can See That Is The Same Thing
<X-word-ms ms=460,119,140,279,220 index=4028 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-18,19-22>They Have The First Leg
<X-word-ms ms=119,180,199,140,279,159 index=4029 character_ranges=0-4,5-11,12-16,17-20,21-23,24-26>Going Higher From The 50 Am
<X-word-ms ms=60,199,500,199,220 index=4030 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-12,13-18,19-23>I Trend Reset Right From
This Consideration For
<X-word-ms ms=159,19,640,180,159 index=4032 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-17,18-20>In The 51st League On
Hire 1st Value Conservation
Was Forming Here At
<X-word-ms ms=139,240,279,319,180 index=4035 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-15,16-18>The Same Time 80 20
15 Missers Tucked
<X-word-ms ms=39,139,300,199,199,260 index=4037 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-13,14-16,17-23,24-30>Up Un Training It Seemed Screen
<X-word-ms ms=400,79,180,239,159 index=4038 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-16,17-23>There Is No Close Better
<X-word-ms ms=159,180,199,140,79,179,240 index=4039 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-14,15-17,18-21,22-27>To End Team May At All Times
In The Consideration Right
We Have Their Length
<X-word-ms ms=160,319,279,159,360 index=4042 character_ranges=0-1,2-12,13-16,17-18,19-23>Of Conclusion Off 7 Days
This Was An Ascending
Triangle The Trend
<X-word-ms ms=259,119,340,239,240 index=4045 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-16,17-21,22-26>Let's Work Former Like Base
<X-word-ms ms=199,119,100,119,399,140 index=4046 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-12,13-28,29-33>On All Of The Characteristics That
<X-word-ms ms=140,159,159,279,160,219 index=4047 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-14,15-17,18-22>We Need To Find To Draw
<X-word-ms ms=100,159,199,140,199,239 index=4048 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-14,15-20,21-25>It From Us Like These Were
There So We
<X-word-ms ms=179,100,260,159,140,299 index=4050 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-11,12-15,16-21,22-26>Took A Break Out Right Here
And We Wrote For
5 Day Move But
<X-word-ms ms=99,60,179,100,159,319,640 index=4053 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-15,16-21,22-26,27-31>You Can See That Right Here Five
<X-word-ms ms=199,99,199,260,539 index=4054 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-15,16-19>They Spot To Get The
Profits Selling Too Strength
Gator Equity Group Going
Higher And
<X-word-ms ms=239,199,119,360,239 index=4058 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-22,23-25>Stop You Know Defending Of
Really Trading Every Single
<X-word-ms ms=340,179,180,79,100,139 index=4060 character_ranges=0-4,5-12,13-18,19-24,25-27,28-31>Trade Because We're Going To Get
Frustrated As
<X-word-ms ms=259,140,199,140,340 index=4062 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-18,19-22>You Can Get Waiting For
<X-word-ms ms=99,220,279,280,239 index=4063 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-18,19-21>That Home Run Which It
<X-word-ms ms=159,199,440,139,220 index=4064 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-16,17-23,24-27>Could Take Months Before You
Really Get A Home
Rent So But Short
<X-word-ms ms=279,180,159,139,140,119 index=4067 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-16,17-21,22-24>Rate Here That We Took Us
Well I
<X-word-ms ms=119,180,319,199,320 index=4069 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-17,18-22>Did See That Right From
Here Is First
Leg Lower Right We
Have Earnings There Triggered
This Huge Selling Candle
The First Finally Consideration
From Their Near To
See Them I'm
<X-word-ms ms=140,199,300,359,140 index=4077 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-13,14-17>Sorry Be 80 20 And
<X-word-ms ms=199,279,39,220,79,199 index=4078 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-16,17-18,19-22>50 Mers Are Stuck A Low
Work Down Trending
CML Wars Green
<X-word-ms ms=460,140,180,199,260 index=4081 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-16,17-21>They Were As Well Show
<X-word-ms ms=139,119,460,240,379 index=4082 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-16,17-20,21-28>In That Linearity Was Present
Everything You Know No
<X-word-ms ms=180,159,140,199,300,179 index=4084 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-13,14-16,17-20,21-23>Close About It 20 May On
<X-word-ms ms=119,160,159,179,200,279 index=4085 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-15,16-20,21-23>The Bear Side As Well So
<X-word-ms ms=220,119,199,159,60,119,619 index=4086 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-16,17-19,20-23,24-37>How Did Break Out Of The Consideration
Of This Vcp
Winter They Close There
<X-word-ms ms=279,159,159,280,279 index=4089 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-9,10-15,16-19>Put A Stop Above And
<X-word-ms ms=159,260,180,39,79,99,300 index=4090 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-11,12-15,16-19,20-22,23-25>We Exited At The End Of 50
Which Was
This Day Right Here
<X-word-ms ms=260,300,279,119,200 index=4093 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-14,15-19,20-21>Great Trade You Know I
Can See That It's
<X-word-ms ms=99,239,180,140,260,279 index=4095 character_ranges=0-0,1-7,8-10,11-14,15-22,23-27>A Matter Of Not Hitting Home
<X-word-ms ms=319,60,380,159,479,199 index=4096 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-15,16-21,22-27,28-32>Runs But Heating These Short-Term
Trades In Just Compounding
<X-word-ms ms=239,280,119,199,180 index=4098 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-12,13-16,17-20>Against As We Ask The
Market Face Really Dictates
<X-word-ms ms=180,319,279,159,160 index=4100 character_ranges=0-4,5-17,18-22,23-25,26-29>Their Distribution When We Get
<X-word-ms ms=239,559,140,39,119 index=4101 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-15,16-22>Them Then It's A Matter
Of Just Compounding And
Working At It And
Pushing In Right This
Cbi Trade
<X-word-ms ms=340,180,260,179,240 index=4106 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-13,14-22>That We Took I Remember
These One On
June 2025
The Last
Time You Know There
<X-word-ms ms=200,179,220,239,280 index=4111 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-9,10-13,14-18>Was Such A Big Push
<X-word-ms ms=119,439,140,199,159 index=4112 character_ranges=0-1,2-9,10-13,14-17,18-22>In Markets Was You Know
June 20 25 Last
Year Where We
Did 16% Return
And Is Massive
Trader Again
Have Perfect First
Like Going
Higher From 50 May
You Know Off New
Intermediate Term Trend This
<X-word-ms ms=119,140,319,300,140 index=4123 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-10,11-15,16-18>Was A Major Base Of
<X-word-ms ms=199,239,279,159,260 index=4124 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-16,17-20,21-29>Also Going Around But Remember
<X-word-ms ms=239,160,159,99,79,140,220 index=4125 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-14,15-19,20-23,24-29>As Long As They Have The First
<X-word-ms ms=219,210,159,159,300 index=4126 character_ranges=0-5,6-12,13-16,17-22,23-25>Select Coming Off There 50
<X-word-ms ms=319,239,100,159,420 index=4127 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-8,9-13,14-19>May Is It Turn Reset
<X-word-ms ms=300,209,300,159,180 index=4128 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-17,18-19>Right Then We Have D
<X-word-ms ms=210,119,119,160,279,359 index=4129 character_ranges=0-0,1-2,3-4,5-9,10-12,13-18>E M S Open Up Never
Close With 20 Am
<X-word-ms ms=99,460,210,100,119,140 index=4131 character_ranges=0-3,4-13,14-16,17-20,21-25,26-31>Very Important So You Have These
<X-word-ms ms=279,420,140,100,259 index=4132 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-9,10-14,15-20>Non What I Told Train
<X-word-ms ms=200,119,39,219,260,159,119 index=4133 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-17,18-22,23-27,28-31>Will Be Done Ready Here With The
1st Valley Consideration
Write You Have The
1st 5 Days
Right Here Was
3 4 Five So
The End
Of 50 Is Exactly
<X-word-ms ms=319,220,259,180,220 index=4141 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-13,14-19>At Top Of This Swing
So I
<X-word-ms ms=260,119,220,300,260 index=4143 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-12,13-20,21-26>Am Not Cherry Picking These
<X-word-ms ms=139,159,280,239,260 index=4144 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-14,15-19,20-24>And Just Seeing This With
<X-word-ms ms=119,139,200,239,159,180 index=4145 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-12,13-17,18-20,21-24>You Right Now That In The
Other Fifth Day What's
<X-word-ms ms=119,199,180,119,199,140,79 index=4147 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-13,14-20,21-24,25-29>The End Of The Spring And They
<X-word-ms ms=159,199,159,200,679 index=4148 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-14,15-19>Just Pull To 20 Then
Just When Just Went
<X-word-ms ms=359,140,140,279,239 index=4150 character_ranges=0-0,1-7,8-11,12-18,19-22>A Little Bit Higher But
<X-word-ms ms=159,160,19,180,359,520 index=4151 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-14,15-22,23-27>Even If It Just Trailed With
80 May Your
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,220,300,439 index=4153 character_ranges=0-6,7-8,9-14,15-20,21-23>Getting A Worse Price If
<X-word-ms ms=119,159,159,100,220,319 index=4154 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-17,18-20,21-24>You Trade With The 20 May
And Are Closing I
<X-word-ms ms=79,119,260,259,100,119,279 index=4156 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-17,18-23,24-26,27-34,35-40>Don't Know Whether Close We Already Train
<X-word-ms ms=100,319,259,320,260 index=4157 character_ranges=0-1,2-11,12-17,18-22,23-28>Or Something Right Here There
Is Not Much Of
A Difference Here
In Prize Write
An Would
Like To Just
<X-word-ms ms=420,159,259,120,79 index=4163 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-15,16-19>Cash Out Here At The
<X-word-ms ms=139,79,140,279,440 index=4164 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-10,11-16,17-20>End Of This Swing All
<X-word-ms ms=179,120,139,119,280,519 index=4165 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-16,17-21,22-26>Would You Like To Just Hold
Through These Trader
For Life 30 Days
<X-word-ms ms=260,179,100,260,559 index=4168 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-10,11-16,17-22>More Like A Whole Month
I Mean
Just Hold This Trade
For 30 Days More
Just To Gain Water
<X-word-ms ms=219,160,239,300,259,680 index=4173 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-10,11-15,16-17,18-20>I Mean Went From 5.58
No Sorry Yeah
From Five Point Four
From Fire Fine
05 Hour 2
6 . 5 Hours
<X-word-ms ms=119,160,139,340,480 index=4179 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-7,8-13,14-17>So Is It Worth You
Know Spending 30 Days
<X-word-ms ms=300,159,300,220,279 index=4181 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-14,15-23,24-27>More Of Waiting Together One
<X-word-ms ms=239,180,220,139,240 index=4182 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-10,11-14,15-20>More Out Of The Train
Or Just Cash Out
Immediately Five Days Later
<X-word-ms ms=199,39,100,239,220,539 index=4185 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-5,6-8,9-10,11-14>At A 5 On 5 And
Take His Money Compounding
Into Other Trades Right
<X-word-ms ms=180,159,119,260,500 index=4188 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-14,15-21,22-27>Because At That Moment There
<X-word-ms ms=119,439,140,279,260 index=4189 character_ranges=0-3,4-11,12-15,16-22,23-25>Were Signals Are Coming In
<X-word-ms ms=159,119,220,139,340,119 index=4190 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-14,15-17,18-24,25-29>And Just Giving Us Profit Over
Compounding Aggressively
So Not
<X-word-ms ms=260,159,220,239,200 index=4193 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-15,16-21,22-25>During The Month Write But
Done End Result You
<X-word-ms ms=159,100,159,100,119,340,459 index=4195 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-15,16-21,22-27,28-31>Want To Take Out Their Money I'm
<X-word-ms ms=140,199,200,239,260 index=4196 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-19,20-23,24-32>Putting Into Another One Together
No More Of This
Fast Moves Because After
<X-word-ms ms=119,199,319,209,120,159 index=4199 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-10,11-14,15-18,19-22>A Fast Move You Can See
These Printed The
Second Leg You
<X-word-ms ms=140,180,79,99,120,279,199 index=4202 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-14,15-18,19-24,25-28>Can Count It As The Third Leg
<X-word-ms ms=119,119,159,360,99,420 index=4203 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-18,19-21,22-27>And They Just Ended Up There
And You Know That's
<X-word-ms ms=100,180,179,300,180,139 index=4205 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-13,14-17,18-20>The Way At The End Of
50 Rule It
<X-word-ms ms=300,159,280,199,139 index=4207 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-14,15-17>Is So Much That Is
Really Engineered To Do
That I Cannot Make
Justice In This Video
<X-word-ms ms=279,439,140,79,119 index=4211 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-15,16-18,19-20>Really But There Is A
Lot Of Benefits
<X-word-ms ms=159,119,180,359,199 index=4213 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-16,17-19>Are You Don't See On
<X-word-ms ms=180,559,140,59,60,99 index=4214 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-18,19-21>The Exit At The End Of
<X-word-ms ms=180,220,180,200,659 index=4215 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-12,13-16,17-31>The Fifth Day And Mathematically
Profits Wise Doesn'T
Make Much Of Difference
Already Trailing Let's
Get Some Into Other
Examples Here So
<X-word-ms ms=260,220,140,99,319 index=4221 character_ranges=0-6,7-10,11-15,16-18,19-23>Another One That We Took
This Hooks Trade
We Dis Was I
<X-word-ms ms=260,119,119,380,319 index=4224 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-13,14-18,19-20>Believe It Was This 1
<X-word-ms ms=260,119,99,119,120,500 index=4225 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-10,11-13,14-18,19-24>Yeah But It Is What These
On Ya Will
<X-word-ms ms=399,159,180,220,300 index=4227 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-14,15-18,19-23>Reenter In This One This
<X-word-ms ms=159,119,260,219,260 index=4228 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-12,13-18,19-22>Was A Trailer Which You
We Actually To Distrate
Right Here This
<X-word-ms ms=219,200,239,199,380 index=4231 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-15,16-24>When We Took The Straight
Because Stopped Out Know
<X-word-ms ms=299,220,140,119,220,219 index=4233 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-17,18-21,22-26>This Want Of Every Bit With
<X-word-ms ms=320,139,159,100,260,199 index=4234 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-13,14-18,19-23>Two And We Can Stop Down
<X-word-ms ms=79,180,159,79,159,120,319 index=4235 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-11,12-17,18-22,23-26,27-29>Of Course We Don't Have The 50
<X-word-ms ms=159,239,119,200,259,480 index=4236 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-18,19-22,23-25>May Here In History But It
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,119,140,139,460 index=4237 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-16,17-24,25-29>Was There Is Kind Exactly Same
At 1st
<X-word-ms ms=220,159,180,199,680 index=4239 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-19,20-33>Leg The First Valley Consolidation
Had A Break Up
Their And They Know
<X-word-ms ms=119,119,100,159,300,119,460 index=4242 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-10,11-14,15-22,23-27,28-36>All Of Them Are Stucked Upon Trending
<X-word-ms ms=99,180,119,220,479 index=4243 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-16,17-19>Not Close With 20 Me
<X-word-ms ms=180,360,139,199,119,200 index=4244 character_ranges=0-3,4-17,18-21,22-25,26-29,30-35>This Consideration Was Not The First
Folly Conservation Because
<X-word-ms ms=119,119,180,79,119,320,159 index=4246 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-13,14-17,18-24,25-27>Of The Lens Of The Candle So
<X-word-ms ms=179,160,99,140,260,139,159 index=4247 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-12,13-16,17-20,21-25,26-29>After You Can Let End That The
Lake Consolidation If We
<X-word-ms ms=119,119,239,119,160,239,159 index=4249 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-10,11-13,14-17,18-22,23-26>Had A Trade Or Not With The
Know Probably Not And
<X-word-ms ms=359,100,180,319,399 index=4251 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-14,15-17,18-26>Then Would Just No Continue
<X-word-ms ms=220,180,99,140,380 index=4252 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-14,15-20>To Look For Our Scans
<X-word-ms ms=479,79,180,220,279 index=4253 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-10,11-15,16-18>I Knew This Work So
<X-word-ms ms=269,180,319,100,300 index=4254 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-13,14-16,17-24>Again Going To Go Through
Deeper Into Scan
Later On On
The Next Session
<X-word-ms ms=159,360,269,180,319 index=4258 character_ranges=0-2,3-14,15-19,20-24,25-28>But Essentially They Will Run
<X-word-ms ms=220,239,380,140,539 index=4259 character_ranges=0-4,5-10,11-13,14-18,19-21>These Stuff Is That We
We Ran The Skins
We Look First Talks
<X-word-ms ms=39,460,180,260,270 index=4262 character_ranges=0-1,2-10,11-14,15-17,18-26>On Breakout Day So Whenever
<X-word-ms ms=260,179,199,300,199 index=4263 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-16,17-25,26-29>Stock It's Really Breaking Out
<X-word-ms ms=160,159,139,180,239,220 index=4264 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-15,16-20,21-23>Are Going To See That On
<X-word-ms ms=180,420,179,119,120 index=4265 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-12,13-17,18-20>Our Scans And Then We
<X-word-ms ms=139,119,320,139,159,240 index=4266 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-14,15-17,18-20,21-26>Going To Decide If It Meets
<X-word-ms ms=159,119,399,79,220,520 index=4267 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-15,16-18,19-22,23-27>All The Criteria Or Not Take
It Or Not So
Is Very Easy
To Do So So
In Where Just Looking
Again For Scanning
For Breakout Day
<X-word-ms ms=460,220,140,139,200 index=4274 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-14,15-20>And All Of This Stuff
<X-word-ms ms=239,79,159,279,320 index=4275 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-22,23-28>You Don't Have Although Seems
Like A Big List
In Five My
Mentees Know That They
Actually Go Through The
<X-word-ms ms=339,180,100,299,220 index=4280 character_ranges=0-9,10-12,13-14,15-19,20-24>Mentorship Is A Huge Huge
<X-word-ms ms=239,180,480,59,100 index=4281 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-17,18-22>List But You Don't Have
<X-word-ms ms=159,119,199,140,180,159,139 index=4282 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-12,13-17,18-23,24-28,29-33>To Go Through This Stuff It's Just
Tough To Explain What
<X-word-ms ms=140,79,239,319,180,179 index=4284 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-19,20-25,26-30>We Are Doing Because These Cans
<X-word-ms ms=80,139,119,100,159,140,179,60,199 index=4285 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-14,15-19,20-24,25-29,30-32,33-36>Are Going To Do More Than Most Of The
Heavy Lifting Pointing
<X-word-ms ms=119,200,199,420,340 index=4287 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-15,16-22>Out To You There Stucks
<X-word-ms ms=99,119,100,180,299,380 index=4288 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-16,17-26,27-30>That You Have Pay Attention Too
<X-word-ms ms=480,119,159,220,199 index=4289 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-16,17-19>And Then It Takes Me
Literally Two Seconds To
<X-word-ms ms=140,119,20,159,99,260,199,220 index=4291 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-8,9-13,14-15,16-22,23-25,26-29>Know If I Have A Signal Or Not
<X-word-ms ms=400,59,140,79,79,220,220 index=4292 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-16,17-18,19-24,25-27>When They Look At A Chart So
When I Go Through
<X-word-ms ms=220,399,79,140,140,159 index=4294 character_ranges=0-1,2-10,11-14,15-20,21-23,24-28>My Scanning And Going To Show
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,79,140,279,440 index=4295 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-15,16-21,22-26>That In The Next Video Just
<X-word-ms ms=399,119,100,260,219 index=4296 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-10,11-16,17-20>Hit In This Space Bar
Like Crazy It Takes
Me Literally Two
Seconds To
<X-word-ms ms=260,159,79,159,180,179 index=4300 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-13,14-20,21-23>Know If Have A Signal Or
<X-word-ms ms=180,220,239,220,479 index=4301 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-16,17-23>Not Right So Very Simple
Is Just The
Way Works Again We
<X-word-ms ms=59,79,79,79,400,220,159 index=4304 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-14,15-25,26-30,31-34>Are Going To Be Discussing Into The
Next Session A
Lot About Process Distribution
You Know System Trading
On The Trend I
Think About A
Lot Today Know How
<X-word-ms ms=219,79,300,260,199 index=4311 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-14,15-20,21-24>This Was Really Built And
Why But Again
<X-word-ms ms=420,99,240,199,199 index=4313 character_ranges=0-7,8-10,11-18,19-20,21-28>Disagree It Started I Believe
<X-word-ms ms=439,199,100,180,159 index=4314 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-16,17-21>We Can Go Through Some
Examples If You Wish
Again Just To See
<X-word-ms ms=139,380,119,159,180,119 index=4317 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-15,16-21,22-26>That This Is The Thing That
Goes Again And
<X-word-ms ms=99,119,240,219,180,440 index=4319 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-16,17-21,22-24>Its Just Same All Time So
These On This Db
<X-word-ms ms=179,160,139,199,220,440 index=4321 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-16,17-26,27-30>Tree That We Took Sometimes The
First Leg Lower It
Can Be A Train
<X-word-ms ms=220,140,219,240,199 index=4324 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-14,15-19>Reset Of 50 May With
<X-word-ms ms=179,300,220,199,279 index=4325 character_ranges=0-0,1-4,5-7,8-9,10-13>A Gap So A Gab
<X-word-ms ms=280,260,219,140,140 index=4326 character_ranges=0-9,10-12,13-18,19-23,24-29>Especially On Ernie Some Stuff
Like That This
Could Be It Is
<X-word-ms ms=200,199,199,340,300 index=4329 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-12,13-15,16-25>The First Leg Of Operation
<X-word-ms ms=199,159,300,279,359 index=4330 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-16,17-19,20-23>You Train Because We See
<X-word-ms ms=280,179,200,239,319 index=4331 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-11,12-14>D8 And 20 In 50
<X-word-ms ms=240,99,119,160,279,220 index=4332 character_ranges=0-0,1-2,3-5,6-8,9-14,15-16>M S At Up Lower C
More Green And These
Huge Gaps Right There
And Below To
<X-word-ms ms=199,140,279,220,340 index=4336 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-15,16-18,19-28>Have Our Firstly So Sometimes
Gaps Can Be Part
Offers Next Does
<X-word-ms ms=79,119,199,239,239,160 index=4339 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-12,13-15,16-20,21-25>It Make Sense So Then Will
<X-word-ms ms=199,199,359,180,600 index=4340 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-14,15-19,20-25>Have This First Must Touch
<X-word-ms ms=239,340,179,220,180 index=4341 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-11,12-14,15-16>At Least The 80 M
<X-word-ms ms=119,440,159,220,220 index=4342 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-10,11-14,15-20>A Right And Not Close
Beyond That
<X-word-ms ms=179,140,420,119,239 index=4344 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-16,17-20,21-23>You Can Overshoot The 50
<X-word-ms ms=220,159,440,179,100 index=4345 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-15,16-18,19-21>But Never Closed Be On
<X-word-ms ms=140,179,140,460,119 index=4346 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-8,9-11,12-14>The Fif T So We
<X-word-ms ms=100,119,259,320,279 index=4347 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-14,15-20>Need To Pull It Needs
<X-word-ms ms=79,220,139,320,219,360 index=4348 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-14,15-16,17-19>To Pull Back 28 N 20
<X-word-ms ms=340,99,359,140,500 index=4349 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-10,11-13,14-19>In 8 Layers So Think
<X-word-ms ms=199,200,279,139,180,100 index=4350 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-14,15-17,18-22,23-24>About This Area Is Like A
<X-word-ms ms=279,180,319,220,119 index=4351 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-17,18-22,23-27>Cloud Or Something They Need
To Pull Back Into
Right So When He
<X-word-ms ms=239,220,159,119,199,399 index=4354 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-13,14-18,19-22,23-31>Does Of Course Have The Breakout
There And We Had
A Nice Five Day
Move But Again Can
Also Be Right
The Part Of The
<X-word-ms ms=219,220,100,179,160,79,199 index=4360 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-10,11-14,15-17,18-21,22-27>First Leg I See On The Short
<X-word-ms ms=239,140,199,300,800 index=4361 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-13,14-17,18-21>Side As Always Say 1st
Lake 1st Down For
5 Firs Valley Consideration
Final Dump
And Then 3rd L
<X-word-ms ms=119,300,39,119,400,199 index=4366 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-9,10-13,14-24,25-27>E Tends To Get Truncation Or
<X-word-ms ms=199,260,179,300,199 index=4367 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-16,17-22,23-26>Higher Low Cities Right Now
And They Just Continue
To Move Higher That
Is No That's
<X-word-ms ms=119,159,100,219,160,59,100,159 index=4371 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-15,16-22,23-26,27-30,31-37>The Way It Works That's The Way Market
Really Works After Not
<X-word-ms ms=159,359,180,159,119,400 index=4373 character_ranges=0-2,3-13,14-18,19-21,22-24,25-34>The Thoroughly Tend To Be Something
<X-word-ms ms=239,180,219,240,699 index=4374 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-19,20-32>That It Never Really Materializes
So That'S
Why Short Trades There
Is Nothing More Beyond
<X-word-ms ms=279,239,220,260,579 index=4378 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-14,15-17,18-22>This Second Leg So This
<X-word-ms ms=99,160,159,119,199,319 index=4379 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-13,14-15,16-22>Is One That We I Showed
<X-word-ms ms=60,180,139,159,240,219,280 index=4380 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-15,16-19,20-22,23-27>You Not Too Long Ago So Same
<X-word-ms ms=299,239,159,160,579 index=4381 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-18,19-22>Thing You Know Have 1st
<X-word-ms ms=159,279,239,180,799 index=4382 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-15,16-22,23-36>Lake Lower First Valley Consideration
<X-word-ms ms=500,140,79,119,320 index=4383 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-14,15-17>Put Them Out In 20
Me Layer All Of
<X-word-ms ms=239,319,239,160,299 index=4385 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-11,12-15,16-19>Dm Sacked Up The CML
Green We Have Perfect
Combination Of Momentum
Linearity With A Moment
D Volatility Contraction
Expansion On Breakout Day
You Know Do
Have Their Right Length
Of Concernation So
<X-word-ms ms=200,79,439,140,639 index=4394 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-17,18-31>This Is 1st Valley Consideration
<X-word-ms ms=219,120,219,159,240,319 index=4395 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-11,12-15,16-21,22-27>Had It Break Out There Which
Took The Entry At
<X-word-ms ms=59,119,220,220,100,219,500 index=4397 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-11,12-15,16-18,19-24,25-28>End Of Today But As Short I'm
Sorry Stop
<X-word-ms ms=340,220,219,119,220 index=4399 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-13,14-17,18-21>Above High Off The Day
Just Write For 5
They More No
Is Same Thing Again
And Again So This
<X-word-ms ms=220,99,140,420,140 index=4404 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-16,17-23>Is The Way Stocks Really
<X-word-ms ms=299,200,139,220,460 index=4405 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-17,18-22>Move You Know They Have
<X-word-ms ms=159,239,119,120,199,519 index=4406 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-13,14-18,19-22,23-28>Been Moving In This Way Since
Forever Show I
Show As You Know
<X-word-ms ms=179,260,159,119,320 index=4409 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-15,16-19,20-24>The Oldest Setup Can Find
<X-word-ms ms=99,220,239,380,579 index=4410 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-15,16-18>It 115 Years Ago So
Same Thing Another Gap
<X-word-ms ms=260,159,300,159,279 index=4412 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-14,15-18,19-24>Here That Shows The First
<X-word-ms ms=239,159,300,260,279 index=4413 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-8,9-12,13-16>Leg So At The 1st
<X-word-ms ms=159,240,219,280,159 index=4414 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-17,18-24>Like There The 1st Valley
Consideration And That
Question About How Far
Can Go You
<X-word-ms ms=119,180,219,220,520 index=4418 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-12,13-17>Know De Or As This
Move Keeps On Moving
Sideways You
<X-word-ms ms=79,160,79,179,119,100,279,260 index=4421 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-9,10-15,16-20,21-24,25-27,28-31>Will See A Close With The 20 May
Because The 80 Am
8 Gets Into Price
<X-word-ms ms=259,180,180,199,159,119 index=4424 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-17,18-20,21-26>And Then Next Step Be Cause
<X-word-ms ms=140,79,140,319,159,100,219 index=4425 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-7,8-15,16-18,19-22,23-27>It Is An Average Of The Past
Twenty Period
<X-word-ms ms=219,140,119,199,440 index=4427 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-15,16-23>So If They Daily Candles
<X-word-ms ms=199,119,180,279,340 index=4428 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-13,14-17,18-22>In There Guess Too Long
De 20 Me
We Get Within Pressing
<X-word-ms ms=119,239,360,79,299 index=4431 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-13,14-16,17-19>Us Here Closer To 20
<X-word-ms ms=300,119,120,159,259,539 index=4432 character_ranges=0-0,1-2,3-5,6-10,11-16,17-20>M S At That Point You
<X-word-ms ms=140,239,280,99,119,100,519 index=4433 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-18,19-21,22-24,25-31>Draw Line That This Is No Longer
A Momentum Stock
That You Probably Have
<X-word-ms ms=159,340,239,119,120,439 index=4436 character_ranges=0-3,4-14,15-17,18-22,23-28,29-37>Some Volatility Or It's Going Sideways
<X-word-ms ms=159,220,319,220,220 index=4437 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-14,15-18,19-25>And Stop Really The Moment
So They
Close Below Their
<X-word-ms ms=220,199,179,120,299 index=4440 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-13,14-16>Rule That If I If
<X-word-ms ms=60,159,119,420,140,99,300 index=4441 character_ranges=0-0,1-7,8-10,11-24,25-28,29-30,31-37>A Second In Consideration Has A Closer
<X-word-ms ms=100,300,359,240,239 index=4442 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-12,13-17>To 20 May Its Also
Something Too There
Has Something Backed
Up There Is There
Are Things There Right
So That There Is
<X-word-ms ms=119,359,220,220,319 index=4448 character_ranges=0-2,3-9,10-13,14-19,20-25>Our Reason Why Stuff Works
<X-word-ms ms=180,220,179,280,239 index=4449 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-16,17-19,20-24>Like These Rights Oh This
<X-word-ms ms=340,139,260,180,219 index=4450 character_ranges=0-1,2-9,10-13,14-16,17-21>Is Another One We Took
<X-word-ms ms=220,119,140,279,460 index=4451 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-15,16-20>Not Too Long Ago This
<X-word-ms ms=199,119,140,139,20,220,359 index=4452 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-9,10-12,13-16,17-21,22-26>One I Said To You From 2026
Our Reason 1 And
<X-word-ms ms=420,220,159,119,319 index=4454 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-17,18-22>Again You Have The Lake
Higher Be End
<X-word-ms ms=220,119,259,140,159,340 index=4456 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-15,16-21,22-28>Of The First Way Going Higher
First Valley Consideration
They Breakout DMS
<X-word-ms ms=160,119,399,199,140 index=4459 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-14,15-19>Are All Open Up That
Or All Open
<X-word-ms ms=199,300,159,219,260 index=4461 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-11,12-17,18-21>Up After The First Leg
<X-word-ms ms=420,119,159,240,139 index=4462 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-13,14-19,20-23>For Me Through Reset Off
There 50 May CML
Green It Had
<X-word-ms ms=119,99,120,259,440 index=4465 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-24,25-29>The First By Conservation Then
The Breakout Through
The Trendline This Is
No It D
Consolidation Is Valid
<X-word-ms ms=160,339,140,119,360 index=4470 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-11,12-15,16-23>By Length Of The Candles
They Points Are There
<X-word-ms ms=119,199,140,199,199,239 index=4472 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-16,17-21,22-26>To Draw The Train Line That
<X-word-ms ms=400,119,199,159,180 index=4473 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-6,7-9,10-13>We I Do It And
<X-word-ms ms=180,119,139,79,300,220 index=4474 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-9,10-12,13-21,22-25>Its A Kind Of Standard Way
To Do It Will
<X-word-ms ms=159,140,180,199,180,179 index=4476 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-17,18-20,21-26>Have The Break Out We Enter
<X-word-ms ms=159,79,260,180,380 index=4477 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-12,13-16>At The End Of Day
Play Put Stop
Right There Just
<X-word-ms ms=279,140,179,300,279 index=4480 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-10,11-14,15-19>Write For 5 Day Move
<X-word-ms ms=480,99,200,139,340 index=4481 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-15,16-20>You Can See Even Then
On Five Hours So
<X-word-ms ms=259,120,239,260,159 index=4483 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-15,16-18>If You Sell Some At
<X-word-ms ms=99,240,219,140,140,99,180 index=4484 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-15,16-19,20-22,23-27>The Pop And Then Try To Turn
<X-word-ms ms=140,199,279,140,239,240 index=4485 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-18,19-27,28-32>The Rest Your Going Together Less
<X-word-ms ms=319,180,240,159,399 index=4486 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-16,17-19,20-22>Than Just Selling Of 50
So I
Hope Improving A Point
Here That This
Is Very Powerful There's
A Very Repeatable Power
Full Setup An Edge
<X-word-ms ms=159,119,99,160,199,399 index=4493 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-8,9-13,14-18,19-25>And It Is Just Away Stocks
Movies Happening Again And
Again So Again
First Like Lower
Their Offers 15 May
<X-word-ms ms=159,140,239,260,79,199 index=4498 character_ranges=0-5,6-8,9-18,19-25,26-29,30-32>Should Be Somewhere Around The 50
May All They Am
<X-word-ms ms=79,180,260,339,140,640 index=4500 character_ranges=0-0,1-4,5-7,8-10,11-15,16-21>A Set Up As That Lower
Sorry And Down Trending
CML Green You
<X-word-ms ms=199,180,180,119,99,120,179 index=4503 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-15,16-19,20-22,23-28>Take It Close At End Of Today
<X-word-ms ms=239,279,159,300,199 index=4504 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-11,12-15,16-20>Have Right 5 Day Move
On Quality Today I
<X-word-ms ms=100,139,159,240,619 index=4506 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-18,19-21>Go For An Excellent So
<X-word-ms ms=179,100,239,380,440 index=4507 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-17,18-23>This Is Same Thing Again
And Again And Again
To Another One
Here Then Metal There
<X-word-ms ms=239,159,160,179,180,239 index=4511 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-11,12-16,17-20,21-24>Rules Are We Took Not Too
Long Ago So We
<X-word-ms ms=180,219,280,279,300 index=4513 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-15,16-21>Have No These Be Lower
<X-word-ms ms=199,260,219,140,140,179 index=4514 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-18,19-21,22-26>High Their And Then It Just
<X-word-ms ms=140,119,220,239,239,239 index=4515 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-18,19-21,22-28>You Know Is Started To Behave
Volatile Based Out
Enter Into A Massive
Base Which Them Either
<X-word-ms ms=220,359,220,100,339 index=4519 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-12,13-19>Goes Up Or Go Slower
For Another First Layer
<X-word-ms ms=199,159,160,119,179,560 index=4521 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-16,17-23,24-37>We Have The First Valley Consideration
Somewhere Around Here But
<X-word-ms ms=239,199,279,120,119,299 index=4523 character_ranges=0-7,8-11,12-19,20-22,23-26,27-33>Whenever Got Trigger In Two Signal
Anyways Last I Want
<X-word-ms ms=139,200,159,99,199,240 index=4525 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-8,9-13,14-18,19-23>To Find I Want Show This
<X-word-ms ms=259,160,79,119,260,480 index=4526 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-16,17-21,22-26>Trade With Us Are Very Cool
Trailer We Had And
We Had A Massive
<X-word-ms ms=239,79,300,100,139,619 index=4529 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-16,17-20,21-31>They Know Soon In Our Unrealized
Pnl Right Here So
<X-word-ms ms=300,239,119,280,199 index=4531 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-7,8-13,14-17>We Had A First Leg
Higher Right There It
<X-word-ms ms=119,159,140,159,539 index=4533 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-17,18-31>Is The First Value Consideration
<X-word-ms ms=159,320,139,100,279,199 index=4534 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-11,12-15,16-23,24-27>By Length Of The Candles Not
<X-word-ms ms=220,119,119,119,340,439 index=4535 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-14,15-19,20-29,30-40>Taking Out They High Obviously Everything
<X-word-ms ms=260,239,220,180,139 index=4536 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-16,17-21>Is Their No Close Very
20 May Have To
<X-word-ms ms=340,239,199,140,199 index=4538 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-10,11-16,17-22>Hire Low So Every Thing
<X-word-ms ms=100,199,100,199,179,280 index=4539 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-10,11-15,16-19,20-25>Was There I Took The Break
Over Here And
You Can See Massive
Massive Swing
In The Equity Curve
So We Have Three
Four No At One
Point Intraday
<X-word-ms ms=199,120,179,159,180,319,320 index=4547 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-10,11-15,16-20,21-22,23-23>This Was Up Like Over 5%
But I Followed
The Strictly In Of
Their Fifth Day And
<X-word-ms ms=160,219,220,159,100,99,500 index=4551 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-14,15-16,17-18,19-21>We Got Out With A 1.42
So Does It Really
Matter And
This Is Approved Appoint
That I Still Follow
My Signals As To
<X-word-ms ms=200,139,180,300,500 index=4557 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-15,16-19>Full On My Rules 100
Percent An Accident
<X-word-ms ms=199,280,260,259,360 index=4559 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-14,15-22>Of 50 Why Start Because
It's Not About Any
Individual Trade If It's
About The Result
Over Hundreds Of
Traits So If I
Do This Rule Like
Keep On Consistent Pushing
<X-word-ms ms=300,239,240,219,300 index=4567 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-14,15-21>On These Over A Series
<X-word-ms ms=239,340,119,220,199 index=4568 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-12,13-21,22-24>Of Trades For Hundreds Of
Treats I Know
<X-word-ms ms=199,159,380,119,140,159 index=4570 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-17,18-20,21-26,27-29>What My Expectance Is Going To
<X-word-ms ms=180,239,159,140,139,620 index=4571 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-14,15-17,18-27>Be And All What Am Expecting
<X-word-ms ms=159,519,159,120,279 index=4572 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-14,15-17,18-22>Right But Start To Mess
<X-word-ms ms=220,199,199,279,140 index=4573 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-17,18-22>Out With Rules And Send
<X-word-ms ms=180,279,279,220,479 index=4574 character_ranges=0-3,4-12,13-15,16-24,25-28>Into Strength Or Whatever You
<X-word-ms ms=140,279,159,80,79,59,140,199 index=4575 character_ranges=0-3,4-5,6-11,12-16,17-19,20-22,23-28,29-31>Know I Don't Know If He Going To
Hurt Over Time But
This Is Something That
<X-word-ms ms=159,240,219,159,260 index=4578 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-16,17-19,20-25>Will Really Start To Bring
<X-word-ms ms=380,239,140,100,159 index=4579 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-16,17-19>Um You Will Start To
Break The Discipline Of
Just Following Rules And
<X-word-ms ms=119,39,140,380,699 index=4582 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-17,18-26>It Was Are Getting Creative
With Your Own Thinking
And Once Open Down
Door And Go Into
<X-word-ms ms=240,179,240,179,280 index=4586 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-16,17-21>It Very Hard From Back
So Again From
Experience I Prefer
<X-word-ms ms=180,199,159,240,619 index=4589 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-11,12-17,18-26>To Follow My Rules Strictly
<X-word-ms ms=159,199,279,320,239 index=4590 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-13,14-16,17-23>If This Wasn't An Unreal
<X-word-ms ms=340,99,180,359,220 index=4591 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-10,11-11,12-16>Spend All 5% Then
<X-word-ms ms=220,399,100,199,140 index=4592 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-14,15-19>In End Up Being Less
Than 1.5% I
<X-word-ms ms=240,199,239,199,100,260 index=4594 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-17,18-21,22-25,26-33>Don't Care Because I'm Not Looking
<X-word-ms ms=159,380,179,260,520 index=4595 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-7,8-13,14-20>At A Per Trade Result
<X-word-ms ms=159,179,140,460,399 index=4596 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-13,14-21>And Look In An Overall
Equity Curve Movement After
<X-word-ms ms=219,180,300,119,99,200 index=4598 character_ranges=0-7,8-10,11-17,18-21,22-27,28-35>Hundreds Of Trades And Going Through
Market Faces That's
<X-word-ms ms=239,159,319,119,280 index=4600 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-14,15-18>If You Focus On Too
Much One Single Trailer
<X-word-ms ms=380,99,120,99,199,159 index=4602 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-14,15-19,20-22>Are Going To Do Side Up
<X-word-ms ms=120,159,19,240,279,239 index=4603 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-11,12-17,18-22,23-28>What We Were Doing Here Which
<X-word-ms ms=100,219,200,219,400 index=4604 character_ranges=0-1,2-9,10-12,13-17,18-20>Is Running An Edge It
<X-word-ms ms=59,260,220,179,100,340 index=4605 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-11,12-16,17-19,20-26>Is About Its Game Of Volume
No Note Of
Getting Like In One
A Just Single
Trade Right Hope That
Makes Sense Obviously
So Again
<X-word-ms ms=220,199,100,99,79,60,140,259 index=4612 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-11,12-14,15-18,19-23,24-27,28-37>I Don't Know If You Have Any Questions
Here I
Believe We Probably
Went Through Some Cool
<X-word-ms ms=299,260,100,260,259 index=4616 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-20,21-26>Stuff In This Session Today
On The Next
<X-word-ms ms=160,99,159,180,100,199,199 index=4618 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-16,17-19,20-27,28-33>Day Were Going To Be Talking About
The Process The Scanning
And All Of These
Staff Also About
Distribution
<X-word-ms ms=179,119,140,199,400 index=4623 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-12,13-17,18-27>Of The System Very Important
And Also Touch About
On System Trading Stuff
So It's
Going To Complete And
Compliment This One
<X-word-ms ms=180,299,300,119,119 index=4629 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-15,16-18,19-22>Really Have Kind Of The
Whole Picture Overview
Here So I
<X-word-ms ms=600,79,60,39,79,119,460 index=4632 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-12,13-16,17-21,22-25,26-35>Don't Know If You Have Any Questions
But Even Pretty Clear
<X-word-ms ms=180,179,180,119,159,380 index=4634 character_ranges=0-4,5-11,12-14,15-19,20-23,24-32>About Anyone To Have Any Question
<X-word-ms ms=220,250,140,140,119,239 index=4635 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-10,11-13,14-17,18-22>Just Put In On The Chat
Now We Can Answer
Them Anybody Has Questions
<X-word-ms ms=250,159,59,140,220,359 index=4638 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-15,16-20,21-30>And If You Don'T Have Questions
Now See
These Video Later
<X-word-ms ms=250,159,260,220,279 index=4641 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-13,14-17,18-21>You Can Always Not Put
Them Right There Probably
In The Chat Or
Something We Can Discuss
<X-word-ms ms=260,220,319,140,79 index=4645 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-9,10-15,16-20>That But I Don't Know
<X-word-ms ms=139,140,199,140,399 index=4646 character_ranges=0-1,2-9,10-13,14-17,18-27>If Anybody Has Any Questions
Going To Probably Give
<X-word-ms ms=140,159,359,280,399 index=4648 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-11,12-14,15-23>Out A Minute Of Somebody
Once You Put
<X-word-ms ms=119,240,159,99,220,479 index=4650 character_ranges=0-2,3-11,12-14,15-18,19-24,25-33>The Question In The Chart Probably
<X-word-ms ms=199,159,39,80,500,359 index=4651 character_ranges=0-0,1-6,7-11,12-15,16-20,21-30>I Don'T Know How Many Questions
Are Any Which Is
<X-word-ms ms=160,139,140,140,239,239 index=4653 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-13,14-15,16-20,21-27>At All Because I Kind Repeat
This Stuff Every Single
<X-word-ms ms=319,220,219,180,199 index=4655 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-15,16-18>Day And Train To No
Brain Was Anyone With
System Trading And
How Things Work Everything
So Again
It Is Michael
<X-word-ms ms=280,139,199,200,179,119 index=4661 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-16,17-20,21-25>How Are You Thank You Very
<X-word-ms ms=300,199,120,79,279,640 index=4662 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-18,19-23,24-28>Much Thank You Very Much Have
A Question To
<X-word-ms ms=239,199,319,180,60,239 index=4664 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-9,10-14,15-18,19-24>Get Oh How What You Doing
Brother Even Unlimited
<X-word-ms ms=259,140,199,320,139 index=4666 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-14,15-21,22-26>Time To Further Define Your
First Flag
System Which Area Would
You Follow Good Question
<X-word-ms ms=180,79,100,99,520,300 index=4670 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-9,10-17,18-22,23-25>If I Haven Limited Time To
Further Refiner 1st
Flag System Which
<X-word-ms ms=300,260,100,319,319 index=4673 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-19,20-22>Area Would You Focus On
<X-word-ms ms=229,140,159,140,139,200 index=4674 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-15,16-20,21-27>With The Part Of This System
<X-word-ms ms=139,180,239,180,199,440 index=4675 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-13,14-16,17-22,23-31>Do Think Could Be Still Improved
<X-word-ms ms=60,119,159,100,159,579,340,239,1159,340,319 index=4676 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-13,14-23,24-28,29-31,32-38,39-45,46-50,51-56>So if you have unlimited time to really refine this more,
<X-word-ms ms=200,79,239,260,159,159 index=4677 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-13,14-17,18-22>If You Want If You Want
<X-word-ms ms=340,319,119,140,220 index=4678 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-11,12-16,17-21>To Refine It Even More
What I Would Do
Is Have More Time
It's Not Refined
This System By Itself
Because I
Believe Already Being Punished
<X-word-ms ms=159,119,159,180,159,159,180 index=4685 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-9,10-14,15-17,18-21,22-25>At A Point That If You Try
<X-word-ms ms=239,340,159,79,79,660 index=4686 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-17,18-28>Too Even If You Go Marginally
To Really Go Deeper
Into Getting Lower Drawdowns
<X-word-ms ms=159,300,159,220,20,179 index=4689 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-19,20-22,23-26,27-32>More Profit Whatever We Are Going
<X-word-ms ms=180,140,99,279,440 index=4690 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-8,9-12,13-16>To Get In Two You
<X-word-ms ms=79,140,199,239,300,279 index=4691 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-16,17-24,25-31>Can Get Into Core Fitting That's
<X-word-ms ms=100,139,200,339,560 index=4692 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-11,12-14,15-24>Why It Could Be Dangerous
To Refine Even
More A System
If Its Simple Robust
And Its Profitable
<X-word-ms ms=160,99,220,260,599 index=4697 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-11,12-16,17-20>Has A Strong Edge The
<X-word-ms ms=220,239,220,119,79,140 index=4698 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-15,16-18,19-23>Best Thing To Do Is Keep
<X-word-ms ms=139,300,300,159,100,159 index=4699 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-11,12-16,17-18,19-24>It Simple So What I Would
Do Is Not
Refined This One But
Maybe Build Another One
That Complements These Ones
<X-word-ms ms=199,260,199,159,60,579 index=4704 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-18,19-20,21-30>Right And Have Like A Portfolio
Thing Going On As
Some For People
That Sends To Really
<X-word-ms ms=239,159,500,20,300 index=4708 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-18,19-22,23-25>Lower The Drawdowns And It
Will Lower Also Profits
But You Can Sleep
More
<X-word-ms ms=140,180,500,159,99 index=4712 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-10,11-13,14-18>On That Now If Your
<X-word-ms ms=180,319,260,199,340 index=4713 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-15,16-20,21-25>More Active Have More Time
<X-word-ms ms=220,99,120,279,279,440 index=4714 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-11,12-16,17-21,22-27>When You Are Full Time Doing
This Hundred Percent I
Believe Be Deliver
<X-word-ms ms=239,140,239,220,179 index=4717 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-18,19-21>Each One Time Would Be
Develop Another Swing
Training System Maybe A
Bulldog System So
Complement These One Or
Even Build Develop
Something That Profits
When Essentially 1
D System Doesn't Profit
<X-word-ms ms=120,139,199,160,459 index=4726 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-15,16-20>Which Is Will Be When
<X-word-ms ms=120,99,420,340,260 index=4727 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-14,15-20,21-24>There Is Choppy Faces Now
For Example If
You Just Say A
Question Here If
You Would Be It
<X-word-ms ms=520,159,139,140,319 index=4732 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-14,15-21>Will Be In This Market
Since October For Exam
I Know That People
Are Still Premium Have
<X-word-ms ms=159,119,240,299,420 index=4736 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-16,17-21,22-27>Been Doing Really Well Right
But You Need To
And Again Train
Options Another Whole Beast
It's Another Thing
<X-word-ms ms=260,99,140,140,299,140 index=4741 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-13,14-21,22-24>You Have To Go Through At
An Echo Deeper
And Make Sure That
<X-word-ms ms=139,40,319,260,159,139 index=4744 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-15,16-25,26-27,28-31>You Are Building Something I Was
<X-word-ms ms=200,299,280,179,400 index=4745 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-15,16-26>On Those Type Of Conditions
<X-word-ms ms=179,260,220,199,619 index=4746 character_ranges=0-1,2-10,11-20,21-27,28-39>By Building Something Really Compliments
This Stuff When This
<X-word-ms ms=239,260,100,159,79,79,380 index=4748 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-18,19-21,22-23,24-32>Thing You Know It's In A Drawdown
Build Some Bring Something
<X-word-ms ms=159,140,199,460,100 index=4750 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-13,14-20,21-23>Like I'm Being Profit To
<X-word-ms ms=139,220,199,180,180,359 index=4751 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-16,17-24,25-30>Add Two Lower The Journal Maybe
Even Give Your Consistent
Prophet Every Single Month
Will Be Way Go
Now If You Need
Nor Get Data
Options Historical
Data And
<X-word-ms ms=159,480,139,79,180 index=4759 character_ranges=0-4,5-13,14-20,21-23,24-30>Start Modeling Shapes To Really
Run Through Nor Gate
Data With
Python And Really Come
Up Ways To Build
Something Without
Options That Profits
<X-word-ms ms=159,180,260,119,139,480 index=4766 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-15,16-18,19-24,25-33>When This System Is Going Sideways
<X-word-ms ms=159,119,180,420,739 index=4767 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-13,14-16,17-24>You Have Still Be Running
<X-word-ms ms=239,159,79,80,159,420 index=4768 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-14,15-19,20-29>It And You Will Have Drawdowns
<X-word-ms ms=99,180,100,99,180,179,320 index=4769 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-16,17-21,22-26,27-30>But When You Have Draw Down The
System Would Not
<X-word-ms ms=240,59,199,340,199 index=4771 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-19,20-22>We Will Be Profiting So
<X-word-ms ms=260,119,260,180,199 index=4772 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-14,15-17,18-21>Kind Of Balance Us Out
<X-word-ms ms=159,119,39,159,140,180,559 index=4773 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-14,15-16,17-21,22-28>So You Can Have A More Stable
Equal Girl Steel So
That Will Be
Very Important Your Conditions
<X-word-ms ms=140,159,300,359,279 index=4777 character_ranges=0-0,1-8,9-13,14-19,20-23>I Believe Both Might Not
Do That Well
Once You
<X-word-ms ms=220,140,179,199,160,880 index=4780 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-15,16-18,19-23,24-28>Test And Develop It Make Sure
With Ample
<X-word-ms ms=260,239,220,19,340 index=4782 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-16,17-22>Data What You Are Doing
Is Really Durable Right
So Maybe
Like Selling Premium
Spreads
Or Something On
The SPX Or Something
Like That Would
Be A System To
Allocate Percentage Of Capital
They Can Really Work
Its Another Thing It's
Different From This
But It's Still Trading
<X-word-ms ms=159,199,280,99,200,279 index=4796 character_ranges=0-1,2-11,12-16,17-20,21-24,25-29>Is Something That You Can Work
<X-word-ms ms=340,179,119,240,139 index=4797 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-10,11-14,15-20>And If Have The Right
Mindset With System
Developing Or How To
<X-word-ms ms=159,159,439,80,219 index=4800 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-12,13-20>Do It You Can Develop
<X-word-ms ms=140,140,219,159,440 index=4801 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-11,12-16,17-27>It With Data Just Manipulate
<X-word-ms ms=220,99,159,79,160,199,159 index=4802 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-10,11-12,13-17,18-21,22-24>In There In A Ride Way So
Avoid Curve Fading
Having Ample Data
Really Compare See That
<X-word-ms ms=200,179,140,460,159 index=4806 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-23,24-26>You Know The Correlation Is
<X-word-ms ms=79,239,120,159,179,560 index=4807 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-16,17-25,26-37>Not They Are This Negative Correlation
<X-word-ms ms=300,59,140,440,440 index=4808 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-14,15-17,18-21>For Your Really If You
<X-word-ms ms=139,160,519,140,139 index=4809 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-14,15-19,20-22>Had More Margin That We
Do Appearance Due
<X-word-ms ms=300,100,119,220,679 index=4811 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-11,12-20,21-32>Would You Do Anything Differently
<X-word-ms ms=260,199,160,259,140 index=4812 character_ranges=0-3,4-10,11-15,16-23,24-27>Like Taking More Signals Per
<X-word-ms ms=279,220,199,159,260 index=4813 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-14,15-21>Day And Not Not Really
<X-word-ms ms=239,119,100,199,199,60,340 index=4814 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-7,8-14,15-19,20-22,23-30>I Mean A Happen Full Of Marging
Right As Europeans Europeans
Have More Market
<X-word-ms ms=159,119,100,359,220,79 index=4817 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-16,17-26,27-32,33-35>Because They Have Portfolio Marge In
<X-word-ms ms=140,159,260,299,439 index=4818 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-12,13-20,21-32>To Begin With Because Regulations
<X-word-ms ms=200,199,139,300,180 index=4819 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-18,19-21>Are Not That Street Us
<X-word-ms ms=159,100,159,99,240,539 index=4820 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-7,8-9,10-16,17-19>In The U.S Canada So
<X-word-ms ms=220,199,260,139,60,279 index=4821 character_ranges=0-0,1-3,4-10,11-14,15-18,19-25>I Do Hopper For The Margen
So In
<X-word-ms ms=399,100,39,260,279 index=4823 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-12,13-22,23-29>Order To Have Portfolio Margin
<X-word-ms ms=140,179,220,440,359 index=4824 character_ranges=0-2,3-4,5-6,7-9,10-16>The U.S Or Canada
I Don't Know
<X-word-ms ms=240,199,260,239,100 index=4826 character_ranges=0-5,6-9,10-12,13-16,17-21>Really But Us You Have
<X-word-ms ms=99,300,180,250,300 index=4827 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-8,9-13,14-18>To Have A Unit More
Than 100 Hundred And
Ten Thous Dollars Account
<X-word-ms ms=279,140,279,220,139 index=4830 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-12,13-16,17-19>To Really Ask For It
<X-word-ms ms=120,139,140,139,80,299,250 index=4831 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-9,10-13,14-16,17-24,25-28>We Can Ask For It Anyways And
<X-word-ms ms=199,139,180,199,300 index=4832 character_ranges=0-0,1-5,6-10,11-15,16-22>I Know That Most People
Are No Nobody Is
Really Trading
With Very Low Capital
Here So They
Point Is That If
We Have More Marging
Available Would
Here But My Rule
Of Exposure Is Five
New Signals Per Day
So I Cannot Open
<X-word-ms ms=180,99,220,279,119,60,119 index=4844 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-10,11-18,19-21,22-23,24-27>More Than 5 Signals In A Day
Sometimes It's From Markets
Like 12 Signals
<X-word-ms ms=119,59,160,139,60,359,220 index=4847 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-8,9-13,14-17,18-23,24-27>In A Date That Are Valid But
<X-word-ms ms=100,139,180,199,319,280 index=4848 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-14,15-19,20-23,24-29>They Don't Take Them And There
<X-word-ms ms=59,100,179,180,260,220,119 index=4849 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-7,8-11,12-16,17-19,20-24>Is A Big Why Even If Have
More Margin I
<X-word-ms ms=199,159,100,199,439 index=4851 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-10,11-13,14-16>Don't Do It So In
The Stock Market Things
Break Out In Waves
<X-word-ms ms=279,199,239,100,460 index=4854 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-13,14-16,17-23>They Break Out In Groups
They Break Out The
Move Tend To Move
Together And
Bear Markets Everything
Moves Together In Bullish
Market Sectors Move
Together You Have
These Waves Of Signals
<X-word-ms ms=280,219,400,79,239 index=4863 character_ranges=0-1,2-11,12-19,20-22,23-32>In Different Markets At Different
<X-word-ms ms=360,339,200,99,279 index=4864 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-12,13-16,17-23>One Two Three Day Window
<X-word-ms ms=280,300,199,119,260 index=4865 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-16,17-21>So You Don't Want Over
Exposed There
<X-word-ms ms=300,199,319,180,279 index=4867 character_ranges=0-4,5-6,7-11,12-16,17-21>Right I Have This Five
Day 5
Positions Maximum
Per Day Of Exposure
<X-word-ms ms=300,139,60,180,359 index=4871 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-9,10-14,15-25>And It's A Risk Management
Thing Is Something
Really Keep More
<X-word-ms ms=79,320,260,179,220 index=4874 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-18,19-21,22-27>Than Five Positions In Total
Long Short ETFs
<X-word-ms ms=180,220,140,99,200,219 index=4876 character_ranges=0-7,8-10,11-15,16-20,21-22,23-25>Whatever No More Than 5 So
The Next Day Probably
Have More Signals But
<X-word-ms ms=380,159,199,160,179 index=4879 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-17,18-21>Less Then The Next Day
<X-word-ms ms=100,99,180,239,220,579 index=4880 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-16,17-19,20-25>On The Same Group So Maybe
<X-word-ms ms=199,220,100,339,280 index=4881 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-12,13-17,18-21>Now There Are Only Two
<X-word-ms ms=279,279,180,180,179 index=4882 character_ranges=0-4,5-6,7-11,12-17,18-20>Sorry I Take Those To
Write And Keep On
A Key Post Myself
By It If You
<X-word-ms ms=159,239,319,260,779 index=4886 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-15,16-22>Put This Rule Of Number
<X-word-ms ms=199,240,239,100,319 index=4887 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-13,14-16,17-20>Down Find Seen Us Per
Day Which Is Only
<X-word-ms ms=299,160,220,60,479 index=4889 character_ranges=0-6,7-11,12-16,17-21,22-24>Happens From Last This So
If You Have
More Margin You
<X-word-ms ms=119,219,160,479,420 index=4892 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-19,20-28>Can Take More Trades Probably
In The Following Days
And We Really
Do That It Is
<X-word-ms ms=159,140,159,39,239,460 index=4896 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-20,21-25>Not That We Are Doing That
Because We Never
Have 10 Signals
<X-word-ms ms=139,79,220,239,179,440 index=4899 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-7,8-11,12-16,17-19>In A Day Two Days In
A Row It Doesn't
Happen Because The
Rules Of System Is
Very Specific So It
<X-word-ms ms=199,119,200,219,119,160 index=4904 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-14,15-22,23-25,26-31>Does Not Really Happens To Begin
With Right But We
<X-word-ms ms=230,199,279,260,260 index=4906 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-14,15-18,19-22>Could Take More Per Day
<X-word-ms ms=199,140,119,119,140,339 index=4907 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-11,12-14,15-17,18-21>But We Don't Do It And
<X-word-ms ms=260,239,160,179,140,180 index=4908 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-17,18-19,20-24>Also Not Only From A Risk
Management Perspective But
From An Operational
Perspective Will Be Very
<X-word-ms ms=260,140,159,300,340 index=4912 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-12,13-15,16-22>Hard To Enter 10 Trades
Per Days So If
You Risk For Exam
Pl 0.5 Person
Per Trade You Can
Take Five Positions
<X-word-ms ms=159,220,220,179,500 index=4918 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-16,17-19>Per Day And Still Be
Within The Res Parameters
<X-word-ms ms=219,119,100,140,299,460 index=4920 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-10,11-13,14-18,19-23>If You Want To Keep Push
Those Parameters As
<X-word-ms ms=139,240,500,159,340 index=4922 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-14,15-16,17-17>You Are Risking 1%
<X-word-ms ms=279,279,219,140,79,100 index=4923 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-11,12-14,15-18,19-24>Right So But If You Start
<X-word-ms ms=119,219,300,220,699 index=4924 character_ranges=0-1,2-7,8-13,14-16,17-20>To Think About It Can
You Put 10 Singles
<X-word-ms ms=140,79,220,439,119,340 index=4926 character_ranges=0-1,2-3,4-7,8-10,11-15,16-23>In A Day If They Trigger
He Will Be Completely
<X-word-ms ms=440,119,179,79,140,359 index=4928 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-16,17-19,20-27>You Know We Would Be Amassed
<X-word-ms ms=180,100,259,140,239,260 index=4929 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-10,11-14,15-21,22-24>You Can Run The Script Or
Something By I Like
<X-word-ms ms=140,99,160,159,159,140,239 index=4931 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-9,10-15,16-20,21-25,26-32>To Keep In Touch With This Spread
Live What Is Debit
<X-word-ms ms=140,199,340,199,239 index=4933 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-9,10-16,17-21>And Ask To Really Feel
<X-word-ms ms=220,300,179,180,460 index=4934 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-13,14-17,18-26>The Trade Best Way Possible
On You Know
<X-word-ms ms=140,440,180,219,360 index=4936 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-22,23-27>Its Two Risk Management Rule
That Prevents Us
From Doing It And
<X-word-ms ms=79,139,539,140,300 index=4939 character_ranges=0-1,2-8,9-19,20-22,23-25>Is Really Protecting US So
Its For Our Own
Protection On Our Management
<X-word-ms ms=260,140,219,300,140 index=4942 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-12,13-18,19-21>Of The Equity Curve So
<X-word-ms ms=139,140,79,159,260,239 index=4943 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-11,12-17,18-23,24-28>Again All Of These Rules They
<X-word-ms ms=140,380,479,60,159 index=4944 character_ranges=0-3,4-12,13-19,20-21,22-27>Work Together That's A Major
<X-word-ms ms=219,200,159,399,239 index=4945 character_ranges=0-4,5-9,10-14,15-23,24-26>Thing They Were Together So
If You Change
One It Will Change
Absolutely Everything In
<X-word-ms ms=159,200,239,380,679 index=4949 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-14,15-20>The Rest Of The Whole
Distribution Of Them Off
This System So It
<X-word-ms ms=100,139,140,300,119,159,340 index=4952 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-9,10-16,17-19,20-25,26-30>Is At Risk Manage My Rules Yeah
So Yeah I
<X-word-ms ms=139,300,119,260,219 index=4954 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-10,11-16,17-22>Mean If You Think There
<X-word-ms ms=60,119,159,380,260,279 index=4955 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-12,13-22,23-28,29-32>Are Some More Questions Right Now
Here Live So You
<X-word-ms ms=159,300,300,239,279 index=4957 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-11,12-20,21-26>Can Send The Question Later
<X-word-ms ms=260,300,139,199,320 index=4958 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-13,14-19>On In The Chat After
People Keep Seeing
This At Mine Will
Answer Those Questions Obviously
<X-word-ms ms=259,120,239,239,220 index=4962 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-10,11-14,15-16>Let Me Then Put A
IQ In The Channel
Of These Lessons
<X-word-ms ms=79,179,180,100,500 index=4965 character_ranges=0-3,4-9,10-12,13-15,16-24>That Going To Be Uploaded
So Again Either
Open Duty Session Next
<X-word-ms ms=159,79,119,180,239,260 index=4968 character_ranges=0-2,3-5,6-11,12-14,15-21,22-25>One Is Going To Really Sum
Up The Whole Thing
<X-word-ms ms=179,79,180,300,239,200 index=4970 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-14,15-18,19-23>That We Do Here For This
New Swim Training Master
<X-word-ms ms=240,159,79,180,219,119,140 index=4972 character_ranges=0-4,5-6,7-11,12-18,19-25,26-28,29-34>Class I Hope Really Hoping To Enjoy
<X-word-ms ms=140,219,380,220,239 index=4973 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-16,17-21,22-25>These One Session Guys And
Again Thank You
For Joining In
All Probably
<X-word-ms ms=279,220,259,120,79,99 index=4977 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-12,13-14,15-20,21-25>With Next One I Don't Know
<X-word-ms ms=100,39,220,259,260,220 index=4978 character_ranges=0-1,2-4,5-8,9-14,15-17,18-20>If It Was Going To Do
On Sunday
<X-word-ms ms=319,180,239,260,479 index=4980 character_ranges=0-6,7-9,10-15,16-20,21-29>Because It Seems That Although
I Believe That Where
<X-word-ms ms=320,179,320,179,140 index=4982 character_ranges=0-1,2-5,6-11,12-14,15-19>He Was Going It Wasn
<X-word-ms ms=79,220,460,219,260 index=4983 character_ranges=0-4,5-7,8-9,10-14,15-19>Going Be A Good Time
To Join You
Know For All People
<X-word-ms ms=260,159,199,380,400 index=4986 character_ranges=0-3,4-7,8-12,13-18,19-27>From All Time Zones Probably
<X-word-ms ms=239,119,199,200,359 index=4987 character_ranges=0-2,3-6,7-11,12-15,16-20>Not The Best But They
<X-word-ms ms=79,180,199,159,140,79,159,180 index=4988 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-14,15-17,18-20,21-23,24-31,32-35>Are Still Going To Do It Because You
<X-word-ms ms=299,120,199,239,159 index=4989 character_ranges=0-3,4-8,9-11,12-17,18-20>Know Give Us Peace Of
<X-word-ms ms=260,220,199,200,139 index=4990 character_ranges=0-3,4-6,7-9,10-15,16-17>Mind So So Again I
<X-word-ms ms=140,139,160,199,220,199 index=4991 character_ranges=0-5,6-10,11-16,17-21,22-27,28-32>Really Hope Enjoy This Video Guys
<X-word-ms ms=139,140,159,539,380 index=4992 character_ranges=0-2,3-7,8-10,11-19,20-30>And Want To Complete Everything
<X-word-ms ms=220,180,419,120,139 index=4993 character_ranges=0-1,2-6,7-14,15-17,18-23>On Next Session Is About
<X-word-ms ms=180,99,180,220,279,180 index=4994 character_ranges=0-2,3-8,9-11,12-13,14-18,19-23>Its Going Be A Very Good
One So Again
<X-word-ms ms=159,300,99,160,119,340 index=4996 character_ranges=0-4,5-8,9-13,14-18,19-22,23-29>Thank You Very Much For Coming
And See In The
Chat In Few Minutes
We Are Going To